<schedule id="uk.blocweekend.2012" title="Bloc.2012" xmlns="http://gaa.st/giggity#sched"><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/google.png" id="google" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/lastfm.png" id="lastfm" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/wikipedia.png" id="wikipedia" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/myspace.png" id="myspace" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/soundcloud.png" id="soundcloud" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/discogs.png" id="discogs" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/youtube.png" id="youtube" /><line id="mainarena" title="Main Arena"><item endTime="1341604800" id="union" startTime="1341601200" title="Union"><itemDescription>Union

After hosting a stage last year UNION, join forces with Bloc once again to programme our main stage. They &#160;are joined by Snoop Dogg, DOOM and Amon Tobin&#8217;s ISAM live show.

UNION are responsible for the secret as f*ck/pop-up rave scene that&#8217;s swept across the capital. With a policy of bringing left-of-centre dance music events to birth without warning and with no promotion beyond a single post on their facebook page, UNION parties regularly have no pre-announced venue or headliner at all before the night of the party. And what a party&#8230;

With UNION at the controls regulars have come to expect a no boundaries approach to glitched up bass music. It&#8217;s the kind of deranged and sweaty soiree where the great and good from dubstep, drum n bass and techno turn up to party and play to an animalistic crowd of clued up party people. Now producing major events under their own steam, UNION&#8217;s ferociously guarded success just keeps on growing, establishing them as a leading force in the new order of things.

As well as co-programming the stage UNION will be represented at Bloc via a DJ set from themselves and a live performance from Amon Tobin: ISAM.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Union" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Union" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341610200" id="amontobinisam" startTime="1341604800" title="Amon Tobin: ISAM"><itemDescription>Amon Tobin: ISAM

Amon Tobin is the latest headline addition to the UNION stage at Bloc. The masterful Amon returns to Bloc with an all new presentation of his ISAM project, featuring a stunning 25&#8242; x 14&#8242; x 8&#8242; multi-dimensional / shape shifting 3-D art installation surrounding Tobin and enveloping him and the audience in a beyond 3-D experience. One of the most visionary artists working in electronic music over the last fifteen years, Amon has established a reputation for musical ingenuity that is unconfined by genre, whether working with the classical avant garde Kronos Quartet, or D&#8217;n'B legends Noisia, or on his own in some invented form. A modernist in the best sense of the word, his audio-visual live show extravaganza pushes the boundaries of what a live show can really achieve, musically flitting from experimental electronics to resounding rhythmic power and beyond. Amon Tobin is the very special guest on the Union stage.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Amon_Tobin" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/amon-tobin/amon-tobin-isam" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Amon+Tobin%3A+ISAM" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WWai4UZ0OqI" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341615600" id="doom" startTime="1341610200" title="DOOM"><itemDescription>DOOM

[US / Live]

A counterpoint to the cloying bling obsession that usually engulfs hip-hop luminaries, DOOM &#8211; or MF Doom as he was known until 2010 &#8211; is part-comic book villain, part next-level rap genius, and part disturbed psycho. Although a fixture on the underground rap scene since the 80s as a producer and MC, it wasn&#8217;t until 2004 that his collaboration with Madlib as Madvillainy caused the wider world to sit up and take notice of his oblique and highly distinctive talent. Working murky, lo-fi production against unsettling yet often hilarious lyrics delivered in his instantly-recognisable drawl, consequent albums MM..Food?, Venomous Villain (under the moniker Viktor Vaughn) and The Mouse and The Mask (with Danger Mouse) cemented his status as wayward hip-hop&#8217;s most independent and intriguing voice. Infamous for his erratic temper during his live shows &#8211; he&#8217;s even been known to send stand-ins to perform in his place without telling anyone &#8211; a DOOM gig is certainly among modern hip-hop&#8217;s most unpredictable and exciting
prospects.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/DOOM" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=DOOM" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KfwYpJToTYI" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341619200" id="snoopdogg" startTime="1341615600" title="Snoop Dogg"><itemDescription>Snoop Dogg

[US / Live]

Global superstar, cultural phenomenon and rap&#8217;s most charismatic frontman Snoop Dogg needs little introduction, such is his overwhelming presence in music history. Alongside Dr Dre, he was responsible for launching the classic west coast sound into the homes of millions, and has managed to stay at the forefront of his game throughout.

Snoop is a universally adored figurehead in recent years, a loveable mix of pop culture icon and Yoda-esque ghetto guru with an ear for a P-Funk hook and a drawl like no-one else on earth. &#160;More unusually still, he&#8217;s kept his credibility, managing to perform surreal stunts (like last year&#8217;s youtube video for Wales&#8217;s giant vegetable growing record holder) while still churning out epochal, high-quality hits such as &#8216;Drop It Like It&#8217;s Hot&#8217;. A true institution and utterly unique star of our times, Snoop&#8217;s exclusive Bloc show comes ahead of his latest album, &#8216;Reincarnated&#8217;.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Snoop+Dogg" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Snoop_Dogg" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/snoopdogg" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/snoopdogg" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Snoop+Dogg" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m3Lwx4HziNw" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341622800" id="billynasty" startTime="1341619200" title="Billy Nasty"><itemDescription>Billy Nasty

A veteran of UK techno and electro who&#8217;s never rested on his laurels, Billy Nasty continues to fly the flag for quality techno-based music in its many forms. Starting out at the Brain club with Lost&#8217;s Steve Bicknell in the late 80s, he went on to become one of the international techno scene&#8217;s most travelled jocks, honing a fierce style that found an outlet in his legendary label Tortured towards the end of the century. He also championed the quality electro scene, most notably through his venerated Electric imprint, home to some of the sound&#8217;s most seminal club hits. A resident at Bloc since the outset, he continues to travel far and wide as a DJ, and has recently found acclaim through his collaborative work with Keith Tenniswood as Radionasty.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Billy+Nasty" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djbillynasty" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/djbillynasty" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Billy+Nasty" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e_I1iby22Xo" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341680400" id="richiehawtin" startTime="1341622800" title="Richie Hawtin"><itemDescription>Richie Hawtin

[CA / DJ]

It&#8217;s been a long time coming, but finally, high emperor of techno Richie Hawtin is playing at Bloc. A tireless ambassador for techno music&#8217;s forward-looking potential and one of the genre&#8217;s few DJs who can truly take control of vast crowds and put them under his spell, Hawtin&#8217;s ascent began a few years after the first wave of Detroit techno artists blew his mind at the legendary Music Institute. He quickly set up his own outpost for the work of fellow techno acolytes including Dan Bell, Kenny Larkin and Speedy J, Plus 8, before transforming the scene&#8217;s direction with his timeless Plastikman productions. Austere, tripped-out, and unlike any dance music around, Plastikman heralded a new minimalist approach that remains central to techno and its innumerable related subgenres to this day. Renowned for his constant search for something &#8216;new&#8217;, his Minus label has been a world-beating springboard for artists like Magda, Troy Pierce, and many more, working a close knit mentality into its aesthetic to create an
evolving but distinctive &#8216;Minus&#8217; sound along the way. As a DJ, his scope is perhaps broader but equally singular, forensically deconstructing tracks into component parts and rebuilding them for the one-off experience that is a Richie Hawtin DJ set.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Richie+Hawtin" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richie_Hawtin" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/richiehawtin" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Richie+Hawtin" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9RJlvCe7W-w" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341685800" id="garynuman" startTime="1341680400" title="Gary Numan"><itemDescription>Gary Numan

[UK / Live]

The original synth-pop outsider, Gary Numan&#8217;s stark collision of raw punk energy, electronic production, and sci-fi themes has been widely imitated but rarely equaled. Originally emerging in the same fertile period that saw epochal British acts like Depeche Mode and Human League move beyond rock&#8217;s tired guitars and embrace Kraftwerk&#8217;s robotic charms, Numan forged an idiosyncratic identity that swung between morose introspection, effortlessly anthemic &#160;hooks, and excitable alien funk. His global hits &#8216;Are Friends Electric&#8217; and &#8216;Cars&#8217; still raise the roof at office parties and underground techno meccas alike, but his extensive back catalogue often travels down darker and more abstract creative avenues, prefiguring numerous key aspects of modern techno and electronica. Continually touring and creating new music for over three decades, he&#8217;s rarely diverted from his distinctively skewed man-machine aesthetic, making him an unparalleled influence to countless musicians and a hero to legions of fans.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Gary+Numan" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Gary+Numan" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Gary+Numan" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Uu6MDdxBork" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341691200" id="battles" startTime="1341685800" title="Battles"><itemDescription>Battles

[US / Live]

NYC&#8217;s lauded experimental rock band Battles spent four years honing their ultra-technical sound before erupting globally in 2007 with single, &#8216;Atlas&#8217;. Labyrinthine in structure yet giddily indebted to a brazen glam rock stomp, the track heralded a remarkable new approach to guitar-based music that was promptly labeled &#8216;math&#8217; rock. Their first album Mirrored was certainly a tour de force of musical intellect, but beneath the songs&#8217; maddening layers emerged a playfulness and pop sensibility that was frequently lacking in the po-faced &#160;efforts of most of their peers. The band rapidly gained a reputation for blistering live performances, and toured extensively until the run up to second album Gloss Drop, a more accessible work that saw the band harness their harmonic logarithms to compact and compelling effect.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Battles" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battles_(band)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/battlestheband" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Battles" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4D7RzUtFEps" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341698400" id="orbital" startTime="1341691200" title="Orbital"><itemDescription>Orbital

[UK / Live]

Rightly ranked among the best-loved UK dance acts of all time, Orbital&#8217;s famed live shows conclusively proved that electronic dance music in its pure form could hold sway on a major festival stage. Part of the first wave of musicians to take the nascent acid house scene beyond the warehouses of the M25 (the road that famously inspired their moniker) and on to world domination, brothers Phil and Paul Hartnoll shot to prominence on the back of their timeless hit &#8216;Chime&#8217;, fusing the abstract moods of Detroit techno with unabashedly widescreen atmospherics to hugely successful effect. Still resonating as gloriously as they ever did, Orbital&#8217;s special power to unify dance music&#8217;s myriad tribes shows few signs of abating over twenty years on.

Check out Orbitals&#8217;s new video &#8216;Wonky&#8217; here.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Orbital" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orbital_(band)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/orbitalofficial" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/orbital-4/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Orbital" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q9675nvyses" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341705600" id="flyinglotus" startTime="1341698400" title="Flying Lotus"><itemDescription>Flying Lotus

[US / Live] - UK Exclusive

Stephen Ellis, the given name of&#160;Flying Lotus describes his post-everything amalgam of influences as &#8220;surrealist hip-hop&#8221; &#8211; but that barely skims the surface of his astonishing musical ability. The ambitious complexity of his albums 1983, Low End Theory and Cosmogramma are testament to the kind of innate talent that only comes along once or twice in a generation, channeling bass music, hip-hop, avant-garde jazz and space age psychedelia into wild new forms. A cornerstone artist on Warp, he&#8217;s also gained considerable acclaim for his own Brainfeeder label, worked with artists as varied as Thom Yorke and Erykha Badu, and topped just about every music poll worth topping at some point or other. A genuine auteur of modern electronic music.


</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Flying+Lotus" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flying_Lotus" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/flyinglotus" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/flyinglotus/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Flying+Lotus" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wtjZOf0WmdE" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341711000" id="squarepusher" startTime="1341705600" title="Squarepusher"><itemDescription>Squarepusher

[UK / Live]

Tom &#8216;Squarepusher&#8217; Jenkinson&#8217;s innovative work spans almost every musical genre, although he&#8217;s perhaps best loved for his experimental drum&#8217;n&#8217;bass with a heavy jazz fusion influence. Initially known for his insane blend of superfast jungle breaks with Aphex-style synth textures, he went on to scale previously unheard levels of sonic sophistication, inspired in no small part by jazz fusion pioneers like Mahavishnu Orchestra and Weather Report.

Claiming a closer affinity with jazz than jungle, Jenkinson&#8217;s early EPs as Squarepusher and the Duke of Harringay &#160;were initially disregarded by the jungle scene, but found a ready audience in fans of experimental electronica. Signing a deal with the mighty Warp label in 1995, his albums Feed Me Weird Things, Hard Normal Daddy and Music Is Rotted One Note are uncontested classics of the era, while subsequent releases saw him continually refining his fusion of composition, programming, and musicianship. Performing with a jaw-dropping display of virtuosity &#8211; particularly on his beloved bass guitar &#8211; Jenkinson is widely regarded as one of modern music&#8217;s most spectacular talents, as his incomparable gigs attest.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Squarepusher" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Squarepusher" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/doyouknowsquarepusher" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Squarepusher" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XvLAKrVbCBM" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341716400" id="jeffmills" startTime="1341711000" title="Jeff Mills"><itemDescription>Jeff Mills

[US / Live]

There are techno DJs, and then there&#8217;s Jeff Mills. Schooled in the eclectic radio scene of early 80&#8242;s Detroit, Mills developed a rapid-fire mixing style that became the blueprint for virtually all the city&#8217;s techno DJs, though few have managed to achieve his mythical status and universal respect. A co-founder of the equally revered Underground Resistance collective, Mills took the plaintive sci-fi moods of his techno forebears May, Saunderson and Atkins into fierce and uncharted realms, stripping tracks back to their bare bones and unleashing them into the mix one after the other with nuclear intensity and unremitting funk. An avowed futurist, Mills&#8217; own recording projects not only pioneered but pretty much set the high watermark for many of the scene&#8217;s most prominent movements, from industrial to hardcore, tribal and minimal techno, while recent years have seen him investigate slower, more hypnotic moods. In full force , pure techno is rarely finer than in Mills&#8217; furiously flickering hands.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jeff+Mills" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jeff_Mills" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jeffmillsofficialspace" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Jeff+Mills" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KevUFO2moZI" type="youtube" /></item></line><line id="residentadvisorhub" title="Resident Advisor Hub"><item endTime="1341601200" id="stevereichbangonacanallstars" startTime="1341594000" title="Steve Reich &amp; Bang On A Can Allstars"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Steve+Reich+%26+Bang+On+A+Can+Allstars" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341604800" id="nicolasjaar" startTime="1341601200" title="Nicolas Jaar"><itemDescription>Nicolas Jaar

[US / Live]

One of the few musicians who genuinely deserves the term &#8216;prodigious&#8217;, Nicolas Jaar was already making waves on the underground house and techno scene at the tender age of 17, when Seth Troxler described his debut release for Wolf &amp; Lamb as &#8220;one of the most talented minds dance music is about to see develop&#8221;. He was bang on the money; Jaar quickly built up a sizeable following thanks to a stream of killer EPs, and was touring the globe extensively by the time he enrolled at university in 2009. His defining moment to date, though, is his smash 2011 album &#8216;Space Is Only Noise&#8217;, a startling and spanking fresh collision of sophisticated slo-mo house, avant-pop, and psyche disco-techno that sounds unlike anything else around. The album&#8217;s success triggered a string of sell out live shows, allowing Jaar&#8217;s advanced musical abilities the space to really shine, and cementing his status as one of leftfield dance music&#8217;s most engaging and exciting figures.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Nicolas+Jaar" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nicolas_Jaar" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/nicolasjaar" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/nicolas-jaar" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1GX_4PgUhYo" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341608400" id="digitalmystikz" startTime="1341604800" title="Digital Mystikz"><itemDescription>Digital Mystikz

[UK / DJ]

Renowned for their key role in the venerated DMZ club nights and label, London duo Digital Mystikz have long been considered among the most integral and influential figures on the dubstep scene. Comprised of Mala and Coki, Digital Mystikz anthems like &#8216;Pathways&#8217;, &#8216;Haunted&#8217;, and &#8216;Anti-War Dub&#8217; are fundamental entries into the bass music canon, inspiring countless producers and DJs to step up and make their voices heard. The duo&#8217;s ability to spot and break new talent is long-established, and they were rewarded in kind when Mary Anne Hobbes supported them relentlessly on her Radio 1 show, helping to break the sound they pioneered on a national and eventually global level. The pair&#8217;s acclaimed LPs Return II Space and Urban Ethics are essential listening for any fan of the style, and sealed their status as genuine UK bass royalty.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Digital+Mystikz" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Digital_Mystikz" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/malamystikz" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/streeets/digital-mystikz-essential-mix" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Digital+Mystikz" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aVpjPuzlvus" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341612000" id="shackleton" startTime="1341608400" title="Shackleton"><itemDescription>Shackleton

[UK / Live]

One of a clutch of artists to start exploring the boundaries of bass music towards the end of the last decade, Sam Shackleton&#8217;s maverick combination of intricate, snaking percussion, hypnotic melodies, seriously deep bass lines and dubwise sensibilities has made him one of the scene&#8217;s most highly-rated producers. Along with Appleblim he ran the venerated Skull Disco label, releasing a series of EPs that instantly became classics, heralding a fresh and experimental era for UK electronic music. With a sound that bore little resemblance to anything else around, he quickly formed an evangelical fanbase stretching outside the restrictions of the club scene and into the wider world. His acclaimed live show is renowned for its head-spinning, mind-expanding brilliance.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Shackleton" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/shackletonmusic" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Shackleton" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Shackleton" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NZwPDttOm2M" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341615600" id="xhin" startTime="1341612000" title="Xhin"><itemDescription>Xhin

[Singapore / ]

Besides famed megaclub Zouk, Singapore is not widely renowned for its pool of techno talent, but Xhin&#8217;s music is so otherwordly it barely matters where he comes from. Known for layering intricate, sometimes obtuse IDM-style production over hypnotic and club-focussed rhythms, he&#8217;d bubbled under with a few functional tech-house efforts in the mid-00s before his underground hit &#8216;Link&#8217; for Stroboscopic Artefacts established him as a central player in the pure techno resurgence of the last few years. His 2011 album &#8216;Swords&#8217; was one of the genre&#8217;s more challenging but rewarding longplayers of recent times, largely abandoning straight-up sounds and delving deeper into drone, industrial and dark ambient textures. DJ-wise, he&#8217;s perhaps a little less experimental but no less intense than he is in the studio, throwing together new and classic techno with well-timed forays into bass, house, and abstract electronica.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Xhin" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/xhin" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Xhin" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Xhin" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yBfZGgXO-L4" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341622800" id="sandwelldistrict" startTime="1341615600" title="Sandwell District"><itemDescription>Sandwell District

[UK / Live]

Originally formed in 2002 by British techno stalwart Female, Sandwell District is now a collaborative effort alongside Regis and Function, refining over the years an austere yet rich minimalist techno sound. They count Marcel Dettmann, Laurent Garnier, Miss Kitten, Jeff Mills, and Richie Hawtin among their many devotees, and have been credited with spurring the welcome resurgence of gimmick-free pure techno that&#8217;s come back to prominence in recent years. Respectful to the classic pioneers of the 90s while rewiring the sound&#8217;s DNA for a fresh generation of techno fans, their debut album Feed Forward was roundly proclaimed to be one of the foremost long-players of the year, incorporating industrial ambience, haunting Sahko-style minimalism and tightly-wound dark hour techno to brilliant effect.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Sandwell+District" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/animal-farm/sandwell-district-live-animal" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Sandwell+District" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Sandwell+District" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=245edaBPV8Q" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341626400" id="carlcraig69" startTime="1341622800" title="Carl Craig-69"><itemDescription>Carl Craig &#8211; 69

[US / Live]

Detroit techno legend Carl Craig&#8217;s rarely been out of the spotlight in his 23-year career, continually leading the way at the vanguard of electronic music as a producer, remixer, DJ and label head. Performing that rare trick of pleasing the purists and slaying the masses with equal aplomb, he&#8217;s the kind of manifestly talented musician who&#8217;s as adept at tearing festivals apart with slamming DJ sets as he is experimenting with Moritz Von Oswald on an electronic interpretation of Ravel&#8217;s Bolero.

Of all his guises, though, perhaps the best loved is his 69 project. A series of records throughout the early 90s that redefined the boundaries of the genre with a cut-up, sample-heavy aesthetic shot through with spacey funk and machine soul, &#160;69 is now finally presented in a live format by the man himself. A rare chance to hear a master of his craft reliving one of his most exciting creative periods.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carl_Craig" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/69" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Carl+Craig-69" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e2WGnM8JhE" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341630000" id="danielstefanik" startTime="1341626400" title="Daniel Stefanik"><itemDescription>Daniel Stefanik

[DE / DJ]

In a world of seemingly infinite unimaginative variations on tired deep house and techno themes, Germany&#8217;s Daniel Stefanik brings a welcome creative spark to proceedings on his releases for Moon Harbour, Freunde-Am Tanzen, and Dessous. Combining a strong grounding in classic American dance music with a taut and restrained European flair, his productions and sets balance straight-ahead grooves with unfussy contemporary flourishes. Quietly ascending the ranks while staying true to the sound that&#8217;s made his name, he&#8217;s emerged as one of the German scene&#8217;s most reliable and consistent underground figures.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Daniel+Stefanik" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/danielstefanik" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/daniel-stefanik" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Daniel+Stefanik" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ipCb_0WVjTI" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341673200" id="ricardovillalobos" startTime="1341630000" title="Ricardo Villalobos"><itemDescription>Ricardo Villalobos

[CHILE / DJ]

Of all the underground DJ-producers who&#8217;ve risen to prominence in the last decade, Chile&#8217;s Ricardo Villalobos surely inspires the most slavish devotion, creating an almost shamanic aura and an inevitable road-block wherever he appears. Although rightly regarded as a figurehead for the global minimal techno explosion, both his DJ sets and his production work transcend the genre tag, forging a warped realignment of four-four club music that owes as much to modern classical and the indigenous sounds of his homeland as it does to Kraftwerk and Derrick May.

Notorious for inspiring eight to ten hour long mass freakouts on the dancefloor, his own productions are similarly revered and often just as epic, consistently defying clich&#233; to forge oblique excursions into techno&#8217;s furthest-flung microcosms.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Ricardo+Villalobos" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ricardo_Villalobos" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/ricardococoon" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/r_co/ricardo-villalobos-2702" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Ricardo+Villalobos" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nzxyw_XgMyU" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341676800" id="actress" startTime="1341673200" title="Actress"><itemDescription>Actress

[UK / Live]

When Darren Cunningham aka Actress&#8217;s Hazyville came out in 2008, it sounded unlike anything else out there, spinning distant echoes of Moodymann, Jan Jelinek, 80s R&amp;B, and wonky into unusually gritty yet effortlessly musical new forms. As well as running the excellent Werk Discs label, Actress&#8217;s own music has continued to evolve across singles for Prime Numbers, Nonplus, and Honest Jon&#8217;s, refining a deliberately lo-fi sound that manages to extract extraordinary and wildly innovative ideas from seemingly disparate ingredients. His second album, Splazsh, came out on Honest Jon&#8217;s at the end of May 2010, and it&#8217;s easily a candidate for the experimental techno record of the year.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Actress" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Actress_(musician)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/actress" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Actress" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0wsKiQDTBzg" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341683100" id="apparatband" startTime="1341676800" title="Apparat Band"><itemDescription>Apparat Band

[DE / Live]

Sascha Ring, the Berlin artist better known as Apparat, has been a restless force in contemporary electronic music for a decade. In that time he&#8217;s released four acclaimed Apparat albums, collaborated with fellow Berlin luminaries Modeselektor and Ellen Allien, and performed his intense live show in front of thousands at clubs and festivals around the world. Broadly speaking, he produces richly textured, emotional electronica and heavy sci-fi soul &#8211; the missing link between Steve Reich and Radiohead, perhaps. Most recently he made the full leap from lonely studio-dwelling solo artist to certified frontman with his latest album Devil&#8217;s Walk, a largely straight-ahead band project informed as much by the Cure, Roxy Music and Cocteau Twins as James Blake and Four Tet. His all new full group live show delivers highlights from the album alongside magically reworked hits from his much-loved back catalogue, in certified heart-wrenching Apparat style.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Apparat+Band" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apparat_(musician)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/apparat" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/evil_concussion/2012-02-22-apparat-band-live" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4AhpoqTkuwY" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341686700" id="snd" startTime="1341683100" title="SND"><itemDescription>SND

[UK / Live]

SND was formed in Sheffield, UK, in 1998 by Mark Fell and Mat Steel. Inspired by highly focused label runs such as Mike Ink&#8217;s Studio One or Thomas Brinkmann&#8217;s Max/Ernst, and influenced equally by house, techno, and experimental music, they were picked up by the now defunct Mille Plateaux, whose owner Achim Szepanski heard Peter Ford DJ&#8217;ing their debut record. Thus began a period which saw three critically acclaimed albums for Mille Plateaux, pioneering a sound that always influenced but also resisted the so called &#8216;clicks and cuts&#8217; movement that built up around them.

After a five year recording hiatus, SND returned in 2008 &#160;with the release &#8216;4,5,6&#8217;, which spurred an extensive period of touring (notably with fellow experimental deities Autechre), a reworking of Billie Jean for the &#8216;Recovery&#8217; box set on Fractured Records, a major feature in the Wire magazine, a tour of Japan with Raster-Noton, and eventually their most recent effort, Atavism, a continuation of their stark, considered, and expertly programmed sound.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/SND" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Snd_(band)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Snd" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=SND" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nY8PeoI0Vhk" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341690300" id="byetone" startTime="1341686700" title="Byetone"><itemDescription>Byetone

[DE / Live]

Although he&#8217;s co-owned the Raster-Noton label since the start, until recently Olaf Bender aka Byetone was less prolific than his colleagues Carsten Nicolai and Frank Bretschneider, and seemed to be concentrating more on the label&#8217;s extensive visual and design projects as much as his own musical efforts. That all changed in 2008 with his Death Of A Typographer album, a tense and brilliantly-realised fusion of immense drone distortion and lithe electro grooves. The album spurred a new, dancefloor-orientated direction for Raster-Noton, and the 2011 follow-up &#8216;Systema&#8217; emerged as one of the most brutal yet beautiful experimental electronic releases of recent years. As you&#8217;d expect, Byetone&#8217;s live shows head straight for the jugular with claustrophobic walls of sound, apocalyptic glitch-outs, and kinetic jackhammer beats.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Byetone" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/benderbyetone" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Byetone" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Byetone" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SdwhhhM-iQU" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341694800" id="alvanoto" startTime="1341690300" title="Alva Noto"><itemDescription>Alva Noto

[DE / Live]

A longtime explorer of electronic music&#8217;s most abstract boundaries, Alva Noto aka Carsten Nicolai is well known for his concept-based experiments fusing electronic sound-design with art and architecture theory. A prolific and committed composer, his work has featured in numerous installations at prestigious galleries including the Guggenheim Museum and Tate Modern, but he&#8217;s also an ardent fan of body-shaking classic techno. These two poles feed into his mind-blowing Alva Noto live shows, where intense swathes of noise are underpinned by uncannily funky electro-glitch rhythms and stunning visuals. Pitched somewhere between the fragmented crackles of Oval, the logarithmic genius of Authechre, and the robotic snap of Kraftwerk, the Alva Noto live show genuinely warrants the term &#8216;mind-blowing&#8217;.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Alva+Noto" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alva_Noto" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/alvanoto" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Alva+Noto" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-SFYfFBdzNQ" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341698400" id="fourtet" startTime="1341694800" title="Four Tet"><itemDescription>Four Tet

[UK / DJ]

From his pioneering work with avant-garde band Tortoise to his stunning albums Everything Ecstatic, Pause and Rounds, Kieran Hebden aka Four Tet has consistently delivered some the finest alternative electronic music of the last decade. Variously delving into post-folk, trip-hop, broken beat and alternative house, Hebden doesn&#8217;t fit comfortably in any particular genre pigeon hole, and his richly layered compositions are all the better for it. A passionate advocate of quality dance music in all its forms, Four Tet DJ sets are as eclectic and carefully crafted as you&#8217;d expect, with deep house, techno, garage and experimental tones all tied together seamlessly. Moving away from &#160;the languid &#160;instrumental hip hop breaks that made his name in recent years and more firmly onto the dancefloor, Hebden&#8217;s hugely popular contribution to the Fabric mix series was roundly regarded as one of the finest mixes of 2011.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Four+Tet" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kieran_Hebden" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/fourtetkieranhebden" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/four-tet/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Four+Tet" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iQ_Yu_4zeo0" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341702000" id="clark" startTime="1341698400" title="Clark"><itemDescription>Clark

[UK / Live]

Combining overtly processed crunches and clicks with smart synthy textures and heavily processed rhythms, Chris Clark&#8217;s intense electronica is by turns ominous, lush, aggressive and beguiling. Clark, who lived in Bristol and Brighton before settling in Birmingham, debuted on Warp in 2001 while he was still at university, and went on to release a string of stylistically unbound EPs and albums over the next eight years, showcasing a rare and unique mastery of his machines. With overdriven sounds and unsettling atmospheres overlapping with paradoxically comforting and elegant synths, Clark constructs a buzzing and claustrophobic universe all of his own.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Clark" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chris_Clark_(musician)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/throttleclark" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Clark" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ymh13G8YgQE" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341705600" id="monolake" startTime="1341702000" title="Monolake"><itemDescription>Monolake

[DE / Live Surround Sound]

Robert Henke is widely acknowledged as one of electronic music&#8217;s finest mastercraftsmen, a rare talent who can combine the most advanced sound design and production theory with instinctive musical talent like few others. His early work for Berlin institution Chain Reaction heralded an atmospheric, highly considered take on the city&#8217;s dub-techno sound in the mid-90s, but Monolake soon broke out of the constraints of four-four techno, with subsequent releases working echoes of drum n bass, ambient, and unclassifiable avant-garde studio experiments into an impossibly advanced-sounding whole. His live show at Bloc 2012 is a full surround sound collaborative performance with the Dutch artist Tarik Barri, who contributes stunning real time visuals, an artist Robert has been working with since 2009 for his Monolake live shows.

The appearance is a welcome return for Henke who last performed at Bloc 2008, also in full surround sound and in the middle of the audience. In a recent published essay, he recalls the experience:

&#8220;In spring 2008 I was invited to play at the Bloc in the UK. I arrived at the venue, a big dancefloor, a big stage, four impressive stacks of Funktion One speakers, and a FOH mixer set up at the back of the dancefloor, which happend to be still quite central in that big room. When I arrived an other artist was performing. The sound on the dancefloor was quite good. I walked backstage, entered the stage to set up my equipment and was totally frustrated by the fact that the sound on stage had absolutely nothing to do with the experience down on the dancefloor. I decided that I would want to play next to the FOH mixer and not on stage. The organizers looked at me with a funny expression; a headliner who wants to play off stage at a 2500 people event? Yes. I played where I could actually play with the PA, where I could shape every detail, every wave of bass, every single snare sound in a way which created the most impact on the dancefloor. And, I was less than one meter away from the people, on their level. It
was one of the best Monolake sets I ever did. We all had a great time.&#8221;

To read the full article, click here.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Monolake" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Monolake" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/monolake/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Monolake" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9A1BwBI_UhE" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341710100" id="scuba" startTime="1341705600" title="Scuba"><itemDescription>Scuba

UK Exclusive [UK / DJ]

Scuba (Paul Rose) is the founder of the influential and consistently high quality Hotflush Recordings, and a first-rate DJ and producer in his own right. &#160;From an early introduction to the scene playing the pirate radio stations of the early 90s, his profile has exploded in the last five years, combining techno and dubstep with his own distinct and accomplished sense of musicality. His last full-length album Triangulation topped charts all over the world, &#160;while 2011 saw&#160; &#8211; amongst other triumphs &#8211; critical and commercial success for his DJ-Kicks mix, plus a bona fide club smash in the form of the dizzily euphoric &#8217;Adrenalin&#8217;. As ever, expect &#160;Scuba&#8217;s record bag to be bursting with exclusive dubs of uncompromising calibre.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Scuba" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Scuba+(4)" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Scuba" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FuwERY7woXA" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341718200" id="atolmodeselektormarceldettmannshed" startTime="1341710100" title="A.T.O.L. = Modeselektor +Marcel Dettmann +Shed"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=A.T.O.L.+%3D+Modeselektor+%2BMarcel+Dettmann+%2BShed" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341723600" id="ellenallien" startTime="1341718200" title="Ellen Allien"><itemDescription>Ellen Allien

[DE / DJ]

Regularly referred to as the &#8220;first lady&#8221; of Berlin techno, Ellen Allien does indeed represent everything that makes the German capital city such a key location for electronic music. Combining impeccable taste in music with a distinctive brand of independent entrepreneurship, her label Bpitch Control has emerged as one of the global leaders for alternative electronic sounds. As an artist, both her solo work and her collaborations with Apparat &#160;and others have wowed audiences in her homeland and beyond, taking in house, techno, pop, minimalism, and new-wave moods with unrestricted glee. As you&#8217;d expect from someone who runs a label that&#8217;s made stars out of talents as diverse as Modeselektor, Paul Kalkbrenner and Telefon Tel Aviv, her DJ sets rarely get stuck in one genre for too long, combining classic Teutonic stylishness with unabashed rave-friendly force.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Ellen+Allien" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ellen_Allien" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/ellenallien" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/nicolas-jaar/flashy-flashy" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Ellen+Allien" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hAdy15aO2Qs" type="youtube" /></item></line><line id="carharttdome" title="Carhartt Dome"><item endTime="1341601200" id="twilliamsb2bdusky" startTime="1341594000" title="T Williams b2b Dusky"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=T+Williams+b2b+Dusky" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341604800" id="midland" startTime="1341601200" title="Midland"><itemDescription>Midland

[UK / DJ]

Midland erupted onto a house and techno scene in need of some new ideas in 2010 with the anthemic &#8216;Your Words Matter&#8217;, alongside longtime friend Pearson Sound . Rooted in house and techno, tempered by dubstep&#8217;s bassy churn, and enhanced by cinematic electronica sophistication, subsequent releases on Phonica, More Music and Aus have consistently marked him out as a producer whose tastes reach far beyond the dancefloor. As a DJ, Midland&#8217;s sets touch on numerous cornerstones of contemporary and classic dance music, and he&#8217;s as at home with young bucks like Joy Orbison or Ben Ufo as he is venerable talents like James Zabiela, Steffi or Will Saul. Unrestricted by the usual club music pigeon holes, he&#8217;s certainly among the leftfield house and techno scene&#8217;s most promising individuals.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Midland" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/midland" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Midland" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cLPg-ALg7n0" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341608400" id="appleblim" startTime="1341604800" title="Appleblim"><itemDescription>Appleblim

[UK / DJ]

Co-founder of avant-dubstep label Skull Disco with Shackleton, Appleblim is one of British music&#8217;s most interesting and inspiring characters, whether solo, as part of one of his many collaborations, or behind the decks. Having placed his stamp on the scene with two bona fide classics on Skull Disco &#8211; &#8216;Vansan&#8217; and &#8216;Circling&#8217; &#8211; he went on to form the Applepips label, releasing music from established scene heroes like T++, Sven Weisemann, Pearson Sound, and Martyn, as well as fresh talent from the UK (Arkist, Orphan101, KidKut,&#160;Greena and Brackles). His sporadic but legendary sets for Rinse FM have been compared to the great John Peel thanks to their off-the-wall diversity, and he remains one of the contemporary scene&#8217;s least predictable and most most exciting DJs.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Appleblim" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/appleblim" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/appleblim" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Appleblim" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MTA-iGrKYwc" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341612000" id="willsaul" startTime="1341608400" title="Will Saul"><itemDescription>Will Saul

[UK / DJ]

A true gentleman of British electronic music, Will Saul is a tireless supporter of quality music in a wide range of forms. From early beginnings winning Muzik magazine&#8217;s Bedroom Bedlam competition, Will&#8217;s initial love of lush, jazzy grooves, leftfield oddities, dubby breaks and broken beats soon blossomed into an appreciation of deep house and techno, following a stint in London record store Phonica. His emerging label Simple reflected this development, quickly becoming one of underground club music&#8217;s go-to imprints, and was soon augmented by quirky sister label Aus, which he co-owns with Ninja tunes artist Fink. An occasional but acclaimed producer, often in tandem with Tam Cooper, Will&#8217;s own music aptly reflects his tastes as a DJ and label head, combining house, techno and future-bass vibes with a heap of electronic soul.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Will+Saul" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Will_Saul" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/willsaul" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/willsaul" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Will+Saul" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U157cJ3GHTg" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341615600" id="mosca" startTime="1341612000" title="Mosca"><itemDescription>Mosca

[UK / DJ]

Widely regarded as one of the bass/whatever scene&#8217;s fiercest talents, Mosca came to prominence in 2010 with his genre-busting &#8216;Square One&#8217;, the very first release on wayward bass label Night Slugs. A steady flow of remixes and production followed, notably his thumping rework of Four Tet, his contribution to the Fabric Elevator Music comp, and especially his homage to Niche, &#8216;Done Me Wrong&#8217;, a beast of tune that was championed by Jackmaster among many others. Dipping in and out of tempos and styles with an attention-span defecit that borders on the right side of obnoxiousness, expect a tornado-like swirl through juke, jungle, hip-hop, dancehall, grime, techno and bassline.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Mosca" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/deejaymosca" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/deejaymosca" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Mosca+(2)" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n4rilZACTBI" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341619200" id="joker" startTime="1341615600" title="Joker"><itemDescription>Joker

[UK / DJ]

Joker burst onto the dubstep and grime scenes in 2008 with the vibrant &#8216;Grimey Princess&#8217; and &#8216;Gully Brook Lane&#8217;, released on Earwax and Plastician&#8217;s Terrorhythm imprint respectively. Both possessed a rare blend of intense rawness and nonchalant energy, the soundtrack to a self-styled pimp on an interstellar journey.

Born to grime and adopted by dubstep, Joker is reluctant to be classified, but his productions have been described as Jehri Curl Boogie and Wiley stuck in an elevator with Cameo. Named &#8220;2009 king of bass music&#8221; by XLR8R Magazine, his instantly recognisable sound played a key part in the ascent of London-based label Hyperdub, before signing to 4AD for his long awaited debut album, The Vision.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Joker" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/thejokerproductions" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Joker" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RadZTuZEKlM" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341622800" id="steffi" startTime="1341619200" title="Steffi"><itemDescription>Steffi

[DE / DJ]

Panoramabar&#8217;s doyenne of real house music Steffi is a club DJ in the classic sense; no soft blends or timid transitions for her, as she tweaks, chops and cuts her way through some of the best dance music you&#8217;re likely to ever hear, often for marathon stretches lasting well into Monday morning. A renowned producer also, her work for the Berghain/P-Bar in house label Ostgut-Ton makes clear her undying love for the timeless sounds of Chicago, Detroit and New York, all bound up with a distinctly contemporary sensibility. By turns sensual, jacking, and irresistibly danceable, Steffi&#8217;s take on house music is most definitely in a league of its own, earning her a devoted following and heaps of critical acclaim along the way.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Steffi" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/steffiklakson" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Steffi+(8)" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Steffi" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9hCJrvfBdw0" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341626400" id="artdepartment" startTime="1341622800" title="Art Department"><itemDescription>Art Department

Responsible for some of the most exciting house music to have come out of Canada in recent times, Kenny Glasgow and Jonny White combine a couple of decades of frontline DJing experience with a fresh and funk-heavy twist that&#8217;s made them the toast of the global club underground. The pair joined forces in the studio until only as recently as 2009, when Damian Lazarus called on them to remix Riz MC for his prestigious Crosstown Rebels Label. The result was a futuristic and raw, synth-driven, underground masterpiece, followed by a string of unforgettable shows, notably at Crosstown&#8217;s 2010 legendary Get Lost Miami showcase. A bona fide hit in the form of &#8216;Without You&#8217; followed, along with one of 2011&#8217;s best house albums, &#8216;The Drawing Board&#8217;. Live, the duo&#8217;s blend of lean robo-funk and evergreen house goodness makes them a serious force to be reckoned with.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Art+Department" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/theartdepartmentbaltimore" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Art+Department" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rrtqXg8dAMA" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341633600" id="jamiejones" startTime="1341626400" title="Jamie Jones"><itemDescription>Jamie Jones

[UK / DJ]

Few in house and techno have seen a rise to prominence in the last few years like Jamie Jones, key player in the Crosstown Rebels / Hot Natured family and deserved winner of Resident Advisor&#8217;s 2011 DJ poll. First coming to wider attention with the release of his underground hit &#8216;Amazon&#8217;, he&#8217;s since continued to work and refine his darkly funky brand of electronic club music over the intervening years, holding down a relentless touring schedule that&#8217;s seen him destroy clubs and festivals the world weekend in, weekend out. Studio-wise, his sound touches on most of the styles that make his sets so popular, taking in dark robotic funk, strutting neo-disco and no small amount of razor-sharp swing, pitched between house music&#8217;s past, present and future with effortless skill.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jamie+Jones" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jamiejonesdj" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/jamie-jones" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Jamie+Jones+(2)" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Go14fQGV8Zw" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341673200" id="geddes" startTime="1341633600" title="Geddes"><itemDescription>Geddes

[UK / DJ]

One of the most influential players in the London house scene of the last decade, Stuart Geddes was ahead of the game at the dawn of a new warehouse era in the early 2000s. His Mulletover party crew were integral in the rise of the underground in the capital and beyond, displaying an enduring policy of championing the freshest talent around in the city&#8217;s most interesting unused spaces. Since then, Geddes has turned his attention to a number of creative projects, including the launch of his own label, Murmur, and offshoot party venture nofitstate. In the three years since Murmur was born, the imprint has become synonymous with the kind of homegrown talent that embodies the underground events Geddes curates, while his own production under the Rekleiner guise (alongside Anthony Middleton and Luca Saporito) has amply demonstrated his love of clean, deep beats and quality electronic production. With an ever-evolving ability to move with the times, not to mention the support and love from a tight community of
music fans and artists alike, the omnipresence of Geddes and his contribution to underground London looks set to continue for years to come.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Geddes" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/stuartgeddes" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/geddes" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Geddes" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WqIXbYN2GcM" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341676800" id="pariah" startTime="1341673200" title="Pariah"><itemDescription>Pariah

[UK / DJ]

London dubstep/future garage producer Arthur Cayzer&#8217;s astonishing singles &#8216;Detroit Fall&#8217; and &#8216;Safehouses&#8217; on R&amp;S established him as a leading light in the emerging British scene, fusing fierce electrronics with intricate programming and leftfield, hyperactive soulfulness. His remixes The xx , Erykah Badu and Brandy are pretty much the definition of &#8216;transformative&#8217;, winning him the patronage of Radio 1&#8217;s Mary Anne Hobbes and rave reviews from influential sites Pitchfork and Resident Advisor. His gigs, meanwhile, are every bit as unpredicatable and energetic as you&#8217;d expect, spinning through dance music&#8217;s myriad subcultures in the space of a few seconds.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Pariah" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/pariah-r" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Pariah" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mD2Mj5cma8E" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341680400" id="untold" startTime="1341676800" title="Untold"><itemDescription>Untold

[UK / DJ]

Jack Dunning&#8217;s weighty and bass-heavy production work as Untold has consistently ignited future-leaning dancefloors everywhere, from his earliest releases for Hessle Audio, to his wild remixes for acts like Radiohead and Homework, and of course a clutch of modern classics for R&amp;S. His own Hemlock label has housed likeminded electronica/dubstep crossover artists Mount Kimbie, Fantastic Mr Fox, CosminTRG, Ramadanman, LV and a certain producer called James Blake, while his restless flitting between disparate styles has made him one of the most characteristic talents of recent times. By turns raw and refined, heavy yet artfully composed, he&#8217;s one of the UK scene&#8217;s most distinctive musical &#160;visionaries.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Untold" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/untold/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Untold" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Untold" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MQLjhG9Ogwo" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341684000" id="jacquesgreene" startTime="1341680400" title="Jacques Greene"><itemDescription>Jacques Greene

[CA / Live]

A native of Montreal Canada, Jacques Greene&#8217;s killer release for LuckyMe, NightSlugs and vase are powered by straight-ahead beats, bright hooks and lightly shaded steppers shuffles. Owing less to the grime and bassline scenes than his contemporaries, his sound is an invitingly fresh take on bleeding-edge house mingled with a naked love for 80s R&amp;B, opting for unfussy straightness over puffed up melodrama. Hits like &#8216;The Look&#8217;, and &#8216;(Baby I Don&#8217;t Know) What You Want&#8217; are among the most hotly hyped singles of the last few years, while his contribution to Radiohead&#8217;s TKOL remix package was a highlight of the release, confirming his reputation as one of the post-everything scene&#8217;s most exciting artists.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jacques+Greene" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jacquesgreene" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/jacquesgreene/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Jacques+Greene" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=79J58LlPiAg" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341687600" id="spacedimensioncontroller" startTime="1341684000" title="Space Dimension Controller"><itemDescription>Space Dimension Controller

[UK / DJ]

Irish techno-disco-electrofunk wizard Jack Hamill arrived with a bang in 2009 with a pair of EPs for R&amp;S that instantly marked him out as one of the most exciting producers around. Spinning a questionable but intoxicating yarn in interviews that revolves around having been sent to earth from the 24th century, SDC&#8217;s space-age superfreak jams have won him consistent acclaim from across the electronic music spectrum. Meanwhile, high profile remixes for Detroit demigods like Antony &#8216;Shake&#8217; Shakir and Juan Atkins pretty much set his stall as the natural successor to the well worn &#8216;Kraftwerk in an elevator with George Clinton&#8217; adage.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Space+Dimension+Controller" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/spacedimensioncontroller" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/spacedimensioncontroller/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Space+Dimension+Controller" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e6Vq9E-p3xM" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341691200" id="jamesblake" startTime="1341687600" title="James Blake"><itemDescription>James Blake (born October 1988) is an electronic musician and singer-songwriter from London, England, United Kingdom. Blake is primarily considered a dubstep producer and is frequently heralded as a leading figure in the &#8220;post-dubstep&#8221; community, but he is also noted for his prominent soul influences. Blake was nominated the Critic&#8217;s Choice award by the 2011 BRIT Awards and the Sound of 2011 award by the BBC, and won second place in the latter. In addition, his self-titled debut LP, James Blake, was nominated for the 2011 Mercury Prize. Blake has also released material under the alias Harmonimix.

James Blake began his final year at Goldsmiths in September 2009 studying popular music while recording songs in his bedroom. In July 2009, he attended the Latymer School and released his debut single &#8220;Air and Lack Thereof&#8221; on Hemlock Audio. It was a firm favorite with Gilles Peterson from BBC Radio 1, and Blake was invited to do a special mix on Peterson&#8217;s worldwide show, which included an exclusive Mount Kimbie track.

Blake released his debut EP The Bells Sketch on 8 March 2010 on Hessle Audio, followed soon after by CMYK on 31 May 2010 and Klavierwerke on 10 October 2010, both on R&amp;S Records. All three EPs were met with significant critical acclaim: BBC&#8217;s Nick Grimshaw chose CMYK as his Record of the Week, the title track of CMYK was ranked 24th on Frontier Psychiatrist&#8217;s top 40 songs of the year, and all three of Blake&#8217;s 2010 EPs were collectively ranked 8th on Pitchfork&#8217;s top 50 albums of 2010.

Tags: dubstep, electronic, experimental, downtempo, soul</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/James+Blake" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_Blake_(musician)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jamesblakeproduction" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=James+Blake" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341693900" id="lukehandsfree" startTime="1341691200" title="Luke Handsfree"><itemDescription>Luke Handsfree

Luke Handsfree, co-founder of Plex and long time fixture of the London electronic scene is know for his open-minded selection in his DJ sets. Adept at playing Techno, Jungle, Dubstep, House, and everything in between, his sets criss-cross genre and tempo; all the while with an ear attuned to the rave. Inspired to start mixing by hearing Coldcut&#8217;s Solid Steel shows on Kiss FM after accruing a well-stocked larder of Jungle from Section 5 and Techno from Hard Wax, he cut his teeth in London&#8217;s late 90s fertile music scene before joining up with James Tec to form Plex in 2006. Expect some heavily mixed up Techno/Bass/What-You-Call-It from Luke at Bloc!

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Luke+Handsfree" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/lukehandsfree" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/lukehandsfree/luke-handsfree-patience" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Luke+Handsfree" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341696600" id="jamestec" startTime="1341693900" title="James Tec"><itemDescription>James Tec

James Tec has been a stalwart of the London techno/electronic scene for nigh on 17 years now. Usually hitting the harder end of the techno spectrum with heavily layered, sonically driven unrelenting sets that aim to showcase the very best of what the genre has to offer.

After brief spells running free parties in the wilds of north London in the late 90&#8242;s James set-up Plex with his likeminded cohort Luke Handsfree in 2006 as a platform to showcase not only already established artists, but also the many friends of Plex who produce and DJ. A long time ally and friend of Bloc James has now appeared at every Bloc festival thus far and also helped set-up Brackout a record label and Bloc Weekend Thursday warm-up tribute night to honour our late great friend Ben Bracket; a former resident of Plex and Bloc regular.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/james_tec" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/j-tec" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=James+Tec" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341700200" id="truss" startTime="1341696600" title="Truss"><itemDescription>Truss

[UK / Live]

Tom Russell has been many of the techno scene&#8217;s major players in the last few years, both solo and as one half of Donor/Truss. Forging a sound that falls loosely under the &#8216;pure techno&#8217; banner, but thankfully eschewing the tedium so often associated with that term, his productions are taut, rich, and gimmick-free, leading to a steady flow of killer releases on acclaimed labels including Thema, Synewave and, of course, Perc Trax. An accomplished DJ to boot, expect the very finest in up-to-the minute dark hour techno supplemented by a healthy dose of wayward bass-heavy experiments.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/truss" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Truss" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UENRCRX6Ams" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341703800" id="lucy" startTime="1341700200" title="Lucy"><itemDescription>Lucy

[IT / Live]

One of the foremost players in the new wave of Italian techno artists, Lucy and his label Stroboscopic Artefacts have developed a firm following in recent years. Coming from an IDM background, Lucy&#8217;s own production work &#160;is carefully crafted and admirably uncompromising, layering ambient and IDM textures over hypnotic four-four rhythms. It&#8217;s an approach that reached its culmination in the form of his 2011 debut LP Wordplay For Working Bees, a diverse yet coherent excursion that took in beatless tonal experiments, unsettling minimalism, and widescreen, main room pushers. Similarly, his DJ sets are characterised by their ability to swell from gentle ambient beginnings to rich and resonant peak-hour pure techno. His magnificent Stroboscopic Artefacts label, meanwhile, has become a consistently reliable outpost for like-minded artists including Xhin, Dadub, Go Hiyama and Perc.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Lucy" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/lucy" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Lucy" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jeweuqkyfxQ" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341707400" id="martyn" startTime="1341703800" title="Martyn"><itemDescription>Martyn

[UK / Live]

Along with 2562, Martyn is the most recognizable face of the Dutch post-dubstep scene. He first made an impression in 2005 with a couple of singles that garnered him immediate underground applause for the way he managed to integrate both techno and jungle/drum n bass techniques into the then-fledgling sounds of dubstep. Further singles and a relentless DJ schedule only added to his increasing profile, culminating with the release of his critically lauded debut album Great Lengths in 2009. This was followed in 2011 by Ghost People, a further refinement and development of his style and sound. One of the few producers who&#8217;s as adept as on stage as he is in the studio, his current live show showcases Martyn&#8217;s smart and sublime take on contemporary bass-heavy techno and futuristic house.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Martyn" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Martyn_(musician)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/martyndnb" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/3024world/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Martyn" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A7Ydvq6bSog" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341711000" id="cosmintrg" startTime="1341707400" title="Cosmin TRG"><itemDescription>Cosmin TRG

[RO / DJ]

With an ever changing sound that&#8217;s oscillated over the years between sophisticated post-dubstep and classically informed techno, Romanian-born Cosmin TRG&#8217;s restless imagination has won him much acclaim. &#160;Initially known as TRG, his early outings were characterised by a loaded two-step bump, albeit one placed at a fair distance from the raw and ready vibes more commonly associated with the style. Elegant yet unrestrained, his work began to investigate more intense and techno-inclined pastures, though he never lost his love for the syncopated thrum of bass music, fusing the two scenes with a distinctly European sense of artistry. Unified by an enveloping analogue warmth, his releases for Hessle Audio, Rush Hour and Modeselektor&#8217;s 50 Weapons are as exhilarating as they are varied, layering up a patchwork of contemporary and traditional electronic music influences. His debut album Simulat was one of the most confident and fully-realised long-layers of 2011, and his roof-raising live shows have made him an
enduring fixture on the international techno festival circuit.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Cosmin+TRG" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/trg/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Cosmin+TRG" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oJLFglK7qDk" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341714600" id="objekt" startTime="1341711000" title="Objekt"><itemDescription>Objekt

[DE / DJ]

He may not have released much so far, but few can lay claim to the buzz generated by Objekt in the last twelve months. Nominally techno but clearly influenced by industrial, breakbeat and dubstep, his tracks combine lean and hard-edged rhythms, inventive samples, and ominous half-step echoes, leading many to believe he was an alias for an experienced techno veteran. Not true: he&#8217;s just a staggeringly talented, admirably non-prolific producer of some of the finest dark-hour club music of recent times. With remixes for Call Super, Sbtrkt and Radiohead to his name, as well as &#8216;Cactus&#8217;, a deadly dubplate that proved a highlight of Ben UFO&#8217;s recent mix CD for Rinse, he&#8217;s a talent whose star is most definitely in the ascendant.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Objekt" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/keinobjekt" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Objekt" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Objekt" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iH7eKyRSxok" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341718200" id="perc" startTime="1341714600" title="Perc"><itemDescription>Perc

[UK / Live]

Perc has been bubbling under on the techno scene for the best part of a decade, but it&#8217;s in the last two years that his powerful, lean, intense sound has really blown up. Early releases on labels like Ovum, Drumcode and his own Perc Trax saw him investigating varying moods and atmospheres, before he honed in on his distinctive industrially-tinged sound. Bridging the gap between the evergreen thump of classic minimal techno and more contemporary abstract sound design, Perc&#8217;s DJ sets &#8211; like his music &#8211; &#160;are heavy without becoming over-aggressive, and intelligent without losing itself in indulgent chin-strokery. Meanwhile, &#160;his 2011 debut album &#8216;Wicker &amp; Steel&#8217; confirmed Perc as one of the most exciting and consistent artists of recent times.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Perc" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/perctrax" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/perc/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Perc" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rJdFz2KK2rU" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341723600" id="surgeon" startTime="1341718200" title="Surgeon"><itemDescription>Surgeon

[UK / DJ]

Perhaps the most universally respected of all UK techno DJs, Surgeon has been pushing the style forward for over two decades. His own intense productions and remixes have regularly re-defined the parameters of electronic music, merging abstract sound-design with complex yet highly physical rhythms, while his industrially-inclined work with Regis as British Murder Boys still stand as one of techno&#8217;s finest and most revered unions. His wide-ranging DJ sets are equally lauded, threading together classic and obscure techno, fearsome ragga, wayward man-machine experiments and industrial blasts of Whitehouse with the all the immaculate skill and precision that his moniker implies. An ambassador for next-level electronic music and a confirmed Bloc hero, his return as part of the Plex showcase is a guaranteed masterclass in techno&#8217;s past, present and future.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Surgeon" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Surgeon_(musician)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Surgeon" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Surgeon" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0rFWda83F8w" type="youtube" /></item></line><line id="stubnitzatrium" title="Stubnitz Atrium"><item endTime="1341594900" id="deadboy" startTime="1341590400" title="Deadboy"><itemDescription>Deadboy

[UK / DJ]

Based in South London, Deadboy has been producing garage influenced tracks for many years, incorporating elements of house, RnB, dancehall, funky, grime, bassline and beyond. His debut &#160;EP &#8216;Cheated&#8217; appeared on Well Rounded records at the end of 2009 and was caned by the likes of Jackmaster, Oneman, Bok Bok and Joy Orbison, with Boomkat placing it at #26 on their end of year chart. His follow-up, &#8216;If You Want Me&#8217;, was a hit for Numbers and led to bookings at Fabric and Plastic People, plays on Radio 1, and a killer mix for FACT. Expect classic and fresh garage, funky, house, bassline, and anything else Deadboy feels like throwing down.

Featuring on the Numbers vs Swamp81 label showcase.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Deadboy" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Deadboy_%26_the_Elephantmen" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/deadboysoundboy" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/deadboy" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Deadboy" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_LAni2nszsw" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341599400" id="pinch" startTime="1341594900" title="Pinch"><itemDescription>Pinch

[UK / DJ]

Bristol&#8217;s Rob Ellis, better known as Pinch, is a latter day hero of the city&#8217;s renowned dubstep scene, noted for his distinctive fusion of styles such as Reggae, World Music, and Dancehall with dubstep. He released his first album, Underwater Dancehall in 2007 on Tectonic records to universal acclaim, before dropping the harmonium sampling anthem &#8216;Qawwali&#8217; on Planet Mu records. A restless studio obsessive and keen collaborator, he most recently hooked up with Shackleton to record a joint LP for Honest Jon&#8217;s which combined the pair&#8217;s distinctive, multi-layered styles to stunning effect.

Featuring on the Numbers vs Swamp81 label showcase.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Pinch" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pinch_(dubstep_musician)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/tectonicrecordings" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/dj-pinch" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Pinch+(2)" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eRbEA-ap21I" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341602100" id="redinho" startTime="1341599400" title="Redinho"><itemDescription>Redinho

[UK / DJ]

Redhino, one of Numbers numerous multi-talented stars, is the nom de plume of London based producer Tom Calvert. After three EPS, he&#8217;s managed to sneak into the public consciousness, with his debut (&#8217;Bare Blips&#8217; EP) instantly selling out. His pummeling stage performances contain both the hard-edged electronic material featured on the Bare Blips release alongside his newer Talklbox electro-funk work; think Roger Troutman produced by the Neptunes with the subs cranked up, UK-style. A rising talent of British club music that&#8217;s definitely worth keeping an eye on.

Featuring on the Numbers vs Swamp81 label showcase.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Redinho" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/nmbrs/redinho-bare-blips-ep-sampler" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Redinho" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oV1oJOB1nqE" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341606600" id="spencer" startTime="1341602100" title="Spencer"><itemDescription>Spencer

One of the co-founders of Glasgow&#8217;s Numbers, Spencer started young. In his teenage years, he embarked upon what is now almost a decade of party planning and record releasing, and is a major factor in the astonishing rise of the label/party collective. From early beginnings in working in Glasgow&#8217;s world-renowned record store Rubadub, honing his DJing skills with schoolfriend Jackmaster, and co-hosting Detroit techno legend Claude Young&#8217;s radio shows, to working at Warp Records and now living in London; Spencer has been a key player in aiding the city&#8217;s recent rise to fame as an essential exporter of electronic music. &#160;Whether it&#8217;s co-running the events and label for Numbers, or delivering killer mixes on and off the dancefloor, he has a musical knowledge and surefire selection that makes volume level 11 seem unsatisfactory.

Featuring on the Numbers vs Swamp81 label showcase.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Spencer" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Spencer" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341611100" id="oneman" startTime="1341606600" title="Oneman"><itemDescription>Oneman

[UK / DJ]

Oneman was introduced to the wider world when Swamp81 boss Loefah put him forward for Mary Anne Hobbes&#8217; generation bass showcase, where his remarkable mixing talents instantly set the scene alight. Known for spinning old tracks alongside killer exclusives &#8211; a rarity in a scene usually obsessed with the newest tunes only &#8211; &#160;he&#8217;s been compared to dubplate pioneers like Slimzee, Hatcha and DMZ, while his own 502 imprint has quickly become a must-check label for UK bass aficionados.

Featuring on the Numbers vs Swamp81 label showcase.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/1mandj" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Oneman" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8hupqptaF0E" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341616500" id="loefah" startTime="1341611100" title="Loefah"><itemDescription>Loefah

[UK / DJ]

A true pioneer, Loefah has been at the forefront of the UK underground for almost 10 years now, founding the infamous DMZ with Mala &amp; Coki, and acting as a global ambassador for the dubstep movement. Early anthems like &#8216;Horror Show&#8217;, &#8216;Mud&#8217; and &#8216;Ruffage&#8217; gained him a reputation for seriously hefty bass weight underpinned by a half-step swing, while the creation of his Swamp 81 imprint witnessed a marked expansion of the genre&#8217;s boundaries, with releases on the label gaining support from DJs as diverse as A-Trak, Ricardo Villalobos, Gilles Peterson and Kode9. The Swamp81 roster reads like a bass lover&#8217;s dream team, featuring such heavies as Kryptic Minds, Skream, Ramadanman and Faulty DL alongside the luminaries presented at the exclusive Bloc showcase; proof, if any were needed, of Loefah&#8217;s famous ability to spot and the sign the cream of the scene&#8217;s talent.

Featuring on the Numbers vs Swamp81 label showcase.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Loefah" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/loefah" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/loefah" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Loefah" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7NKY31AaB-g" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341621000" id="boddika" startTime="1341616500" title="Boddika"><itemDescription>Boddika

[UK / DJ]

Influenced by the expansive sounds of Luke Vibert, the analogue programming of Juan Atkins early work, and the rawness of the Drexciya/Dopplereffekt family, Boddika is the newest project of Al Green, half of the boundary-pushing breakbeat outfit Instra:mental.

Characterised by layers of full, analogue sounds, juke-fuelled vocal chants, innovative drum patterns that morph and develop with each bar, and deep, mechanic stabs, there&#8217;s hardly any trace of the bass genres Green may be known for, but yet it doesn&#8217;t quite fit comfortably in any defined 4/4 box either. In short: it sounds like absolutely nothing else.
With DJs across the board &#8211; including Skream, Loefah, Oneman, Stingray, Martyn, Ramadanman, Joy Orbison, Scuba, Shy FX, Benji B, Addison Groove and Zed Bias &#8211; caning his tracks, it&#8217;s clear that Boddika looks set to continue pushing at the edges of bass music innovation.

Featuring on the Numbers vs Swamp81 label showcase.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Boddika" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/instramentaluk/blog/537835220" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/boddika/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Boddika" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZFbcCZDHRuM" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341630000" id="jackmasterb2bjoyorbison" startTime="1341621000" title="Jackmaster b2b Joy Orbison"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Jackmaster+b2b+Joy+Orbison" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341633600" id="hudsonmohawke" startTime="1341630000" title="Hudson Mohawke"><itemDescription>Hudson Mohawke, (b. Ross Birchard), also known as DJ Itchy, Hudson Mo or Hud Mo, is an electronic music producer/DJ from Glasgow, Scotland, affiliated with the LuckyMe collective of musicians and artists. He is signed to Warp Records and released his debut album Butter in October 2009.

At the age of 15 Birchard, under the name DJ Itchy, was the youngest ever UK DMC finalist. His earliest gigs as a club DJ were with Glasgow Uni&#8217;s Subcity Radio where he was part of the culture city kids show and later other shows including Turntable Science with Pro Vinylist Karim and Cloudo&#8217;s Happy Hardcore show. Birchard became Hudson Mohawke after seeing the name engraved on a statue in the hallway of his accommodation. He was signed to Warp Records despite a very limited track record of official releases; the bulk of his releases were unofficial tracks and DJ mixes circulated on the Internet. His first official release to get major notice was &#8220;Free Mo&#8221;, a track on the Ubiquity Records various-artists compilation Choices, Vol. 1 (2007); subsequently, he was featured as a remixer on Choices, Vol. 2 (2007). In 2008 his 12&#8221; EP Ooops! on LuckyMe/Wireblock became an underground sensation, particularly once word spread of his recording contract with Warp.

Tags: experimental, electronic, hip-hop, instrumental hip-hop, instrumental</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Hudson+Mohawke" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hudson_Mohawke" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/hudsonmo" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/hudsonmohawke/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Hudson+Mohawke" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1341673200" id="addisongroove" startTime="1341633600" title="Addison Groove"><itemDescription>Addison Groove

[UK / DJ]

The juke and ghetto alias of dubstep mainstay Headhunter, Addison Groove is best known for his 2010 anthem &#8216;Footcrab&#8217;, arguably the strongest UK realisation of the Midwest sound to date, followed in 2011 by &#8216;Work It / Sexual&#8217;, a hymn to the sleaze and energy of Detroit&#8217;s fiercest strip-club electro. &#160;Taking in hip-hop, booty, squealing acid and crunchingly raw rhythms, his DJ sets are a high-octane, no-holds-barred surge through the roughest outposts of stripped down club music.

Featuring on the Numbers vs Swamp81 label showcase.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Addison+Groove" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Addison_Groove_Project" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/addisongroove" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Addison+Groove" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QvOC6B6eazo" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341676800" id="rebelintelligence" startTime="1341673200" title="Rebel Intelligence"><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/rebel-intelligence" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/label/Rebel%20Intelligence" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Rebel+Intelligence" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341680400" id="edchamberlain" startTime="1341676800" title="Ed Chamberlain"><itemDescription>Electro wunderkind and resident of the Baselogic crew responsible for the infamous Bloc Weekend, Ed Chamberlain took influences from colleagues Tipper, Keith Tenniswood and Synapse and knuckled down to music production.

Within a handful of highly essential releases, he&#8217;s managed to establish a sound cherished by electronic music cognoscenti: a solid yet intricate framework of electro, filled with touches of wistful melody that give it a timelessness and sets it apart from the rest.

Tight, filtered glitch edits balance out a relentless, driving rave energy reminiscent of Radioactive Man&#8217;s chunky electro workouts.

Releases:

Medicine Gun EP 12&#8221; Vinyl
Haiku Remixes 12&#8221; Vinyl
Fixxy 1 12&#8221; Vinyl
Fixxy 2 12&#8221; Vinyl
Fixxy 3 12&#8221; Vinyl

Tags: electro, electronic, electronica, braindance, acid</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Ed+Chamberlain" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/edchamberlain" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/ed-chamberlain" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Ed+Chamberlain" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1341684000" id="bleepdjs" startTime="1341680400" title="Bleep DJs"><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/bleepdjs" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/djwhatthebleep" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Bleep+DJs" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341687600" id="iliumsphere" startTime="1341684000" title="Ilium Sphere"><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/theillumsphere" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/illum-sphere/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Illum+Sphere" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Ilium+Sphere" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341693000" id="arpanet" startTime="1341687600" title="Arpanet"><itemDescription>Arpanet

Among the most revered projects of Drexciyan overlord Heinrich Mueller, Arpanet&#8217;s cerebral excursions into electro&#8217;s outerspace realms are pretty much incomparable. Until this year, he and cohort To Nhan Le Thi have only appeared live on stage as Arpanet once before, their legacy kept alive by their peerless series of releases (mainly on Rephlex) and a typically head-spinning conceptual legend that&#8217;s the stuff electro dreams are made of. Combining their own visuals, exclusive material and who knows what else, this is a UK festival exclusive, and a very special coup for Bloc indeed.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Arpanet" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/dataphysix" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Arpanet" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yqP21JgRbgo" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341698400" id="scionfeattikiman" startTime="1341693000" title="Scion feat. Tikiman"><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/mariaamostbahnhof/photos/27658191" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Scion+feat.+Tikiman" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341702000" id="ikonika" startTime="1341698400" title="Ikonika"><itemDescription>Ikonika

[UK / DJ]

Although she allegedly hates the &#8216;first lady of dubstep&#8217; tag, it&#8217;s impossible to ignore the impact Ikonika has had on the once notoriously macho bass scene, both as a producer of &#160;game-changing, abyssal music and as a fiercely uncompromising DJ. A combined love of Madonna, garage and video games soundtracked her childhood and inevitably fed into her later musical output, winning praise from pirate radio DJs and Guardian writers alike. Her sets, meanwhile, are an apocalyptic swirl of bass-rave power, incorporating underground classics, abstract oddities, and peerless future bass anthems.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Ikonika" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ikonika" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/ikonika/music" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/ikonika" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Ikonika" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mvpgiiotL0U" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341707400" id="hypewilliams" startTime="1341702000" title="Hype Williams"><itemDescription>Hype Williams

On record, Hype Williams make music laced with their signature hazy glow and full of crunched eurovision lullabies, kinetic drum machine jams, unsettling funk, smeared walls of synth, and moments of unadulterated opiated bliss.

After 3 albums across as many labels, and last years &#8216;Kelly Price W8 Gain EP Vol II &#8216; as Hype Williams, the core duo of the group, Dean Blunt and Inga Copeland, release their debut Hyperdub LP, &#8216;Black is Beautiful&#8217; in April this year.

Rumours about the band circulate but it&#8217;s been confirmed by their &#8216;advisor&#8217; Denna Frances, that this latest album was recorded during a tremulous period for the two: Inga Copeland&#8217;s Arsenalgirls tryouts, Dean&#8217;s &#8216;Waschb&#228;rgate&#8217; trial (he was implicated in being behind a one night robbing spree across 16 taxidermists based in London and the South East, allegedly only for raccoons) and his subsequent conversion to Nation of Islam upon being acquitted.

Live, the band offer a completely different and intense side to their music with each performance being different to the last, so expect to see nothing like it again.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Hype+Williams" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/hypheewilliams" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Hype+Williams+(2)" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Hype+Williams" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UEtIhfJdSMo" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341711000" id="coolyg" startTime="1341707400" title="Cooly G"><itemDescription>Cooly G

[UK / DJ]

Cooly G is a semi-pro footballer, a mum, and a behaviour consultant for young people &#8211; but we&#8217;re most interested in her immaculate fusion of dubstep and house. She&#8217;s the second female producer on Hyperdub alongside Ikonika, and she released her debut single for the label, &#8216;Love Dub&#8217;, after a string of self released CDs caught the attention of Kode9. her first official release caused people to become pretty excited; she was single of the week in the Guardian, One to Watch in the Independent, interviewed all over and was immediately snapped up for remixes by the majors, as well as starting to attract bookings all over the world. Deep, tribal, abstract and funky, she&#8217;s a distinctive and glittering jewel in the Hyperdub crown.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Cooly+G" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/coolyg" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Cooly+G" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Cooly+G" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Md3jK1gOvSg" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341714600" id="scratchadva" startTime="1341711000" title="Scratcha DVA"><itemDescription>Scratcha DVA

[UK / DJ]

Also known as Scratcha DVA, or just DVA for his more recent productions, Scratcha has long been a fixture on the UK scene thanks to his hugely entertaining breakfast show on Rinse FM. When plucked by Hyperdub for his release &#8216;Natty&#8217;, Scratcha was introduced to a new audience as a funky producer, but his production CV extends back further to grime, where he&#8217;s worked with luminaries including Wiley. He&#8217;s not one to rest on the sounds of years gone by, though, packing his bag with up front, left-of-centre killers instead of relying on tried and tired hits. His forthcoming album, &#8216;Pretty Ugly&#8217;, sees him leaping into new realms, working pop-tinged R&amp;B, off kilter rhythms, and vibrant synth brightness around vocal contributions from Cornelia, A.L., Muhsinah, Natalie Maddix and Zaki Ibrahim. Expect a high-octane romp through the UK rave underground.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Scratcha+DVA" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/scratchadva" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/scratchadva" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/DVA+(2)" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xink0y0Nx6M" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341718200" id="terrordanjah" startTime="1341714600" title="Terror Danjah"><itemDescription>Terror Danjah

[UK / DJ]

Considered by many grime cognoscenti to be the foremost grime producer of all time, Terror Danjah&#8217;s productions are full of strikingly original ideas, complex rhythms and pop hooks. Originally part of the Nasty Crew and then Aftershock, Terror has released countless 12&#8243;s and remixes as well as several scene-defining mixtapes. He&#8217;s frequently been compared to Timbaland, with both utilising a signature palate of sounds, shifting, syncopated rhythms, and an utterly distinctive audio logo (in Terror&#8217;s case, the &#8216; the Gremlin cackle&#8217;). Closer to home, he&#8217;s also been singled out as the precursor to the Bristol sound &#8211; Joker, in particular &#8211; and his cuts work as well in conjunction with the UK&#8217;s premier MCs as they do on their own, as proved on &#8216;Gremlin&#8217;, his collection of instrumentals for Plant &#160;Mu. An epochal talent in British music over the last ten years, he&#8217;s the connoisseur&#8217;s choice and a proper godfather of grime.

Terror Danjah will perform with Riko Dan, and give an exclusive preview of his new album &#8216;Dark Crawler&#8216;.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Terror+Danjah" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/terrordanjah" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/terrordanjah" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Terror+Danjah" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_YrIHigmhjY" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341723600" id="kode9" startTime="1341718200" title="Kode 9"><itemDescription>Kode9

[UK / DJ]

Head Hyperdub honcho and renowned DJ/producer in his own right, Glasgow native Kode9 is a junglist at heart, albeit one with remarkably ecelctic tastes. He started DJing in 1990 at the age of 16, playing a fusion of reggae, breaks, hip hop, jazz, funk and house, before being swept up by the emergence of the breakbeat hardcore, jungle and drum&#8217;n&#8217;bass scenes, which have come to form the basis of his ever-widening sonic explorations. Initially forming Hyperdub as a simple blog, then an outlet for his own productions, he&#8217;s overseen the development of the label into the creative powerhouse it is today, guiding the careers of some of modern electronic music&#8217;s brightest talents along the way. As you&#8217;d expect, his sets are second to none, bursting with exclusives, anthems, and a few unusual touches that might take you by surprise.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Kode+9" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kode9" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/kode9" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Kode9" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WaU-pnassYM" type="youtube" /></item></line><line id="laderaum" title="Laderaum"><item endTime="1341594000" id="controlledweirdness" startTime="1341586800" title="Controlled Weirdness"><itemDescription>South London Bass ambassador Neil Keating aka DJ Controlled Weirdness has been rocking the decks and rinsing the rough beats for a few years now. As a young kid the Streetsounds Electro series and early eighties pirate radio stations like LWR started his obsession with nasty electronic music, breakbeats and hard edged funk. Saturday afternoons were spent in Groove records in Soho buying obscure Electro Imports that now go for high sums on Ebay and attending Spats in Oxford street, a Saturday afternoon club where Tim Westwood would play all the new electro/hip hop coming out of the States. This was the start of a lifelong vinyl obsession that still continues to this day. January 1984 and after hearing about Neil&#8217;s eclectic record collection he was asked to DJ at a new club called &#8220;The House of Dolls&#8221; in Farringdon. There he became resident DJ and spun a mixture of electro, industrial, punk and new wave and even some Northern Soul, the start of the DJ bug. At the same time he was also going out to clubs like
Delirium, The Mud Clud and Pyramid at Heaven (allegedly the first place to play house music in England in 1985) and also the very first warehouse parties hosted by people like Family Function(Norman Jays sound System) and Soul II Soul. These parties were held in the old abandoned warehouses down by the Thames from London Bridge up to Blackfriars bridge. Saturday night routine was to meet in the Spice of Life pub in Soho where you got the location of the party and then travel down to the then run down areas near the river where you paid &#163;5 to get in and could dance all night to Funk and Rare Groove.

Tags: electro, drum and bass, dubstep, breakbeat, 2-step</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Controlled+Weirdness" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/controlledweirdness" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/dj-controlled-weirdness/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/DJ+Controlled+Weirdness" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1341597600" id="thedexorcist" startTime="1341594000" title="The Dexorcist"><itemDescription>1982 - Linoleum, spraycans and the &#8220;Return of Captain Rock&#8221; illegally transmitting from a battered ghetto blaster, evil underground influences causing a lifelong addiction to vinyl junkie Simon Brown aka The Dexorcist.
By 89 the sound of Browns brand of audio weaponry could be heard deep beneath the ground, educating those that dare dance in art of acid music.

Within no time at all our devious DJ could be found, hidden inside bass bins of darkened clubs, hatching and plotting with new found conspirators known as the Fear Teachers. Embarking on an outdoor adventure armed with records, speakers, turntables and a generator these reckless rave rebels roamed the great British countryside infecting many innocent souls with the spine chilling sounds of acid house, techno, and electro from deep within a forest under a strobe lit moon.
As time grew older many former Fear founders fell foul to the evils of mortgage and marriage yet the devoted Dexorcist remained true to the cause, speaker surfing, sleep deprivation, vodka and vinyl, burning any bass bins that dare stand in his way.
Our twisted electro engineer soon reformed and regrouped to regenerate a new force in urban audio technology. Firing on all cylinders, the Kore Dispension Unit wreaked havoc through the warehouse wastelands and forbidden fields of London and Europe, broadcasting industrial dance music leaving a trail of burnt out bass, frazzled frequencies and broken beats.

Tags: electro, nu electro, e-l-e-c-t-r-o, electro breaks, spotify</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/The+Dexorcist" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/dexorcist" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/dexorcist" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Dexorcist,+The" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1341615600" id="boilerroomsecretshowcase" startTime="1341597600" title="Boiler Room Secret Showcase"><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/rumpistol" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Boiler+Room+Secret+Showcase" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341619200" id="transparentsound" startTime="1341615600" title="Transparent Sound"><itemDescription>Transparent Sound

Key players in the quality electro scene since they formed in the delightful surroundings of Bognor back in 1994, Orson Bramley and Martin Brown are known for fusing robotic electro drums with sci-fi vibes, alien funk and razor sharp production. Hits like &#8216;Freaks Frequency&#8217; and &#8216;Down In Miami&#8217; are still rinsed by electro heads across the globe today, but they&#8217;ve consistently plugged away for nearly two decades, releasing a steady stream of projects in various alignments and guises over the years, including the acclaimed 2006 Craig Richards collaboration &#8216;Two Headed Monster&#8217;. Live, Transparent Sound really come into their own, throwing down fierce 808 beats layered with timeless tech-funk attitude.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Transparent+Sound" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/transparent_sound" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/transparent-sound" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Transparent+Sound" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5lGSK5MxFjw" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341622800" id="nathanfake" startTime="1341619200" title="Nathan Fake"><itemDescription>Nathan Fake

[UK / Live]

Nathan Fake is returning to Bloc once again. Nathan came to the attention of the wider world with his melodic techno for James Holden&#8217;s Border Community imprint around 2004, but since then his musical path has veered well beyond the dancefloor, with successive albums showcasing his distinctive knack for complex rhythms, crunching sound design and charmed melodies in all manner of unexpected ways. He&#8217;ll be blowing Stubnitz out of the water with his new live set. Get ready for his new album in late August.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Nathan+Fake" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nathan_Fake" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/nathancake" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/nthnfk/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Nathan+Fake" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d7zBePUZMog" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341673200" id="worldunknown" startTime="1341622800" title="World Unknown"><itemDescription>World Unknown

There are many great small club nights going on in and around the capital, but few have forged as distinctive an identity and inspired as cult-like a following as&#160;World Unknown. In not much more than two years, founders Andy Blake and Joe Hart and the regulars at World Unknown have built their own micro-scene from the ground up, thanks to a music policy that shares reference points with the under-appreciated experimental and wide-reaching electronic sound of mid-80s European clubs like Boccaccio and Ancienne Belgique and moves out in all directions from there. Taking in heavier strains of house and techno, EBM, strange European pop records, mysterious Eastern codas, pounding tribal rhythms and all manner of throbbing electronic music, World Unknown is widely regarded as one of the most vital nights happening now &#8211; a spotter&#8217;s delight and a dark dancer&#8217;s paradise &#8211; with FACT magazine calling it &#8220;the best place in London to hear EBM, new beat, synth wave, electro and acid house&#8221;. The WU duo have created a
unique brand of electronic music that is entirely their own and it&#8217;s a pleasure to welcome them &#8211; and their extensive record collections &#8211; to Bloc 2012.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/world-unknown" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=World+Unknown" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341680400" id="warlockb2bnoyeahno" startTime="1341673200" title="Warlock b2b noyeahno"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Warlock+b2b+noyeahno" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341684000" id="alis" startTime="1341680400" title="Alis"><itemDescription>Alis

[UK / Live]

The half Italian, half Bulgarian, London based producer and vocalist is bringing her new project to Bloc. Maybe better known under her previous alias, Subeena, she has released on labels Planet Mu and Fabric. Alis is her new project, that marries, as The Guardian so eloquently puts it, &#8216;her smoky, half-sung vocal to soft cymbal splashes and big drum claps&#8217;.

Here is an interview with Fact Mag on Alis&#8217; debut single &#8216;Twist the Rule&#8217;.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Alis" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Alis" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ywKwNDSyvKA" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341687600" id="lakker" startTime="1341684000" title="Lakker"><itemDescription>www.lakker.com

Lakker are an electronic group comprised of Ian McDonnell and Dara Smith. They make music with laptops using a variety of software. They formed in Dublin in 2003 having previously worked together as part of an electronic band called Undermine.

They have been described in the Journal of Music in Ireland (JMI) as &#8220;one of the best electronic acts in Ireland&#8221;. Their output has ranged from electro-acoustic soundscape pieces to mashed-up death-metal-sampling breakcore: a diversity reflected in their releases to date on labels such as Risc Records, Go Away Recordings and the online EP &#8216;Cosas&#8217; with The Alphabet Set. Their debut album, Ruido, was released in October 2007 on the Lazybird label.

Live performances have included support for numerous acts, including Andrew Weatherall, Tim Exile, The Bug, Aaron Spectre, Pamelia Kirstin, Chevron and Cylob. They have performed at a number of music festivals including the Dublin Electronic Arts Festival (DEAF), the Mor Festival, and the Leechrum and Mantua festivals.

You can obtain their album from their official website, www.lakker.com. They can also be found on MySpace at http://www.myspace.com/lakker.

Tags: irish, glitch, techno, beats, spotify</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Lakker" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/lakker" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/lakker" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Lakker" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1341691200" id="blackamiga" startTime="1341687600" title="Black Amiga"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Black+Amiga" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341694800" id="oneohtrixpointnever" startTime="1341691200" title="Oneohtrix Point Never"><itemDescription>Oneohtrix Point Never

The most lauded of Daniel Lopatin&#8217;s many aliases, Oneohtrix Point Never bubbled around the fringes of the drone-ambient-experimental scene for a few years before exploding into the wider conscious with 2011&#8217;s Replica. A shimmering opus of fractured samples, drawn-out blasts of noise and ghostly pop, it forged new directions for beatless music, establishing his fresh, dark, yet accessible form of ambient as a major musical force. While often considered one of last year&#8217;s breakthrough artists, fans of the style have of course been championing Lopatin for aeons, praising his distinctive collage of just-recognisable sound sources, masterful vintage synthesis, and uniquely skewed, strangely &#160;melancholic humour. Ardently lo-fi ,and yet widely regarded as among most sophisticated musical voices of recent years, the Oneohtrix Point Never live show is as intense and incendiary as you&#8217;d expect.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Oneohtrix+Point+Never" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oneohtrix_Point_Never" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/oneohtrix-point-never" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Oneohtrix+Point+Never" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hiwi7d0f91Y" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341698400" id="adj" startTime="1341694800" title="ADJ"><itemDescription>ADJ

[UK / DJ]

A veteran ambassador for IDM-influenced electro, ADJ aka Andy Jaggers is one of the scene&#8217;s most well-respected figures. With a resume including over 20 years of producing music and 25 years of DJing from Belgium to the USA, ADJ has released music over a myriad of labels, including Outside Recordings, Touchin&#8217; Bass, and his own imprint, Pyramid Transmissions. Aside from &#160;this, ADJ has been deeply involved with underground music for many years. Throughout the late 90&#8242;s, he acted as the music buyer for IQ Record Store, marking him as a curator in the London electronic scene. Expect a synthesis of advanced sounds, eerie pads and finely crafted blips with thick sub bass and syncopated drum patterns.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/ADJ" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/adj-808" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=ADJ" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341702000" id="radionasty" startTime="1341698400" title="Radionasty"><itemDescription>RadioNasty

[UK / DJ]

Keith Tenniswood (aka Radioactive Man) has been privy to some of the most twisted machine funk to emanate from the UK in the last decade, and has hooked up with production partner Billy Nasty for the project RadioNasty.

One of Bloc&#8217;s best-loved residents and an unending source of electro excellence, Radioactive Man returns in 2012 with a fresh set of churning 808 power. Starting out as an engineer for Sabres of Paradise in the 90s, Keith Tenniswood struck up a fruitful alliance with band member Andrew Weatherall, and the pair went on to re-write the techno rulebook later that decade with their peerless Two Lone Swordsmen material. Going solo as Radioactive Man, Tenniswood honed in on his unending love for all things electro, and emerged as one of the UK&#8217;s &#160;prime ambassadors for the sound, as evidenced on his albums &#8216;Radioactive Man&#8217; (2001), &#8216;Booby Trap&#8217; (2003), and &#8216;Growl&#8217; 2008. A bona fide Bloc hero &#8211; and responsible for countless seminal moments at the festival &#8211; &#160;it&#8217;s a pleasure to welcome him back once again this year.

A veteran of UK techno and electro who&#8217;s never rested on his laurels, Billy Nasty continues to fly the flag for quality techno-based music in its many forms. Starting out at the Brain club with Lost&#8217;s Steve Bicknell in the late 80s, he went on to become one of the international techno scene&#8217;s most travelled jocks, honing a fierce style that found an outlet in his legendary label Tortured towards the end of the century. He also championed the quality electro scene, most notably through his venerated Electric imprint, home to some of the sound&#8217;s most seminal club hits. A resident at Bloc since the outset, he continues to travel far and wide as a DJ, and has recently found acclaim through his collaborative work with Keith Tenniswood as Radionasty.

Preview Radioactive Man&#8217;s new EP &#8216;The Room&#8217; here.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/radionastyuk" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/radionasty" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/RadioNasty" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zZDTxCmjCnI" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341705600" id="altourettes" startTime="1341702000" title="Al Tourettes"><itemDescription>Al Tourettes

[UK / DJ]

A graduate of the same Bath Spa University music technology class that included Appleblim, Gatekeeper, Luke&#8217;s Anger and Wedge, Alec Storey first appeared in 2006 as Al Tourettes. before going on to explore the dubstep-techno crossover with Appleblim from 2008 onwards. Deep, driving, and dark, his recent spate of singles and remixes have included outings for Ostgut-Ton, Applepips, and of course, Bloc&#8217;s own Baselogic label, for which he provided the sparkling debut release. Drawing on his teenage experiences as a drummer, his frenetic and highly rhythmic live shows have seen him perform at Fabric, Nuit Sonores, Shambala festival and Space Ibiza, and he even contributed to the soundtrack for Darren Aronofsky&#8217;s film &#8216;Black Swan&#8217;.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Al+Tourettes" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/altourettes" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/altourettes" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Al'Tourettes" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dWn8ZR2ps3s" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341712800" id="lvis1990b2bbokbok" startTime="1341705600" title="L-Vis 1990 b2b Bok Bok"><itemDescription>L Vis 1990 b2b Bok Bok

[UK / DJ]

L-Vis 1990 (James Connolly) and Bok Bok (Alex Sushon) are the men behind Night Slugs, one of the most respected labels and collectives in today&#8217;s British bass scene. The label rapidly ascended through the ranks of the UK bass scene from its 2008 inception, producing a quality string of 12&#8243;s and a CD comp to across-the-board acclaim. &#160;Pitched somewhere between crystalline electro, buzzing club-ready steppers, and of course, no small amount of bowel-churning bass, both the label and the club night it&#8217;s named after famously disregarded the usual conventions of the scene. Working elements of upbeat Baltimore breaks, &#160;Detroit ghetto tech, the footwork/ghetto house hybrids of Chicago and echoes of complex African rhythms, the pair&#8217;s DJ sets are as electrifying and unpredictable as their far-ranging influences suggest.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=L-Vis+1990+b2b+Bok+Bok" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=37S6KPsgxio" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341716400" id="jonhopkins" startTime="1341712800" title="Jon Hopkins"><itemDescription>Jon Hopkins

Renowned for his meticulously arranged, emotively lush electronic music spanning everything from acoustic piano to hammering electro, Jon Hopkins is one of the UK&#8217;s finest &#160;and most highly-regarded composers. Not everyone gets to collaborate with the likes of Brian Eno, David Holmes,and King Creosote, and even less manage to do so successfully, &#160;but Hopkins took to the challenges with aplomb, gaining something approaching international producer superstardom along the way. As well as film scores for Peter Jackson and Gareth Edwards, he&#8217;s turned in stellar remixes for such varied artists as Wild Beasts, Nosaj Thing, James Yorkston and Four Tet, regularly transforming the source material into his own vast and cinematic electronic masterpieces. His own solo work, meanwhile, is expansive, symphonic, and near impossible to pigeonhole. Embarking on his first solo set after a long break, Bloc will be the first airing of tracks from his new electronic album.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jon+Hopkins" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jon_Hopkins" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jonhopkins" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/jonhopkins" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Jon+Hopkins" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l_Rcet8BjdM" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341723600" id="levonvincent" startTime="1341716400" title="Levon Vincent"><itemDescription>Levon Vincent

[US / DJ]

Few artists have electrified the underground techno-house community in recent years as NYC native Levon Vincent. With a heavy DJ schedule, a number 54 spot on the Resident Advisor top 100 DJs poll, massive releases on his own Deconstruct and Novel Sound imprints as well as outings for Berghain&#8217;s esteemed in-house label, Ostgut Ton all under his belt, it&#8217;s no wonder he&#8217;s one of the most sought-after artists of the moment. Blessed with an encyclopedic knowledge of classic house and techno music, his stunning productions are matched by his ability to throw together new and old music in fresh and exhilarating fashion behind the turntables. A proper DJ&#8217;s DJ, and an underground hero for our times.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Levon+Vincent" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/levonvincent" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Levon+Vincent" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Levon+Vincent" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LyKcRiq6BWA" type="youtube" /></item></line><line id="ceephaxacidwaltzers" title="Ceephax Acid Waltzers"><item endTime="1341583200" id="ceephaxacidswaltzerwarmup" startTime="1341579600" title="Ceephax Acid's Waltzer Warm-Up"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Ceephax+Acid%27s+Waltzer+Warm-Up" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341585000" id="cambodianchegwin" startTime="1341583200" title="Cambodian Chegwin"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Cambodian+Chegwin" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341590400" id="xenoglossyvscocadiscodjs" startTime="1341585000" title="Xenoglossy vs Cocadisco DJs"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Xenoglossy+vs+Cocadisco+DJs" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341594000" id="placid" startTime="1341590400" title="Placid"><itemDescription>There are 4 projects called &#8220;Placid&#8221;.

1) - A Industrial Project from the Spanish Members of Proyecto Mirage:
http://www.discogs.com/artist/Placid

2) - A Digital Hardcore / Industrial Rock project.

3) - A Techno Project:
http://www.jamendo.com/en/artist/placid

4) A DJ from Bristol specializing in early Chicago House.
http://www.acid-house.net

Tags: digital hardcore, industrial, ambient, house, detroit techno</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Placid" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Placid" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341597600" id="affieyusuf" startTime="1341594000" title="Affie Yusuf"><itemDescription>Aliases:
Big screen, EF.3.A, Levi Satchell, Lilac Road Productions, Parkwalker, The, Sian Loves It, Waterboatmen, The
In Groups:
House Of 909, Machines Don&#8217;t Care, Traffik, Yusuf &amp; Loveys
Variations:
All | Affie Yusuf | A Yusuf | A. Yusuf | A.Yusuf | Affie &#8216;Tab&#8217; Yousef | Affie Yussuf | Affie Yusuff | Andrew Yusuf | Aphos Yusov | Yusuf
Along with Basement Jaxx, House of 909 is one of the few British production teams able to rival their American counterparts in the creation of mainstream deep house. Anchored by Affie Yusuf.

The whole shebang started with Affie Yusuf an already a well established UK artist who had already recorded a solo &#8216;heavy duty&#8217; Techno album for the Huge German Trance label &#8216;Superstition Records&#8217; This album was called called The Volume, The Volume by Yusuf was Superstition&#8217;s first plunge into a mental Techno scene seen to some as quite a risky move considering they were so associated with Trance and Yusuf&#8217;s existing affiliations were with the amazingly solid German label Force inc also called The Force to many of its artists.

So onto the real House of 909, Yusuf had a chance meeting with a veteran of the underground called DJ NORTH part of the infamous South Coast duo DJ&#8217;s North and South. DJ South is Freaks Justin Harris. Yusuf had somewhat frequented a nut-job of a club in Bournemouth of all things called Kevins House* later becoming the damn right lunatic asylum Remix*

Tags: acid, under 2000 listeners, techno, acid techno</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Affie+Yusuf" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/houseof909" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/affieyusuf" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Affie+Yusuf" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1341601200" id="agtravecru" startTime="1341597600" title="AGT Rave Cru"><itemDescription>AGT Rave Cru are a DJ outfit, mashing up edits &amp; remixes of rave anthems, old skool classics, acid house, and electro. They are the hosts &amp; resident DJs of London&#8217;s monthly Acid House retrospective clubnight I Love Acid.

DJ Mag says: &#8220;like Altern8 meets 2ManyDJs in fluoro coats and Orbital glasses&#8230;beyond insane!&#8221;

Spannered.org says: &#8220;The Chas &amp; Dave of Rave&#8230; pure unadulterated fun&#8221;

Members are Joshu Doherty (of Posthuman) and various guests.

Many of their tracks &amp; mixes can be downloaded for free at http://www.soundcloud.com/agtravecru

http://www.agtravecru.com

Tags: breakstep, acid, rave, under 2000 listeners, hardcore</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/AGT+Rave+Cru" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/agtravecru" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/agtravecru/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/AGT+Rave+Cru" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1341605700" id="markarcheraltern8" startTime="1341601200" title="Mark Archer [Altern8]"><itemDescription>Mark Archer [Altern 8]

Rave heroes don&#8217;t come much better than Mark Archer, one half of facemask-wearing, 303 loving UK legends Altern 8. Hits like &#8220;Activ-8&#8243;, &#8220;E-vapor-8&#8243;, and &#8220;Frequency&#8221; still sound as mind-bendingly out of this world as they did over 20 years ago, and Archer continues to fly the Altern 8 flag with his slamming, retro-tinged DJ sets. From Detroit to London and back again, he&#8217;s a bona fide acid house master.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Altern-8" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/raveoursouls/mark-archer-altern8-rave-our-souls" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Mark+Archer+%5BAltern8%5D" type="google" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y86HFDvvn3c" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341666000" id="raykeith" startTime="1341605700" title="Ray Keith"><itemDescription>Ray Keith

[UK / DJ]

From rare-groove to acid-house to hardcore to jungle, Ray Keith is one of the most renowned veteran DJs to have emerged from the UK over the last three decades, whether as a permanent fixture on the rave scene 1980s and &#8217;90s or as one of breakbeat&#8217;s elder statesman today. After a remix of Orbital&#8217;s &#8216;Chime&#8217;, he became on of the most in demand names around, while his own radio show on Vibe FM confirmed his reputation as one of the most inspired drum&#8217;n'bass DJs and remixers of all time. His own productions, including the jump-up anthem &#8220;Terrorist&#8221;, began taking center stage by the mid-&#8217;90s, while his three separate labels &#8211; Penny Black, Dread and UFO &#8211; are home to numerous scene anthems and classics. A junglist hero and a slamming DJ, it&#8217;s an honour to welcome him to the Ceephax Acid Waltzers stage.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Ray+Keith" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djraykeith" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/ray-keith" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Ray+Keith" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Opkdc8e4bWY" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341669600" id="toosoonfordarude" startTime="1341666000" title="Too Soon For Darude"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Too+Soon+For+Darude" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341674100" id="xtricksbelgianravecartel" startTime="1341669600" title="X&amp;Trick's Belgian Rave Cartel"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=X%26Trick%27s+Belgian+Rave+Cartel" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341676800" id="romanticravers" startTime="1341674100" title="Romantic Ravers"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Romantic+Ravers" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341682200" id="eddmx" startTime="1341676800" title="Ed DMX"><itemDescription>Ed DMX

[UK / Disco set]

Ed DMX may be best known as purveyor of premium grade electro, acid and quirky techno, but for his slot on the Ceephax Acid Waltzers stage he&#8217;s delving into his bulging collection of disco 12s for a very special set. As anyone who&#8217;s heard Ed spin &#8211; or indeed listened to his excellent series of podcasts &#8211; will know, this guy is truly the king of record collectors, tracing down oddities, obscurities and gems from all eras of electronic music with an obsessiveness that would border on troubling if he didn&#8217;t make it sound so much fun behind the decks. Hold tight for a DMX disco session like you&#8217;ve never heard before.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DMX_Krew" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/edmx" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/lo-recordings/3-x-paradise-ft-cosmetics-ed" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Ed+DMX" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oPeL-rH-T5w" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341687600" id="jonnyjenkinson" startTime="1341682200" title="Jonny Jenkinson"><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Jonny+Jenkinson" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Jonny+Jenkinson" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1341692100" id="lukevibert" startTime="1341687600" title="Luke Vibert"><itemDescription>Luke Vibert

[UK / DJ]

A undisputed hero of British electronic music, Luke Vibert first made his mark with his Wagon Christ material &#8211; among numerous other monikers &#8211; &#160;in the early to mid-90s, joining like minded luminaries Squarepusher and Aphex Twin in their wayward restyling of rave. A graduate of the west country early 90s scene, Vibert&#8217;s music combines humour, weirdness, and &#160;off kilter references from dance music history to for a sound that&#8217;s most definitely all his own, as evidenced on classic albums including &#8216;Big Soup&#8217;, &#8216;Drum N Bass For Papa&#8217;, &#8216;Sorry I Make You Lush&#8217; and many more. Initially wiring hip-hop and drum n bass tropes in his own idiosyncratic style, he&#8217;s latterly moved onto acid, disco and techno pastures &#8211; sometimes, all at once &#8211; under a bewildering array of aliases. Critically acclaimed, beloved by music fans old and new, and utterly distinctive, it&#8217;s an honour to welcome Mr Vibert back to the Bloc stage.

</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Luke+Vibert" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Luke_Vibert" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/lukevibertacid" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Luke+Vibert" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hDLZbEQBehA" type="youtube" /></item><item endTime="1341696600" id="ceephaxacidcrew" startTime="1341692100" title="Ceephax Acid Crew"><itemDescription>Ceephax Acid Crew (often simply credited as Ceephax) is a British acid house, and drum and bass electronic musician named Andy Jenkinson. Jenkinson is also known simply by the pseudonym Ceephax, which is a pun on the BBC teletext service Ceefax. He is the brother of Tom Jenkinson, AKA Squarepusher, and for a while he shared living quarters with Jonathan Taylor, AKA Global Goon.

Underground record labels Firstcask, Lo Records and Breakin&#8217; Records each released music by Ceephax (his first record released when he was 18 years old). The more famous Rephlex Records and even more famous Warp Records both released remixes of Squarepusher by Ceephax which sound nothing like the originals.

Piers Martin interviewed Ceephax in 2000: &#8220;In the earlier days when Tom lived at home, I always used to play about on his synths if he was out,&#8221; Andy recalls. &#8220;Obviously Tom was doing loads of music and that was always inspiring, and one day it just clicked for me and I started doing music straight away.&#8221;

On Mary Anne Hobbs&#8217;s BBC Radio 1 show in 2003, Ceephax played unreleased songs. The only way to hear these is through bootlegs or the underground filesharing community Soulseek. Some of Ceephax&#8217;s music is still only available as poorly recorded bootlegs.

In 2005 Andy Jenkinson acted in short comedy films by Philie T of Chelmsford.

Ceephax&#8217;s music.

Tags: acid, electronic, idm, breakcore, electronica</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Ceephax+Acid+Crew" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ceephax_Acid_Crew" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/ceephax/music" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/030303recs/ceephax-acid-crew-south-bank" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Ceephax+Acid+Crew" type="discogs" /></item></line></schedule>