<?xml version="1.0"?>
<schedule xmlns="http://gaa.st/giggity#sched" id="90428e2c6f63e2661cf2c086e465195785613d44" title="Dance Valley 2011">
  <linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/google.png" id="google"/>
  <linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/lastfm.png" id="lastfm"/>
  <linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/wikipedia.png" id="wikipedia"/>
  <linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/myspace.png" id="myspace"/>
  <linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/soundcloud.png" id="soundcloud"/>
  <linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/discogs.png" id="discogs"/>
  <line id="mainstage" title="Mainstage">
    <item endTime="1312628400" id="bennyroyal" startTime="1312624800" title="Benny Royal">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/bennyroyal" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/bennyroyal/benny-royal-cigansko-original" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Benny+Royal" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Benny+Royal" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312632000" id="caritalania" startTime="1312628400" title="Carita la Ni&#xF1;a">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/caritalanina" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/carita-la-nina" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Carita+la+Ni%C3%B1a" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312635600" id="lilith" startTime="1312632000" title="Lilith">
      <itemDescription>&#x201C;Lilith&#x201D; is the name for at least nine different artists:
1) A Polish symphonic metal band founded in 1998
2) A Polish rock / metal band founded in 1999
3) A German-Kurdish female folk group founded in 1999
4) A German rock / metal band founded in 2001
5) A Spanish rock band from Barcelona
6) A Bolivian black / doom metal band from La Paz
7) An experimental music project by Scott Gibbons
8) A Japanese visual Kei band (tag as &#xFF2C;&#xFF49;&#xFF4C;&#xFF49;&#xFF54;&#xFF48; instead)
9) A Finnish goa trance project
10) A Colombian Rock band from Medell&#xED;n

1) Lilith is a Polish symphonic metal band founded in 1998 in Poznan.
www.myspace.com/lilithpl

2) Lilith is a Polish rock/metal band founded in 1999 in Radom.
www.myspace.com/lilithpoland

3) Lilith is a German-Kurdish women group which plays traditional, folk and world music. Lilith was founded in 1999 by Gabriele Thierkopf and &#x15E;ehriban &#xD6;zdemir. In 2003, when the group was complete, they changed their name from &#x201E;G&#xF6;&#x11F;&#xFC;n Yar&#x131;s&#x131; - H&#xE4;lfte des Lebens&#x201C; (Half Of Life) into the shorter name &#x201E;L&#x130;L&#x130;TH&#x201C;.The five artists are two German, two Kurdish and one Turkish-Alevi woman. They sing traditional and new composed folk songs about women themes in Kurdish (Kirmanji and Zaza), German, Yiddish, French and Turkish. These menmbers (four of them live in Germany) are: Gabriele Thierkopf (guitar and vocals), - &#x15E;ehriban &#xD6;zdemir (tembur, dshura), Sariyar (lead vocal), Luise Blum (violin) and Mavis G&#xFC;ne&#x15F;er (frame drum and vocals). Streamable album: &#x201C;G&#xF6;&#x11F;&#xFC;n Yar&#x131;s&#x131;&#x201D;.
(In contrast to here not streamable but however alternative artist profil is: L&#x130;L&#x130;TH)

Tags: gothic, gothic rock, polish, female vocalists, gothic metal</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Lilith" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Lilith" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312639200" id="trevorrockcliffe" startTime="1312635600" title="Trevor Rockcliffe">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/trevorrockcliffe" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/red-bull-elektropedia/trevor-rockcliffe-live-at" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Trevor+Rockcliffe" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Trevor+Rockcliffe" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312642800" id="koengroeneveldvsahmetsendil" startTime="1312639200" title="Koen Groeneveld VS Ahmet Sendil">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/koengroeneveld" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/ahmet-sendil/koen-groeneveld-ahmet-sendil-turboprop-ahmet-sendil-mix" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Koen+Groeneveld+VS+Ahmet+Sendil" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312646400" id="djmadskillz" startTime="1312642800" title="DJ Madskillz">
      <itemDescription>Dutch Dj and producer covering the niche between the rawer urban music and refined lounge music.

Tags: tech house, dutch, electro, lounge, house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/DJ+Madskillz" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djmadskillz1" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/intacto-records/dj-madskillz-burning" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/DJ+Madskillz" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=DJ+Madskillz" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312651800" id="fergie" startTime="1312646400" title="Fergie">
      <itemDescription>Stacy Ann Ferguson (born March 27, 1975 in Hacienda Heights, California) rose to prominence when she joined the hip-hop group Black Eyed Peas in 2003. While the group took a brief hiatus, she released her first solo album, &#x201C;The Dutchess&#x201D;, she was also featured in Slash&#x2019;s debut album &#x201C;Slash&#x201D; singing two rock songs &#x201C;Beautiful Dangerous (feat. Fergie)&#x201D; and &#x201C;Paradise City (feat. Cypress Hill &amp; Fergie)&#x201D;.

In the Summer of 2006. Her debut single titled &#x25CF;London Bridge quickly shot up to #1 on the Billboard Hot 100 chart. She later released &#x25CF;Fergalicious, Glamorous, Big Girls Don&#x2019;t Cry and &#x25CF;Clumsy, all of which led on to become top 5 singles on the chart.

As a child, she appeared on the television program Kids Incorporated for several years with Renee Sands, who would become another member of Wild Orchid. Ferguson&#x2019;s well-scrubbed image on that show presents quite a contrast with the &#x201C;ghetto-funk&#x201D; image she has more recently begun to cultivate. Ferguson was the voice of Sally Brown in two Charlie Brown specials: It&#x2019;s Flashbeagle, Charlie Brown (1984), Snoopy&#x2019;s Getting Married, Charlie Brown (1985) and also voiced Sally in the 1985 version of &#x201C;The Charlie Brown and Snoopy Show&#x201D;.


Official Site: Fergie.com
Brazilian Site: FergieBR.com

B) Fergie (real name Robert Ferguson) is a electronic music artist and DJ from Larne, County Antrim, Northern Ireland. He has mixed sets and released singles under the name Fergie, most notably for Godskitchen, Mixmag and Radio 1.

Tags: pop, rnb, female vocalists, hip-hop, dance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Fergie" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fergie_(singer)" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/fergie" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Fergie" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312657200" id="avicii" startTime="1312651800" title="Avicii">
      <itemDescription>Tim Bergling (born 8 September 1989), known professionally as Avicii and Tim Berg, is a Swedish DJ, remixer, and record producer. His single &#x201C;Bromance&#x201D; (recorded under the pseudonym Tim Berg, has charted in the top 20 on the national single charts of Belgium, the Netherlands, and his native Sweden. A lyricized version titled &#x201C;Seek Bromance&#x201D; was released shortly thereafter, charting on the UK Singles Chart and reaching number one on the international Beatport chart. Other singles include &#x201C;My Feelings for You,&#x201D; with Sebastien Drums, &#x201C;Street Dancer,&#x201D; and &#x201C;Tweet It,&#x201D; among others.

Avici is kind of like Dante&#x2019;s Inferno &#x2026; it&#x2019;s the lowest level of hell in Buddhism. A friend of mine told me about it, and it stuck in my head. I was going to make up a name for my MySpace page for the first time, and I just kind of went for it. I tried a couple of other before, but they were all taken (laughing). I kind of ended up with Avicii, and then I got really attached to it.
&#x2014;Tim Berg


Also known as Tim Berg

Tags: house, electronic, progressive house, electro house, dance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Avicii" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Avicii" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/avicii" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/tags/avicii" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Avicii" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Avicii" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312664400" id="steveangello" startTime="1312657200" title="Steve Angello">
      <itemDescription>Steve Angello (born Steven Angello Josefsson Fragogiannis in 1982) is a Greek-Swedish DJ, producer, and record label owner. He is part of a three person group dubbed the Swedish House Mafia, alongside Axwell and Sebastian Ingrosso.

Angello was born to a Greek father and Swedish mother in Athens, Greece. His father was killed when Steve was a teenager. A life in Stockholm, Sweden and music took the better of him. He started out as a Turntablist, fusing hip-hop, breakbeats and 70&#x2019;s classics but later moved onto house music, in the club life of Stockholm, together with his best friend Sebastian Ingrosso.

Steve Angello&#x2019;s claim to fame came when he released his remix of Eurythmics &#x201C;Sweet Dreams&#x201D; in late 2004. Since then he has exploded onto the house music scene. In 2007 his eternal club banger, a remix of Robin S &#x201C;Show Me Love&#x201D; was released on Data records.

Angello produces under several different aliases. On his own, he has called himself Who&#x2019;s Who and released tracks called &#x201C;Not So Dirty&#x201D; and &#x201C;Sexy Fuck&#x201D;. He often works closely with his childhood friend Sebastian Ingrosso on many projects. Aside from DJing together, they have also produced under the names Buy Now, Fireflies, General Moders, Mode Hookers, Outfunk, and The Sinners. Most recently, they released &#x201C;Bodycrash&#x201D; under their Buy Now alias, sampling the 1978 disco hit &#x201C;Let&#x2019;s All Chant&#x201D; by the Michael Zager Band. The track was first played by Pete Tong on his Radio 1 show in late 2007. Eventually, the Dirty South remix of the tune leaked out onto the Internet in January 2008. The track has since received a much larger release via Positiva Records, also including the Laidback Luke remix.

Tags: house, electro, electronic, progressive house, dance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Steve+Angello" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Steve_Angello" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/steveangello" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/kaskade/kaskade-vs-steve-angello-sorry" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Steve+Angello" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Steve+Angello" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="abovebeyondsgrouptherapystage" title="Above &amp; Beyond's Group Therapy stage">
    <item endTime="1312629300" id="boomjinx" startTime="1312624800" title="Boomjinx">
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boom_Jinx" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/boomjinx" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/boomjinx" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Boom+Jinx" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Boomjinx" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312633800" id="matzo" startTime="1312629300" title="Mat Zo">
      <itemDescription>Matan Zohar (a.k.a Mat Zo, Unripelemon, Reif, MRSA) was born in April of 1990 into a musical family. Throughout his childhood, music was a huge part of his daily life. He was pressured by his parents at an early age to take up an instrument, and when he picked up his first guitar in 1998, he quickly showed a talent for it. During this time he developed a love for Daft Punk. In 2001 he moved in with his dad in London. There he got his first computer and was able to kindle his interest for electronic music. Through the internet Matan discovered the vast world of music production. He then got hold of some production software and started developing his own flavour. Matan explored the styles of trance, drum and bass, house, currently going with a more progressive sound. After 3 years, his productions are played by high profile DJs such as DJ Tarkan, Perry O&#x2019;neil, and Swedish Egil.

By 2006, when he was only 16 years old, Matan had his first signing of a track, but it was after he won the Baroque Remix Competition with Lustral&#x2019;s &#x201C;In My Life&#x201D; that many world-class DJs and producers began to notice this young producer&#x2019;s great talents.

By mid-2007, Mat Zo had remixed the likes of Andy Moor and Markus Schulz. He became a DJ household name after Tiesto hired him to remix &#x201C;Driving To Heaven&#x201D;, and the remix appeared on Ti&#xEB;sto&#x2019;s internationally recognized &#x201C;In Search Of Sunrise 7&#x201D; CD compilation.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, melodic trance, electronic, anjunabeats</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Mat+Zo" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mat_Zo" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/matzomusic" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Mat+Zo" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Mat+Zo" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312638300" id="johnocallaghan" startTime="1312633800" title="John O' Callaghan">
      <itemDescription>1) John O&#x2019;Callaghan is an Irish DJ, mainly producing electronic music. He also produces music under the alias of Joint Operations Centre, Mannix and Stenna. He has also collaborated with fellow Discover artists such as Bryan Kearney, Neal Scarborough (as Inertia), Thomas Bronzwaer (as Lost World) and Greg Downey. His best known track is Big Sky, done with vocalist Audrey Gallagher, formerly of the 90&#x2019;s alt-rock band Scheer.

O&#x2019;Callaghan has had the majority of his work released on Discover, the British record label set up by John Askew. Recently, his work has been released by sub-labels of the Armada Music label; primarily on Armind and Soundpiercing. The remix of his vocal trance production &#x201C;Big Sky&#x201D; by Agnelli &amp; Nelson was voted &#x201C;Tune of The Year&#x201D; by listeners of Armin van Buuren&#x2019;s A State of Trance radio show in 2007.

In addition to numerous single releases, he has released a live album (Discover &#x201C;Live As&#x201D; Volume 2) and an artist album, Something To Live For. He entered the DJ Mag 100 in 2008 at number 60.

In 2009 he released his second artist album &#x201C;Never Fade Away&#x201D;, which includes famous track &#x201C;Big Sky&#x201D;.

2) John O&#x2019;Callaghan is the singer of the Arizona American based pop group, &#x2018;The Maine&#x2019;.

Tags: trance, vocal trance, uplifting trance, progressive trance, melodic trance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/John+O%27+Callaghan" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_O'Callaghan_(DJ)" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/johnocallaghan" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/John+O'Callaghan" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=John+O%27+Callaghan" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312643700" id="super8tab" startTime="1312638300" title="Super 8 &amp; Tab">
      <itemDescription>Only a select number of modern trance artists can convincingly say they are taking the sound to the next level. Although the humble, softly spoken duo would never shout it out themselves, Super8 &amp; Tab are undoubtedly among them.

Renowned for their innovative approach and intricate production values, the Finnish producers have stealthily pushed themselves to the front of the trance pack since coming together in 2005.
DJs like Armin van Buuren, PVD, Above &amp; Beyond &amp; Ferry Corsten regularly smash their tracks both club-side and on the radio, while global dance bibles such as Mixmag and DJmagazine laud them with 5 star reviews.

Through their own energising DJ sets, Super8 &amp; Tab themselves have conquered some of the biggest club brands in the game. They headlined the Future stage at this year&#x2019;s Trance Energy, recently played Australia&#x2019;s Future Music Festival and have also rocked trance totem poles like The Gallery, Mayday, Godskitchen, Trance Energy and A State Of Trance. On home turf, they command a legendary residency at Helsinki&#x2019;s legendary Hallmark club and also find time to hold down a regular spot on the monthly Anjunabeats Worldwide radio show.
Now an integral part of the Anjunabeats family, Super8 &amp; Tab first caused a fervour with the breakthrough success of tracks like &#x2018;First Aid&#x2019; and the definitive &#x2018;Helsiniki Scorchin&#x2019;. Since establishing themselves as the label&#x2019;s best selling artist behind Above &amp; Beyond, the Finnish trailblazers have delivered trance of the highest quality ever since - their ethereal epic &#x2018;Suru&#x2019; was picked out by DJmagazine as &#x201C;the tent-pole release of Anjuna&#x2019;s summer&#x201D;, while &#x2018;Elektra&#x2019; conquered the download charts and festival stages with equal aplomb in 2008.

Tags: trance, uplifting trance, progressive trance, anjunabeats, electronic</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Super+8+%26+Tab" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super8_%26_Tab" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/super8anddjtab" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/super8tab" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Super8+%26+Tab" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Super+8+%26+Tab" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312649100" id="cosmicgate" startTime="1312643700" title="Cosmic Gate">
      <itemDescription>Cosmic Gate is a German trance, progressive trance and hard trance duo made up of Claus Terhoeven (aka Nic Chagall) and Stefan Bossems (DJ Bossi). They are best known for their singles &#x201C;Exploration of Space&#x201D;, &#x201C;The Drums&#x201D;, and &#x201C;The Truth.&#x201D; Cosmic Gate has done remixes for popular DJs including Ti&#xEB;sto, Armin van Buuren, and Ferry Corsten. Cosmic Gate&#x2019;s heavy, analogue trance sound is considered by many to be the definition of hard trance.

Discography

Albums

* Rhythm &amp; Drums (2001)
* No More Sleep (2002)

* Earth Mover (2006)
* Sign Of The Times (2009)

Singles / EPs

* &#x201C;The Drums&#x201D; (1999)
* &#x201C;Mental Atmosphere&#x201D; (1999)
* &#x201C;Somewhere Over the Rainbow&#x201D; (2000)
* &#x201C;Exploration of Space&#x201D; (2000) #29 UK
* &#x201C;Fire Wire&#x201D; (2001) #9 UK
* &#x201C;The Truth&#x201D; (2002)
* &#x201C;The Wave&#x201D; / &#x201C;Raging&#x201D; (featuring Jan Johnston) (2002)
* &#x201C;Human Beings&#x201D; (2003)
* &#x201C;Different Concept&#x201D; (2004)
* &#x201C;I Feel Wonderful&#x201D; (featuring Jan Johnston) (2005)
* &#x201C;Tommorow&#x201D; (N/A)
* &#x201C;This Is The Party&#x201D; (2006)
* &#x201C;Should Have Known&#x201D; (2006)
* &#x201C;Analog Feel&#x201D; (2007)
* &#x201C;Body Of Conflict&#x201D; (featuring Denise Rivera) (2007)
* &#x201C;A Day That Fades&#x201D; (featuring Roxanne Emery) (2008)
* &#x201C;Not Enough Time&#x201D; (featuring Emma Hewitt) (2009)
*&#x201D;Sign Of The Times&#x201D; / &#x201C;F.A.V&#x201D; (2009)

DJ mixes

* Technics DJ Set Volume Three (2001)
* Techno Club Vol. 14 - Talla 2XLC Welcomes Cosmic Gate (2001)
* 3AM Rush (2002)
* Bitte Ein Beat! - Beat 3 (2002)

Tags: trance, progressive trance, hard trance, electronic, vocal trance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Cosmic+Gate" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cosmic_Gate" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/cosmicgate" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/cosmicgateofficial" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Cosmic+Gate" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Cosmic+Gate" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312653600" id="jaytech" startTime="1312649100" title="Jaytech">
      <itemDescription>In a world awash with carbon copy producers, 24-year-old James Cayzer aka Jaytech is a bright exception. Classically trained as a pianist and a perfectionist when it comes to programming, his unique blends of deep melodies and sunny electronic grooves are equally at home in the DJ sets of Sasha or Desyn Masiello as they are in the stadium headlining appearances of Above &amp; Beyond.

&#x2028;Despite his relative youth, Jaytech&#x2019;s prodigious creativity and prolific work rate (he started producing at just 14 and released his first track at 16) have seen him rise up as the most consistent artist on the popular Anjunadeep imprint &#x2014; even releasing the label&#x2019;s first full artist album through 2008&#x2019;s &#x2018;Everything Is Ok&#x2019; (&#x201C;Lush, melodic and soaked in electronic groove - a crossover gem&#x201D; **** -DJ Magazine), and hitting number one in the iTunes dance chart with his Anjunadeep 02 mix compilation in 2010. (&#x201C;Compilation of the month **** -Mixmag.)

Cementing his position as one of the leading lights within deep, uplifting electronic music, Jaytech&#x2019;s monthly mix show &#x2018;Jaytech Music&#x2019; now airs on radio stations across the globe and is downloaded by thousands as a monthly podcast. A window into his sound, it&#x2019;s also the best place to hear Jaytech&#x2019;s upcoming personal productions before anyone else.

Tags: progressive house, trance, progressive trance, house, progressive</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jaytech" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jaytech" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/jaytechmusic/jaytech-music-podcast-041" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Jaytech" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Jaytech" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312664400" id="abovebeyond" startTime="1312653600" title="Above &amp; Beyond">
      <itemDescription>Above &amp; Beyond are a British trance music group formed in 2000 and consists of the members Jono Grant, Tony McGuinness, and Paavo Siljam&#xE4;ki. The trio are popular in the electronic dance music scene for their forward-thinking uplifting trance productions and collaborations with renowned vocalists. They have their own record label, Anjunabeats, which releases trance &amp; progressive music, and they also host their own weekly radio show, Trance Around the World. The group&#x2019;s tracks are regularly played by DJs around the world, including Armin van Buuren, Gareth Emery, Ferry Corsten, ATB, and Kyau &amp; Albert. On 28 October 2010 DJ Magazine announced the results of their annual Top 100 DJ Poll, with Above &amp; Beyond placed at #5 in the world.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, vocal trance, electronic, dance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Above+%26+Beyond" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Above_%26_Beyond_(band)" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/aboveandbeyond" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Above+%26+Beyond" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="prydafriends" title="Pryda | Friends">
    <item endTime="1312632000" id="jeremyolander" startTime="1312624800" title="Jeremy Olander">
      <itemDescription>Pryda&#x2019;s prot&#xE9;g&#xE9;

Tags: house, progressive house, need to rate</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jeremy+Olander" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jeremyolander" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/jeremyolander" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Jeremy+Olander" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312637400" id="timgreen" startTime="1312632000" title="Tim Green">
      <itemDescription>Tim Green is a DJ and producer signed to Claude VonStroke and Christian Martin&#x2019;s San Francisco label dirtybird. Best known for his track &#x25CF;Revox which was played heavily at the Winter Music Conference in Miami and favoured by DJs such as Richie Hawtin.

Tags: tech house, minimal, minimal techno, electronic, house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Tim+Green" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/tg909" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/timgreen" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Tim+Green" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312642800" id="funkdvoid" startTime="1312637400" title="Funk d'Void">
      <itemDescription>Scotland&#x2019;s Lars Sandberg (Currently residing in Spain) aka Funk D&#x2019;Void has been releasing deep funky techno since roughly 1997, whilst Djing since 1986 . He&#x2019;s had three albums to date - &#x2018;1997&#x2019;s &#x2018;Technoir&#x2019;, 2001&#x2019;s &#x2018;Dos&#x2019;, and 2003&#x2019;s &#x2018;Volume Freak&#x2019; (all on Soma).

His new LP &#x201C;Second Skin&#x201D; promises a new arena for Lars to showcase his talents as he is constantly looking for new sounds and inspiration - whilst never losing that visceral, emotional core to his music and performances.

Tags: techno, electronic, tech house, tech-house, idm</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Funk+d%27Void" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/funkdvoid" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/funkdvoid" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Funk+D'Void" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Funk+d%27Void" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312653600" id="ericprydz" startTime="1312642800" title="Eric Prydz">
      <itemDescription>Eric Prydz is a Swedish DJ and producer best known for his 2004 hit single &#x201C;Call On Me&#x201D;, his remix of Pink Floyd&#x2019;s &#x201C;Another Brick In The Wall&#x201D; (known as &#x201C;Proper Education&#x201D;) and more recently the anthem &#x201C;Pjanoo&#x201D;.

He also releases music under the aliases of Cirez D, Pryda and Sheridan. Prydz produces electronic music which falls into a variety of sub genres, most notably house (Including electro house and tech house), minimal and techno.

Aside from producing music Prydz also runs the record labels Pryda, Pryda Friends, and Mouseville, which release most of his own music.

He has enjoyed great chart success with the singles &#x201C;Proper Education&#x201D; and &#x201C;Call on Me&#x201D;, the latter sampling the chorus of &#x25CF;Valerie (the only sample ever allowed of Winwood&#x2019;s work), which topped the UK singles charts for 5 weeks. &#x201C;Proper Education&#x201D; reached number 2, 4 and 12 in the UK, German and Swedish charts respectively.

Although it is reported that Eric Prydz has a fear a flying, he does not let that stop him from playing in places such as New York, as well as various countries in Europe.

Tags: house, dance, electronic, trance, techno</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Eric+Prydz" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eric_Prydz" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/ericprydz" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/eric-prydz" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Eric+Prydz" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Eric+Prydz" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="radioslave" startTime="1312653600" title="Radio Slave">
      <itemDescription>There are at least two artists who have used the name Radio Slave.

01
Radio Slave aka Matt Edwards

No matter what sounds you profess to be your music of choice, chances are, that at some point over the last five years, you will have got your rocks off to Matt Edwards.

As Matthew E he fashions club-based, dancefloor slayers. Under that aegis hes updated the classic Chi-town, sound beloved of house aficionados and layered it with fractured funk, belligerent, oddball beats and mechanical soul.

If Matthew E is all about the Saturday Night Fever, then, by contrast, Rekid is the slower, more deliberate, rhythmical funk of the mid-week mayhem. Its well-intentioned muscular intensity making it perfect soulful sustenance.

Quiet Village is something else all together. A collaboration with long-time musical sparring partner Joel Martin (a vinyl freak, like Mr Edwards, who works in esteemed auction house Christies pop department), its sample-based music which veers from drawn out disco-not-disco delirium to evocative, under-stated soundscapes.

Sea Devils - you keeping up at the back &#x2013; is undeniable electronic pop brilliance. Working with Tom from Cagedbaby, its the least niche of Matts projects and thanks to Sea Devils alluring pop dance grooves they will no doubt be shagging the upper reaches of the hit parade sometime soon.

Last, but by no means least etc, etc, etc, is Radio Slave.

Tags: minimal, techno, house, minimal techno, electronic</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Radio+Slave" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/rekid" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Radio+Slave" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Radio+Slave" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="joshwinkpresentsovum" title="Josh Wink presents Ovum">
    <item endTime="1312630200" id="bennyrodrigues" startTime="1312624800" title="Benny Rodrigues">
      <itemDescription>Benny Rodrigues has infiltrated himself in the list of famous Dutch top DJs in a very short time. This Rotterdam born and raised talent with Portuguese blood understands the art of using the funk, of getting the dancing floor full and the room to its feet. Although confessed because of its groovy/funky (deep) tech-house sound with lots of detroit, minimal and acid influences , he also knows that he has to do some work now and then and he knows how he must use that hatchet, what results in a particularly strong and delightful portion of techno which remains above everything well digestible.

Meanwhile he has turn tabled at all the major and important clubs and festivals in the Netherlands.
On the international base he has showcased his skills around the rest of the world (Opium Garden Miami, Hao Man 17 Jerusalem, Resident-dj for Chris Liebing&#x2019;s Spinclub night @ Space Ibiza &amp; Privelege, Ibiza, Antwerp where he held a 3 year saturday night-residency at the famous Belgium superclub: Cafe d&#x2019; Anvers + the annual Detroit&#x2019;s Electronic Music Festival (Movement/Fuse-in) where he is a gladly seen guest being invited twice (2005/2006) by the legends of techno: Derrick May &amp; Kevin Saunderson).

Besides his huge (mainly dutch) amount of dj-gigs, Benny&#x2019;s main focus nowadays is to produce music wich reflects his tipycal edge sound, so the rest of the world will get to know and experience where Benny Rodrigues musically stands for. With releases scheduled on Darren Emerson&#x2019;s (ex-Underworld) Underwater Records and other very interesting upcoming projects he&#x2019;s setting himself quite a good step in the right direction!

Tags: electronic, techno, trance, minimal techno, spotify</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Benny+Rodrigues" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/bennyrodrigues" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/bennyrodrigues" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Benny+Rodrigues" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Benny+Rodrigues" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312633800" id="maniklive" startTime="1312630200" title="M A N I K Live">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/manikmetalmusic/videos/manik-live/32217982" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/r_co/manik-live-15-years-of-ovum-wmc-24-03-2010/" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=M+A+N+I+K+Live" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312638300" id="djsneak" startTime="1312633800" title="DJ Sneak">
      <itemDescription>In 1983, Carlos Sosa aka DJ Sneak, moved to the city of Chicago from the island of Puerto Rico, where his early musical experiences and Influences were rooted in salsa, meringue and famous Latin orchestras. Chicago, like Puerto Rico, is a city rich with musical styles and sounds.

It was in Chicago that Sneak found inspiration in underground house music, Warehouse parties and &#x201C;old school&#x201D; mix tapes from the early pioneers - Farley Jackmaster Funk, Ralphi Rosario, Steve Hurley and local radio station shows played on WBMX. Sneak earned his nickname rocking designs in the graffiti tagging days and began working at retail stores as an airbrush artist, not long after he cultured the music industry world and began recording his first releases.

While at retail stores Sneak developed his DJing skills around the city working regular mobile DJ jobs and local nightclubs. In an already saturated DJ pool, Sneak focused on music production and started an independent label - Defiant Records. In 1992, using the fundamental studio pieces, Sneak began recording tracks with an unusual new style. In 1994, while still working at local store Gramophone Records sneak met Cajmere (Green Velvet) owner of Cajual and Relief Records.

Cajmere released some of Sneak&#x2019;s pivotal tracks and helped bring international recognition, with it, a global DJing career.In 1995, Sneak&#x2019;s new sound revolutionized house music with inspirational sounds and rhythms never heard. The disco filtered house grooves became Sneak&#x2019;s signature sound. Innovator to many, Sneak&#x2019;s love for music spawned current talents such as Daft Punk, Basement Jaxx &amp; Armand Van Helden.

Tags: house, chicago house, electronic, deep house, techno</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/DJ+Sneak" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DJ_Sneak" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/sneakthedj" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/dj-sneak" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/DJ+Sneak" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=DJ+Sneak" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312642800" id="davidesquillace" startTime="1312638300" title="Davide Squillace">
      <itemDescription>The fermenting Partenopean culture shaped Davide&#x2019;s attitudes and tastes in his early life; in 1995 the techno scene met the passion for his sound innovation and his destiny was born. When he was eighteen, to broaden the knowledge he acquired in Naples, underground he moved to London - the capital city of electronic-music.

In London, he started to produce his first work with just a few machines, which were studies on instruments functionalities and their ranges of use, and his first work was published by Primate and soon Audio and contrast published some EPs.

In 1999 Davide went back to Naples and he started to play gigs now and then. He took time out of playing and producing for two years to study sound engineering. This polishing of his technical knowledge allowed him to fully express his ideas and create work of outstanding quality.

Both DESIGN MUSIC and CONFORM, released his work initially, earning positive critical appraisal internationally. In time, Davide began to struggle with the limitations imposed on his music by these labels and decided to set up on his own. He therefore set up the Sketch project, to finally be free to create sounds true to his pure tastes.

Three years later he set up his second label, MINISKETCH, geared towards more minimalist productions. Davide Squillace is also known as erikOtanabE, an alter ego born as an outlet for another tangent of his genius where he assembles different kind of beats, with greater liberty taken using sounds &amp; samples. His tracks are a mix of minimal tek and glitch house, resulting in something the discerning techno listener can enjoy at a club as well as pottering about the house cooking some beans on toast.

Tags: minimal, electronic, techno, minimal techno artists, techno house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Davide+Squillace" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/davidesquillace" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/davide-squillace" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Davide+Squillace" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Davide+Squillace" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312647300" id="stevebug" startTime="1312642800" title="Steve Bug">
      <itemDescription>Germany&#x2019;s minimal dance connoisseur, Steve Bug, started his DJ-career in a small after-hour bar near Ibiza&#x2019;s Space back in 1991 - soon becoming resident DJ in the best club in his hometown Bremen and booked to major German events such as the Love Parade. In 1993 he released his first productions on Hamburg-based Superstition Recordings (which were immediately licensed by Risin&#x2019; High- UK) and in 1996 he founded his own label Raw Elements, followed by a 12&#x201C; for Felix Da Housecat&#x2019;s Radical Fear imprint. After &#x201C;Volksworld&#x201D;, his first LP on Raw Elements, together with the mix compilations &#x201C;Da Minimal Funk Part 1 &amp; 2&#x201D; Steve put the label to sleep in order to set up two brand-new platforms for vinyl releases &#x2013; Dessous and Poker Flat. Always crossing the bridges between house and techno with relaxed dignity, showing consequently that less can often be more, Steve Bug is soon to be acclaimed minimal tech-house master and one of the few gems of the innovative German electronic house scene. Poker Flat establishes
itself as the number one source for stripped down futuristic house music with amazing musical diversity and it&#x2019;s name spreads like wildfire with Steve&#x2019;s eternal minimal clubhit &#x201C;Loverboy&#x201D; in 1999 - the opener to his album &#x201C;The Other Day&#x201D; and the very first release on Poker Flat. For his second label&#x2013; the deep house oriented Dessous - Steve shows his passion for late night unhurried house and teams up with Vincenzo for the project &#x201C;Discowboys&#x201D;. A new mix compilation &#x201C;Steve Bug presents The Flow&#x201C; was released on Cocoon Records in 2001 and Steve remixes Robotman, ADNY a.

Tags: minimal, techno, minimal techno, electronic, minimal house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Steve+Bug" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/buginmyspace" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/nightclubber-ro/steve-bug-resident-advisor-258" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Steve+Bug" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Steve+Bug" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312650000" id="kinklive" startTime="1312647300" title="KiNK Live">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/kinkpbpm" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=KiNK+Live" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312656300" id="joshwink" startTime="1312650000" title="Josh Wink">
      <itemDescription>Josh Wink (a.k.a Winx, Wink, E-Culture, born Joshua Winkelman in 1970) is an electronic music DJ, label owner, producer, remixer, and artist. He is a native of Philadelphia, United States. A pioneering DJ in the American rave scene during the early 1990s, Wink was the most prominent exponent of the tribal forms of techno and house in the U.S. In 1995, he released several hits, including &#x201C;Don&#x2019;t Laugh,&#x201D; &#x201C;I&#x2019;m Ready&#x201D; (which hit number one on the U.S. Hot Dance Club Play chart) and &#x201C;Higher State of Consciousness,&#x201D; which topped the dance charts in Europe. He has had many recent club hits such as &#x201C;How&#x2019;s Your Evening So Far?&#x201D; (with Lil Louis) and &#x201C;Superfreak (Freak)&#x201D; and has also gained a lot of attention for his remixes of FC Kahuna, Paul Oakenfold, Moby, Towa Tei, Ladytron and Depeche Mode, among others.

Tags: techno, house, minimal, electronic, tech house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Josh+Wink" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Josh_Wink" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/joshwink" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Josh+Wink" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Josh+Wink" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="shlomiaber" startTime="1312656300" title="Shlomi Aber">
      <itemDescription>With his futuristic way of thinking that takes his sound a step beyond, Shlomi&#x2019;s studio works, alongside an exhaustive DJ schedule, are both the key reasons that make him one of the most touted up and coming talents that emerge in today&#x2019;s scene, with both his production and DJ skills held in high regard by many of his peers. His real breakthrough came in early 2006, when his releases found their way into the charts and playlists of many of the top DJs and magazines&#x2026; , with support from names such as John Digweed, Sven Vath, Danny Tenaglia, Pete Tong, Josh Wink, Green Velvet, Carl Craig and Tiefschwarz backed by inclusions in the tastemaker Cool Cuts, Buzz charts, and Top sellers to name but a few. Shlomi has established himself as a &#x201C;New Generation DJ&#x201D;. A DJ that defines himself through the music he is playing. Both his production and sets are based around Techno influenced underground House Music, creating a unique sound of intelligent and futuristic harmonies, and a natural mixture of strong and deep
grooves. His musical inspirations cannot defined by one genre, as they draw upon jazz and funk, house and minimal, in addition to acid and techno, all of which contribute to the unique sound and style that Shlomi has slowly been grooming over the last few years. &#x201C;Shlomi&#x2019;s sets are full with warm and unique sounds that makes you feel like you are going back to the better days of music, it was something I cant define just by one word , If I must I will call it something between house and techno

Tags: minimal, techno, electronic, progressive house, house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Shlomi+Aber" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/shlomiaber" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/elite-music-management/shlomi-aber-spring-mix" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Shlomi+Aber" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Shlomi+Aber" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="intecdigitalpresents" title="Intec Digital presents">
    <item endTime="1312630200" id="jimrivers" startTime="1312624800" title="Jim Rivers">
      <itemDescription>Jim is starting to make his mark. With his debut release, &#x2018;Restore EP&#x2019;, on Satoshi Tomiie&#x2019;s Saw Recordings imprint recieving critical aclaim and an inclusion on Satoshi&#x2019;s 3D compilation on Renaissance, Jim has announced himself to the dane music world. With singles due out on Nic Fanciulli&#x2019;s Saved Recordings, and an EP on EQ, Jim is firmly establishing himself as one to watch in 2006. Support has already come from the scenes biggest players including Sasha, Pete Tong (who played Restore on his legendary Essential Selection show on Radio 1 and included the track on his &#x2018;Tongcast&#x2019;), Nic fanciulli, Satoshi Tomiie, Paulo Mojo, Jody Wisternoff, The Flash Brothers, Chris Lake, Nick Warren, Greg Vickers, Hector Romero and many more&#x2026;

Recently Jim has turned his hand to remixing putting his mark on Mike Miller&#x2019;s - What You Feel on Nascent, The Remote&#x2019;s - Like You on Global Underground and Kreice&#x2019;s - A Cork In The Ocean on EQ, with more remixes lined up for the coming weeks and months&#x2026;

Jim currently holds a residency at Bristols best tech/prog/house night, Empathy and has impressed the likes of James Holden, Hybrid, Lee Burridge, Meat Katie, Andy Moor, Jay Tripwire, Nick warren, Timo Mass and others who have all graced the Empathy turntables&#x2026;

Tags: progressive house, house, minimal, tech-house, electronic</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jim+Rivers" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jimriversdj" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/jimrivers" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Jim+Rivers" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Jim+Rivers" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312635600" id="jonrundell" startTime="1312630200" title="Jon Rundell">
      <itemDescription>&#x201C;I think Jon&#x2019;s a jewel in the crown. He&#x2019;s been a great support to me. Put him in front of 30,000 people and he really goes for it. At the moment he&#x2019;s better than most top DJs I could mention.&#x201D; Carl Cox, 2007.

Tags: techno, electronic, minimal, minimal techno, acid</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jon+Rundell" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jonrundell" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/groups/jon-rundell-revolution-space-remix-contest" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Jon+Rundell" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Jon+Rundell" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312641000" id="robertbabicz" startTime="1312635600" title="Robert Babicz">
      <itemDescription>From Cologne, Germany techno producer has recorded a number of records as Rob Acid, Acid Warrior and Department of Dance for Force Inc in the nineties, now he begins releasing under his name since 2004. He also had records released by acid and techno labels such as Important and Labworks and at some point had launched his own label too, Junkfood. His most recent output is a blend of minimal and deep tunes with a lot of care taken for the detail. His mixes feature melodic constructs set, at times, in a more experimental field of electronic sounds which is considered innovative by many.

Tags: minimal, techno, minimal techno, electronic, tech house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Robert+Babicz" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Babicz" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/robertbabicz" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/psyjukebox/robert-babicz" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Robert+Babicz" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Robert+Babicz" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312646400" id="yousef" startTime="1312641000" title="Yousef">
      <itemDescription>Yousef
Dj / producer / remixer / promoter
Biography

Reputation is a wonderful thing. It&#x2019;s certainly something Liverpool DJ/Producer Yousef has come accustomed too, carving his own legacy across the global electronica circuit for close on a decade. Yousef was first bitten by the acid house bug at the legendary rave metropolis &#x201C;Shelly&#x2019;s&#x201D; in 1991 and since then has grabbed the global industry by the scruff of the neck, forcing his way in through sheer talent and determination. Residencies at Ministry of Sound, Renaissance and most notably Cream, cemented the scouse empire with a love of house at a point where trance began to rule clubland. Yousef then went on to conquer the rest of the UK taking his infallible understanding of house to Basics, Pressure, Shindig and every other top UK club. The rest of the world followed with Yousef skipping across continents with the same glee as the snapping beats in the music he played. Booked in the world&#x2019;s best clubs on a regular basis, Yousef quickly became synonymous as one of dance music&#x2019;s global figures, a position he
still holds to great acclaim.

It is clear that Yousef loves to travel (lucky then with the amount he does) &#x201C;I love seeing the world and its dancefloors&#x201D;, Yousef adds. &#x201C;I love going to Montreal, it&#x2019;s multicultural and multi-sexual and musically broad. My favourite places include New York, LA, South America and Brazil; it&#x2019;s so good down there - Rio, Sao Polo, Porto Alegre, amazing, high energy parties. In Argentina - The Mau Club so underground and intense. And then there&#x2019;s Asia, Japan, just a wonderful country where the vibes never fails to amaze me, Sydney, Melbourne, all over Europe, I could go on!&#x201D;

Tags: house, deep, underground, bbc radio 1, dance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Yousef" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/yousefcircus" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/yousef" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Yousef" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Yousef" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312650900" id="layobushwacka" startTime="1312646400" title="Layo &amp; Bushwacka">
      <itemDescription>Layo &amp; Bushwacka! are one of electronic music&#x2019;s most esteemed duos. Composed of Matthew &#x2018;Bushwacka&#x2019; B, a percussionist in the London School Symphony Orchestra who was converted into a member of the infamous Rat Pack after a warehouse party in &#x2019;88, and Layo Paskin, a North Londoner immersed in the acid house scene who met Mr C at one of the legendary Clink Street parties in 1988, before together setting up their world renowned night club, The End. It was via their mutual friend Mr C that Layo &amp; Bushwacka! first met, whilst Matthew was working at his studio, and by the mid 90s the two had started writing music together. Over a decade later, the partnership has yielded three artist albums, three mix albums, internationally renowned club residencies and a superb record label.

By 1999 they&#x2019;d already composed their debut album, &#x2018;Low Life&#x2019;, released on End Recordings, the label spawned by The End. The album announced the arrival of the duo as a force in electronic music, with a record that brought together electro, house and breakbeat fused with blues, dub and downtempo, all underpinned and informed by their collective experience of underground culture. This inclusive and open minded approach to sound became the blueprint for their future work.

Their sophomore album followed in 2002, this time released on the mighty XL Recordings. Entitled &#x2018;Night Works&#x2019;, the record featured their unforgettable top ten hit &#x2018;Love Story&#x2019;, and took their sound onto a bigger and broader canvas, selling 100,000 copies in the process.

Tags: electronic, house, breakbeat, dance, electronica</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Layo+%26+Bushwacka" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Layo_%26_Bushwacka!" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/olmetorecords" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/r_co/layo-bushwacka-live-sandwiches-wellington-new-zealand-09-10-2010" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Layo+%26+Bushwacka!" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Layo+%26+Bushwacka" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312656300" id="umek" startTime="1312650900" title="Umek">
      <itemDescription>Born in 1976, in Ljubljana, Slovenia, Uro&#x161; Umek began DJing in 1993. He and his friends helped develop the dance music scene in Slovenia, and between them they were responsible for putting on the first large scale parties in Slovenia. The result has been that Umek is Slovenia&#x2019;s most famous techno DJ, and a prolific producer. His current style is the combination of many different roots, which the more long term Umek fans may recognise. Starting with a rough, uncompromising edge he quickly built a reputation in the studio. However, more recently he has moved towards a funkier sound&#x2026;

Most of his tracks are named after medicines or other substances.

Tags: techno, minimal, electronic, electro, electronica</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Umek" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DJ_Umek" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djumek" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/umek" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Umek" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Umek" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="hernancattaneopresentssudbeat" title="Hernan Cattaneo presents Sudbeat">
    <item endTime="1312628400" id="cjay" startTime="1312624800" title="C-Jay">
      <itemDescription>There are two artists who use this name:
1) Dutch Progressive Psychedelic-Trance producer; and 2) Australian Hip-Hop producer.

1) Born in 1976, multi talented Dutch artist C-Jay took up an early interest in electronic and experimental music from the hands of artists like Jean Michel Jarre, Vangelis and Tangerine Dream. At the age of 11, C-Jay started taking his first muscial educations on the ins- and outs of both digital and analogue instruments, with the enthousiastic love and support of his parents.

As an artist / producer C-Jay got his first worldwide release in the spring of 2004.This tune (SwayWatch) got signed to the Moun10 imprint, (owned by Dutch house legend Jaydee) and got massive support from artists like The Flash Brothers, Chris Fortier and Fred Numf. After this first one the attention of the scene rapidly grew. His second release was made together with his friend Jaydee under their &#x201C;Graylock&#x201D; moniker and got released on First Impression Recordings, the label of &#x2026;&#x2026;Jaydee. This release got supported, played and charted by Armin Van Buuren, Ton TB, Paul Van Dyk, The Flash Brothers, Carl Cox, Chris Fortier and many more. The release also made it into the higher ranks of the world renowned Balance Record Pool charts.

Due to the fact that both releases were received so well by the international dance scene, C-Jay decided to start his own record label &#x201C;The Sessions Recordings.&#x201D; The basic idea behind it was to have no boundaries in releasing his own material, not having to depend on other labels in this early stage of his career and trying to draw the attention of the big guys even more.

Tags: electronic, house, progressive trance, iboga records, psychedelic</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/C-Jay" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/cjaysessions" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/c-jay" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=C-Jay" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312632000" id="eelkeklein" startTime="1312628400" title="Eelke Klein">
      <itemDescription>Ever since his 2003 landing in the world of electronic music, Eelke Kleijn has been a name synchronous with quality. Fans and enthusiasts worldwide have come to love the sympathetic Dutchman for his affectionate sound, unique productions and energetic DJ sets, which have taken him from sun-soaked Mexico to Russia, and almost everywhere in between. And it&#x2019;s not just the fans that are moved by his work; avid followers include internationally renowned DJs such as Hern&#xE1;n Catt&#xE1;neo, Sasha and Dave Seaman, who occasionally drop his tracks in clubs and festivals around the world.

Tags: progressive house, electronic, house, tech house, progressive</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Eelke+Klein" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/eelkekleijn" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/eelke-kleijn" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Eelke+Kleijn" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Eelke+Klein" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312637400" id="henrysaiz" startTime="1312632000" title="Henry Saiz">
      <itemDescription>Producer and DJ born in Madrid. He&#x2019;s been involved with music since very young, playing in several bands that offered a tribute to very different styles like black metal or pop. He showed a passion for synthesizers since he was a child, but it is in 1999 when electronic music captures him in an irreversible way, and he starts his fulltime dedication to music production. Since then, he has been working with several artists and bands linked to the vanguard, delivering many projects. While studying Sound Engineering he contacts Logicalnoise Records, where he finds a philosophy similar to his own and a flexible label that cares for quality proposals. Nowadays, he combines his work for advertising and documentary with electronic music and live performances.
Always open-minded to up and coming new styles and very fond of artistic vanguard, he delivers productions and sets that stand out for it&#x2019;s eclecticism and intensity, always trying to stimulate the audience.
Even before the launch of his first solo vinyl, the prestigious British label Global Underground spots Henry Saiz and asks him to remix the work from the German producer Phonique for a new vinyl that is about to be released.
His fist vinyl, &#x201C;Mamut Ep&#x201D;, released by Logicalnoise, is a really elegant and sophisticated piece that illustrates very well Henry&#x2019;s electronic music concept: hypnotic and powerful vibes to travel in the dance floor.

Tags: minimal, techno, tech house, neotrance, electronic</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Henry+Saiz" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/henrysaiz" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/henry-saiz" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Henry+Saiz" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312642800" id="jameszabiela" startTime="1312637400" title="James Zabiela">
      <itemDescription>James Zabiela is a DJ from Southampton in the United Kingdom. Mentored by Sasha, James&#x2019;s sets and releases are strongly influenced by tech house, electro house and breakbeat stylings and his unique capitalization of all available mixing aid &#x201C;utilities&#x201D; give his performances characteristic depth and professional production quality.

He is known for his turntable skills, extensive use of loops and effects, and the use of the Pioneer CDJ1000s, EFX1000 as well as more recently using Ableton Live.

James gained fame in 2000 by winning Muzik Magazine&#x2019;s Bedroom Bedlam competition, Best Bedroom Bedlam DJ 2001, and has since been signed to Sasha&#x2019;s Excession agency.

Tags: progressive house, electronic, house, progressive, electronica</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/James+Zabiela" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_Zabiela" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jameszabiela" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/jameszabiela/james-zabiela-paradigm-shift" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/James+Zabiela" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=James+Zabiela" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312648200" id="nickwarren" startTime="1312642800" title="Nick Warren">
      <itemDescription>You can tell when Nick Warren&#x2019;s on the decks. The music emanating from the DJ booth is that perfect club mix of driving percussion and soaring musicality, bursting out of the speakers, soaking everyone in melody, drenching them in sound. On the floor, where it really matters, the crowd experiences all the peaks and troughs that make Warren&#x2019;s sensibility so unique. He might start with his deeper take on house, then gradually morph into harder territory; then, once Warren has the throng fully in his grip, sweating and losing themselves in the grooves, moving on instinct, he takes them to points unknown they never expected to go. That&#x2019;s why Nick Warren is so respected: he knows how to truly work a crowd, delivering again and again, yet taking them somewhere they&#x2019;ve never been before. That&#x2019;s what comes with vision and, just as importantly in Warren&#x2019;s case, experience.

To this day, Warren remains at the forefront of club culture: he packs clubs and arenas worldwide from London to Los Angeles to Taipei, transfixing dancefloors with his distinctively forward blend of credible progressive sounds, cutting-edge techno, atmospheric breaks and any other crucial grooves Warren deems appropriate for his turntable alchemy. 2008 also finds Warren reaching other milestones. He&#x2019;s releasing his eighth mix CD for the Global Underground series, GU035: Lima; he&#x2019;s also completing his fourth studio album with Way Out West, Warren&#x2019;s pioneering electronic/band collaboration with Jody Wisternoff. Warren also recently became head of A&amp;R for Hope Recordings, keeping him immersed in the shifting tides of new dance-music movements. &#x201C;I&#x2019;m doing same thing I did when I started&#x2014;just playing music I love,&#x201D; he says.

Tags: progressive house, electronic, house, electronica, chillout</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Nick+Warren" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nick_Warren" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/nickwarrenhope" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/djnickwarren" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Nick+Warren" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Nick+Warren" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312653600" id="dannyhowells" startTime="1312648200" title="Danny Howells">
      <itemDescription>There are very few DJs who stand out in the world of dance music today, but Danny Howells is without doubt one of them. From his early years of DJing at Bedrock nights in his home town of Hastings, to the 10+ hour sets in New York today, one thing remains the same - a complete love of all music. It&#x2019;s this passion and plenty of hard work that has helped Danny to get where he is today. It&#x2019;s no coincidence that he&#x2019;s been placed in DJ Magazine&#x2019;s top 20 DJs in the world for the last 3 years. Danny has a unique, eclectic sound which as been described as &#x201C;deepsexyfuturistictechfunkhouse&#x201D; and it&#x2019;s this sound which which is shaking floors worldwide.

With over 12 years of experience, Danny has become truly international. His hectic schedule regularly takes him all over Europe, North and South America, Asia and Australia. He&#x2019;s DJed in the world&#x2019;s coolest clubs and held residencies at Renaissance, Twilo and Home. With 2002 came the announcement of an exciting monthly residency at Vinyl in New York, where Danny&#x2019;s 10 hour marathon sets are fast becoming legendary.

It&#x2019;s not just in the club where Danny has made a name for himself, he&#x2019;s also been busy in the studio. Albums for Global Underground, Renaissance and his own Nocturnal Frequencies series have been the highlights in a continually growing back catalogue of acclaimed mixes. As a producer his main focus is with co-producer Dick Trevor and vocalist Erire as &#x201C;Science Dept.&#x201D;. Last year they released the highly successful single &#x201C;Breathe&#x201D; and fans can expect more to follow in 2002.

Danny&#x2019;s infectious personality and individual style is what really puts him a cut above the rest though. You can really sense his connection with the crowd wherever he plays, and he has fully earned the label &#x201C;the clubbers DJ&#x201D;.

Tags: house, progressive house, electronic, progressive, lounge</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Danny+Howells" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Danny_Howells" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/dannyhowells" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/danny-howells" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Danny+Howells" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Danny+Howells" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="hernancattaneo" startTime="1312653600" title="Hernan Cattaneo">
      <itemDescription>Hern&#xE1;n became a DJ after being inspired by a collection of Chicago house records brought back from America by a friend, featuring artists such as Frankie Knuckles and Inner City. This music played a role in the music he now plays. Hernan describes the music he plays as deep, progressive, funky and tribal house.

In 1996, he won the residency at Clubland Pacha in Buenos Aires. His performances were a great success and led to Cattaneo being invited to DJ at clubs around Latin America. Clubland eventually attracted big-name DJs, such as Sasha, John Digweed, Dave Seaman and Paul Oakenfold who played alongside Hernan. Oakenfold was impressed and signed Hernan Cattaneo to his Perfecto Records label and they toured together in Europe and the United States from 1997 to 1999.

By 2000, Cattaneo was a major name on the world club circuit. Underground releases entitled Clubland Vol. 1 and Vol. 2 created an underground buzz. Also, a DJ magazine released one of his mixes called Funky, Deep &amp; Tribal in 2001. In 2002 he produced the international hit &#x201C;Deep Funk&#x201D;, released his first mix compilation entitled &#x201C;Perfecto Presents South America&#x201D; on Paul Oakenfold&#x2019;s label, and won the &#x201C;Best Newcomer DJ&#x201D; at the Pacha Ibiza Awards. Since releasing his first compilation, he has played about 200 shows a year on every continent around the world.

As a DJ with an ever increasing fanbase, he rose to #22 and then to #6 on the DJ Mag poll of the Top 100 DJs. In addition to appearing repeatedly on John Digweed&#x2019;s Kiss 100 Show due to great reviews of his mixes, Hernan also has a weekly residency show in London that is broadcast on MetroDance 95.

Tags: progressive house, house, progressive, electronic, dance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Hernan+Cattaneo" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hern%C3%A1n_Catt%C3%A1neo" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/hernancattaneo" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/hernancattaneo" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Hern%C3%A1n+Catt%C3%A1neo" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Hernan+Cattaneo" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="roogshouse" title="Roog's House">
    <item endTime="1312630200" id="phonicfunk" startTime="1312624800" title="Phonic Funk">
      <itemDescription>From the start Phonic Funk was inspired by the Funk. The Motown sound from mom &amp; dad&#x2019;s music collection appeared to be determining for Phonic Funk&#x2019;s musical preferences. While collecting music his preferences got more specific and around his 14th Phonic Funk started his own small drive-inn show. Friends, family and strangers could now meet the driven artist.

After the period of &#x2018;DAP&#x2019; turntables and Discmans the time was born to handle things more serious. Two Pioneer CD-players were bought so that it became possible to test own material. After the generally known &#x2018;Bedroom period&#x2019; the most satisfying mixes were spread to get clubs and organizers interested.

The Phonic Funk debut followed quickly at an illegal party organized by a friends organization. Step by step the Phonic Funk career and style evolved. Automatically the decision followed to give full dedication to house music.

In the meanwhile Phonic Funk had the honor to perform with the likes of John Acquaviva, Roog, Laidback Luke and Fedde Le Grand. This at recognized venues such as &#x2018;De Winkel van Sinkel and &#x2018;De Lichtfabriek&#x2019;.

To develop himself Phonic Funk has also devoted himself to the producing side of Music. Relatively quick this resulted in winning The Netherlands&#x2019; largest producer contest &#x2018;Vinylized&#x2019;.

Tags: spotify, deep, funky, chillout, house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Phonic+Funk" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/phonicfunkmusic" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/phonicfunkmusic" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Phonic+Funk" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Phonic+Funk" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312633800" id="balearicsoul" startTime="1312630200" title="Balearic Soul">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/balearicsoul" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/deejaykoma/balearic-soul-vs-ricky-l" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Balearic+Soul" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Balearic+Soul" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312637400" id="hardsoullivefeatrooggregvanbuerenmaevisacquaglennhelderbergetlew" startTime="1312633800" title="Hardsoul live! (feat. Roog, Greg van Bueren, Maevis Acqua, Glenn Helder, Berget Lewis, Sven Figee en ZO! Gospelchoir">
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Hardsoul+live%21+%28feat.+Roog%2C+Greg+van+Bueren%2C+Maevis+Acqua%2C+Glenn+Helder%2C+Berget+Lewis%2C+Sven+Figee+en+ZO%21+Gospelchoir" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312641000" id="roog" startTime="1312637400" title="Roog">
      <itemDescription>Roog (real name Rogier van Bueren) started buying records at the tender age of 7 years late 70&#x2019;s. Thru out the 80&#x2019;s he started playing at school parties, birthday parties and weddings. At the beginning of the 90&#x2019;s he fell in love with house music, the music that he heard while clubbing in Amsterdam&#x2019;s legendary clubs RoXY and iT. Roog has graduated from law school with a specialisation in Intellectual Property. Roog has been voted number 1 house dj of Holland last 3 years by Dutch Magazine; Bassic Groove, was voted most popular club dj of Holland 2004 by Nieuwe Revu Magazine and was the highest ranked house dj in the Dutch Dj Award poll of 2003 and 2004. Roog is playing an astonishing average of 225 gigs a year in and outside Holland. Roog played main stage at Sensation in the Ajax Soccer stadium to 40.000 people in 2001, which was broadcasted live by TMF and radio 538. This event brought him, from well known in the underground house scene, to the Dutch DJ super league. Roog has compiled 7 cd&#x2019;s till date. The
sound of Love and Dedication (United/Zomba, 2000) was the first compilation under his own name and was critically acclaimed by Dutch audiences as well as Dutch music press. The follow up was released in 2003 on his own Hardsoul Pressings label and became one of the biggest selling house compilations of 2003.

Tags: sexy house, spectrum rock, hiphop, electronica hiphop, experimental</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Roog" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/rooghardsoul" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/aerosonic" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/DJ+Roog" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Roog" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312644600" id="copyright" startTime="1312641000" title="Copyright">
      <itemDescription>There are, at least, four artists using this name.

1) London, UK based DJ/production duo Sam Holt &amp; Gavin Mills endeavour to make soulful house with a global vibe. They are soon to release of their debut album - Voices and Visions. A collection of soulful house, classic song-writing, with latin / afrobeat / disco / funk / tech influences, with guest singers.

&#x2018;Voices and Vision&#x2019;s&#x2019; is set propel Copyright into the super league of global house players. Having their first proper release on the hugely influential US label Soulfuric back in 2000, the boys proceeded to put out a slew of quality tracks on that and several other labels (including their own imprint, Copyright Recordings) in the early noughties. Tracks like &#x2018;Good For You&#x2019; feat Angie Brown, &#x2018;Bulo&#x2019; with longtime friend and percussion collaborator Shovel and &#x2018;Release Yourself&#x2019; set the pace, while their move to Defected in 2005 saw them jump up a gear with tracks like &#x2018;He Is&#x2019;, &#x2018;Bring Me Love&#x2019; and &#x2018;I Pray&#x2019;. The international recognition they received from these releases culminated in Defected boss Simon Dunmore asking Copyright to mix the 2007 &#x2018;Miami In The House&#x2019; compilation. Distilling the Copyright sound while showcasing their mixing prowess and nose for what makes a great party, it went on to sell more than 30, 000 copies globally. Which begs the question, with so much success, how come it&#x2019;s taken them so
long to finally deliver their debut long player? &#x201C;I think we wanted to wait until the time was completely right,&#x201D; says Gavin.

Tags: house, funky house, soulful house, canadian, dance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Copyright" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Copyright" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312650000" id="thenewibericanleaugue" startTime="1312644600" title="The New Iberican Leaugue">
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/djchusmusic/sets/the-new-iberican-league/" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=The+New+Iberican+Leaugue" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312653600" id="chocolatepuma" startTime="1312650000" title="Chocolate Puma">
      <itemDescription>Dance-act from Haarlem (The Netherlands), producing energetic and musical house. Their first single &#x2018;I Wanna Be You&#x2019; (2001) was an immediate success, entering the British top 10 at number 6.

Extract from the official webpage http://chocolatepuma.com:

&#x201C;Many beautiful years have passed between their first monster hit Give It Up and now. Born as first generation house producers, a complete musical revolution has taken place right in front of Zki &amp; Dobres eyes: From the first simple sampler, to a complete digital studio built into a laptop.

DJ Zki &amp; Dobre; who are they and what are they up to? Two simple but pressing questions which are not easy to answer. The Dutch producers Zki &amp; Dobre- respectively Ren&#xE9; ter Horst and Gaston Steenkist are responsible for so many productions in all kinds of styles under so many different names that they are extremely difficult to categorize.

Their studio remains their favorite place, but as DJ&#x2019;s, the clubs is where their music is being tested and where their music should be played out loud! Great examples are I Wanna Be U (2001), A Star Is Born (2003) and Always And Forever (2006) which they released under their alter ego Chocolate Puma.

Lets go back in time a little. For sure a special mission from outer space has helped faith a little to ensure that these two all-round musical guys bumped into each other in the 90s.

Together they produced their first hit; The Good Men &#x201C; Give It Up&#x201D;.

Ren&#xE9;: We are still very proud of Give It Up. It was created on a small mixer and mixed on broken speakers in Gastons bedroom. Its a unique record that people still sample and play. The whole world knows that record!

Tags: house, dance, electronic, club, vocal house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Chocolate+Puma" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zki_%26_Dobre" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/chocolatepumamusic" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/chocolate-puma" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Chocolate+Puma" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Chocolate+Puma" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312657200" id="thecubeguys" startTime="1312653600" title="The Cube Guys">
      <itemDescription>THE CUBE GUYS is a club project born in 2000 from the collaboration between two of the most important Italian producers: Roberto Intrallazzi and Luca Provera. Even if they have different background and professional training, they&#x2019;re united by their common desire to release new productions and give their own contribution to the international dance and club scene. They put together their previous experiences to launch their new label: the Cube that in 2006 has been renamed C90 Records.

Roberto Intrallazzi started his musical career at the end of the 80&#x2019;s as one of the producer of the F.P.I. Project , one of the most successful project of the &#x2018;made in Italy&#x2019; dance era, between the 80&#x2019;s and the 90&#x2019;s. Their track &#x2018;Rich in Paradise&#x2019; climbed all the worldwide charts and was considered one of the first house music releases. In the 90&#x2019;s his sound evolved over the years and became more &#x2018;house&#x2019;, but always influenced by the 80&#x2019;s electro experience. We can say that his music comes from the combination between the 80&#x2019;s typical strong energy and the research for new rhythms, with the contemporary minimal-electronic sound.

In 2000 Roberto Intrallazzi met Luca Provera, dj and producer.

Luca is a guy really keen on music and technology since he was very young, he started early to develop his own recording studio and to become familiar with computers, mixer, sampler and keyboards.

Tags: house, dance, funky, electronic, electroclash</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/The+Cube+Guys" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/cubeguys" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/thecubeguys/the-cube-guys-vs-david-jones" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=The+Cube+Guys" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="reneameszbaggibegovic" startTime="1312657200" title="Rene Amesz &amp; Baggi Begovic">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/reneamesz" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/baggi-begovic/rene-amesz-baggi-begovic-smells-like-teen-spirit" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Rene+Amesz+%26+Baggi+Begovic" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="roogshousemc" title="Roog's House (MC)">
    <item endTime="1312653600" id="ifanmc" startTime="1312633800" title="I/Fan (MC)">
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=I/Fan+%28MC%29" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="rogamc" startTime="1312653600" title="Roga (MC)">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/hiphoplogoscrew/videos/video/104482260" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/kriebels/jaz-von-d-feat-mc-roga" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Roga+%28MC%29" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="beatloverz" title="Beatloverz">
    <item endTime="1312628400" id="briandalton" startTime="1312624800" title="Brian Dalton">
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Brian+Dalton" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312632000" id="housereligion" startTime="1312628400" title="House Religion">
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=House+Religion" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312635600" id="nickyromero" startTime="1312632000" title="Nicky Romero">
      <itemDescription>Nicky Romero, born on 6 January 1989 grew up in a small city called &#x201C;Amerongen&#x201D;, lived in Canada (Kingston) for a few years.

Nicky hits the first snare drum at the age of 6 and started playing drums in a fanfare. After playing a year or three, he&#x2019;d been asked to play in a huge group who had acts on street and big events. That was fun though, but not enough for small Nicky. At the age of 12 he got is first set of Drums, and started practising, practising and practising. Well, after 3 years playing drums everyday and night , it was enough and he changed the drums for turntables.

School never had his interest, so after graduating he started producing music. And after hours, hours and hours of practising (throw lots of computers out of the window) he got his first label called &#x201C;Once Records&#x201D;, who&#x2019;s going to release the tracks: Privilege &amp; QWERTY.

After that deal, the next track came up called &#x201C;Funktion One&#x201D;. From that moment everything went very fast. Dutch famous DJ/Producer Madskillz got interested in &#x201C;Funktion One&#x201D; from that on Nicky signed Funktion at Azucar (from Madskillz &amp; Gregor Salto). Later they added &#x201C;Hear My Sound&#x201D; to their label two!

These day&#x2019;s allmost every high rated DJ has a few Romero records in his bag, last summer he did a remix for &#x201C;Sidney Samson &amp; Tony Cha Cha - Get On The Floor&#x201D; and a bootleg for &#x201C;David Guetta - When Love Takes Over&#x201D;. Both tracks got alot of publicity in the world, even Ministry of Sound Australia contacted him for doing some remixes on their label! About a few hundred movie&#x2019;s came up at youtube from dj&#x2019;s who playing the

Tags: house, electro house, minimal techno, minimal, electronic</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Nicky+Romero" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/nickyromeromusic" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/nickyromero/daft-punk-aerodynamic-nicky" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Nicky+Romero" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Nicky+Romero" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312639200" id="themartinezbrothers" startTime="1312635600" title="The Martinez Brothers">
      <itemDescription>&#x201C;It&#x2019;s not our fault we were born after the Garage closed!&#x201D;

Crank up the computer and Google &#x2026;the Martinez Brothers,&#x2026; and you&#x2026;ll be directed to chatrooms containing comments like &#x2026;Oh my god, can these two kids rock the house&#x2026; and &#x2026;They can mix their asses off&#x2026;not to mention postings along the lines of &#x2026;They are the cutest ever&#x2026; Such accolades would be impressive for any DJ, considering the backbiting that is the norm in the online dance-music community, but when you realize that the subjects of those notices, Steve and Chris Martinez, are still in their teens, it. .s remarkable. And considering that the Bronx-born and -raised sibs are working in the world of traditional, NYC-style soulful house&#x2026;a scene generally populated by relative graybeards&#x2026;it&#x2026;s downright mind-boggling.

Within the last year, the duo has been rising through the ranks by rocking some of the city&#x2026;s top soulful house shindigs, including Shelter (a soiree that was born the same year as the 15-year-old Chris) and Danny Krivit&#x2026;s 718 Sessions. They have further been invited to play at the longest standing soulful house party in Paris, Cheers in December and their names will be added to a list of DJ legends such as Timmy Regisford, Quentin Harris and Carl Craig when they headline Dublin&#x2026;s Surface event the same month. &#x2026;It was our father who really got us into this,&#x2026; says Steve, who&#x2026;s all of 18 years old. &#x2026;He&#x2026;s an old house head who goes back to the days of places like the Garage, but he had stepped away from the scene for a long time. Around three years ago, he played us a lot of the music and we both just fell in love with it&#x2026;

Tags: deep house, house, electronic, usa, minimal</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/The+Martinez+Brothers" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/themartinezbros" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/r_co/the-martinez-brothers-live-temple-san-francisco-12-03-2010" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Martinez+Brothers,+The" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=The+Martinez+Brothers" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312642800" id="quintino" startTime="1312639200" title="Quintino">
      <itemDescription>Quintino was born in a place called Den Helder, Netherlands. Here he started his carreer as DJ in a local club called Odeklonje. He quickly moved up and recently scored a #1 hit with the remix of Rap das Armas in the dutch music charts!

Tags: house, spotify, dance, electro house, electronica</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Quintino" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/marceloquintinocinalli" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/tags/quintino" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Quintino" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312646400" id="mastiksoul" startTime="1312642800" title="Mastiksoul">
      <itemDescription>MastikSoul started his career in 92, in a time where his life was split between Portugal and France, and from where he watched the raise of a new musical culture, that in association with his strong African roots designed his talent in a unique form.
Being connected to techno music for a while, where he released his first twelve-inch and developed his dj and producer skills, came in the late 90&#xB4;s with the desire of embracing other styles. House music became his main inspiration.

His vision and his style, both clearly reflect his origins, very percussive and tribal, and recently, with his musical productions, has been truly noticed and acclaimed by some of the biggest house names in the scene such as Tony Thomas, Tom Stephan, Grant Dell, Terry Francis, Nathan Coles, Layo, Circulation, Justin Drake from Peace Division, and also by the Uk&#xB4;s main dance press like Mixmag, Jockey Slut and Dj Magazine.
In the beginning of this century he builds a production studio in London, and materializes two important projects: 4Kenzo Recordings and Digital Distribution with dj Token Pace.
The dj work increases in this period and he plays in important clubs such as Rex (Paris), Ultimate Base (London), Gas (London), The Cross (London), Locomia (Albufeira), Kremlin (Lisbon), Alcantara Club (Lisbon), Decadance (Belgium) among others.

Tags: house, electronic, minimal, tech, dance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Mastiksoul" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mastiksoul" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/mastiksoul" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/mastiksoul" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Mastik+Soul" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Mastiksoul" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312650000" id="shermanology" startTime="1312646400" title="Shermanology">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/shermanologymusic" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/shermanology" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Shermanology" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312653600" id="hardwell" startTime="1312650000" title="Hardwell">
      <itemDescription>Let us introduce to you &#x2013; Hardwell!

At just 21 it&#x2019;s fair to say he&#x2019;s &#x2018;been around&#x2019; if you take into consideration his achievements over the past 18 months. His passion for music, in particular his love of all things house, has helped this multi-talented producer climb his way to the top. Hardwell&#x2019;s overall talent is recognised by the dance music industry as a new, exciting and refreshing take on a scene that continues to evolve and with an apparent everlasting shelf life!

&#x201C;Guess What&#x201D;, a recent co-production with Chuckie, is likely to be one of the most played underground house records of the past two years, his &#x201C;Show Me Love vs. Be&#x201D; bootleg of Steve Angello and Sebastien Ingrosso&#x2019;s track was one of the biggest dance hits of last year and &#x201C;MRKRSTFT&#x201D; has been included in almost all of the house compilations of 2008.

On top of this pronounced success stories, Hardwell has also topped the leading Dutch chart &#x2018;Dance-Tunes.com&#x2019; a grand total of 6 times in the past 12 months. He has also taken up remix duties for artists such as Chris Lake, Funkerman, Laidback Luke, Sharam (Deep Dish), Steve Angello, Booty Luv and Hi_Tack amongst others&#x2026;need we go on?

Behind the decks Hardwell never fails to deliver, his exceptional technical skills, variety of music and that added personal touch make him stand out, and he&#x2019;s ready to bring this to the masses.

There&#x2019;s a new kid on the block, and he&#x2019;s here to stay.

Tags: house, electro, dance, minimal, electro house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Hardwell" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/deejayhardwell" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/hardwell" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Hardwell" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312657200" id="boemklatsch" startTime="1312653600" title="Boemklatsch">
      <itemDescription>Boem, klatsch. Kick, snare. It&#x2019;s as simple as that. The Boemklatsch dj-collective is a colourful creative and energetic group of friends who give a tear-the-roof-of guarantee to everyone who books them. The crew is known to be ahead of the pack in all types of uplifting electronic music, and they still don&#x2019;t mind partying harder then their audience. They incorporate the newest styles of dance music into their territory and present it in a unique style.

The last years have been a rollercoaster ride for these guys. They&#x2019;ve started producing and putting out their own records. Make remixes for a variety of artists such as Stars &amp; Sons, Seymour Bits, Shameboy and Gorillaz and got remixed by oa Dem Slackers, Don Diablo, Hidden Cat, Peace Treaty, Schlachthofbronx and High Rankin. They put out two mix-CD&#x2019;s &#x2018;Mixing in Action&#x2019; and &#x201C;DUMDUM Genetics #1&#x201D; which both sold out in no time. Boemklatsch released their first studio album &#x201C;Spontaneous Combustion&#x201D; on April 17th in The Netherlands. The album contains unexpected international vocal features such as Aloe Blacc, Spoek and Princess Superstar on diverse beats that represent their wide taste of dance music. (The album track &#x201C;One More Day ft. Mike Lord was single of the week on iTunes Benelux). The album will be available worldwide by the end of this year.

Tags: hip-hop, electro, lowlands 2009, hip hop, aanheid</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Boemklatsch" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/boemklatsch" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/boemklatsch" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Boemklatsch" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Boemklatsch" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="vatogonzalezftmctjen" startTime="1312657200" title="Vato Gonzalez ft MC Tjen">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/vatogonzalez" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/vatogonzalez/crowd-control-podcast-4-mixed-by-vato-gonzalez" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Vato+Gonzalez+ft+MC+Tjen" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="beatloverzmc" title="Beatloverz (MC)">
    <item endTime="1312635600" id="mcjollygood" startTime="1312624800" title="MC Jollygood">
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/andyleka/andy-leka-jolly-good-mc-at" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/search?type=all&amp;q=Dj+Dyna+%26+Mc+Jolly+Good" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=MC+Jollygood" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312650000" id="mcmitchcrown" startTime="1312635600" title="MC Mitch Crown">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/mitchcrown" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=MC+Mitch+Crown" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="zawdimc" startTime="1312650000" title="Zawdi MC">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/zawdi" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/jasper-clash/jasper-clash-feat-zawdi-mc" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Zawdi+MC" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="beatloverzmc2" title="Beatloverz (MC)">
    <item endTime="1312635600" id="isax" startTime="1312628400" title="I-Sax">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/isaxinjah" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=I-Sax" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312653600" id="andreirusso" startTime="1312642800" title="Andrei Russo">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/andreirusso" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/andrei-russo" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Andrei+Russo" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Andrei+Russo" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="hq" title="HQ">
    <item endTime="1312630200" id="andyfarley" startTime="1312624800" title="Andy Farley">
      <itemDescription>Andy Farley is a popular hard house DJ/producer, famed &#x201C;The Godfather of Hard House&#x201D;.

Andy Farley [US-Chicago] is a young minimal techno/tech house DJ/producer, famed &#x201C;lover of nerd dance music&#x201D;.

Tags: hard house, techno, hard dance, dance, tidy</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Andy+Farley" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/andyfarleydj" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Andy+Farley" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Andy+Farley" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312635600" id="fausto" startTime="1312630200" title="Fausto">
      <itemDescription>There are 2 musicians known as &#x201C;Fausto&#x201D;
1.
First is Carlos Fausto Bordalo Dias, or simply Fausto, is a portuguese multi-instrumentalist musician born in 1948.

2. Fausto is a Dutch DJ, born in 1970, Amsterdam.

1. Having grown up in Angola, he received influences from African ethnic music there. Militant against the fascist government in Portugal, he teamed with other great names of Portuguese &#x201C;Folk&#x201D; like Jos&#xE9; Afonso, S&#xE9;rgio Godinho, Jos&#xE9; M&#xE1;rio Branco and Adriano Correia de Oliveira.
With more than 12 recordings since 1970, his album Por Este Rio Acima started a new era in Portuguese music.

In the style of portuguese Folk, is seconded perhaps only by Jos&#xE9; Afonso in the number of his recordings.

2.
Fausto Talone was born on November 15th 1970 in Amsterdam, the hometown of his mother. His father comes all the way from Rome,
Italy, which explains the fact that Fausto lives in The Netherlands,
but listens to a 100% Italian name.

Clubs, parties and housemusic

At the age of 17 he discovered the world of clubs, parties and housemusic, which had just started to reach Holland, coming across the ocean from the great clubs in New York, Chicago and Detroit. Soon he was addicted to the Vibe called housemusic and started to go to houseparties more often. Then something happened to him that happens to all true DJ&#x2019;s at a certain moment: he got fascinated by the guy standing in front of the partypeople and playing his favourite tunes; Tha Vibe struck on him. Ladies and gentlemen:
DJ Fausto was born&#x2026;

Tags: portuguese, portugal, folk, hardstyle, portuguese folk</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Fausto" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Fausto" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312639200" id="jp" startTime="1312635600" title="JP">
      <itemDescription>At least 4 artists are producing under the name JP:

1. Rappare fr&#xE5;n Esl&#xF6;v

2. JP is the Brazilian producer Joao Paulo who delivers Freak Out as the next Digital EP on PsyCore Records. With the constant support of Max Lanfranconi and Raja Ram, within a few years JP has become a highly demanded artist.

With a slight teasing progressive start, Freak Out really jumps out at you by track two with fresh grooves
that will do nothing but get you on any trance floor experiance.

The whole Freak Out EP experiance takes you through 5 magical tracks loaded with deep funky psychedelic beats, killer melodies and an array of leads and breakdows that simply, Freak Out! Did I mention the word magical? This magical EP experiance reflects the magic of JP and the magical home land of Bahia, Brazil.

3. Rock Guitarist from Finland. Same person &#x201C;Dj zei&#x201D;

4. A Hip Hop artist from Melbourne, Australia. Also a member in the 9 Piece Progressive Hip Hop group The High Society.

Tags: psytrance, psychedelic, electronic, fullon, full-on trance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/JP" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=JP" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312642800" id="scotproject" startTime="1312639200" title="Scot Project">
      <itemDescription>Taught how to spin by his brother at 13, Frank Zenker alias Scot Project bought his first electro record in 1983 and had begun DJing by 1986, playing breakdance tracks at local youth clubs. Fascinated by the first acid and house tracks in the late 1980s, Scot Project began to incorporate these new sounds in his sets, showcasing music from the house, hip hop and techno scene.

By 1990 he had landed several residencies around Frankfurt and two years later began building his own studio, closely followed by his first single; &#x2018;X&#x2019; released on Overdose in 1995. By the time his hugely successful second single &#x2018;U (I Got A Feeling)&#x2019; hit clubland in 1996, Scot Project was playing regularly in the USA, Canada, Brazil, Russia and Israel. A massive European club hit, it was &#x2018;U&#x2019; that launched DJ Scot Project to international fame

Scot Project has also completed a string of highly-regarded remix projects for German labels including Pulse, Fog, Area and Intercord among others. Most recently, he enjoyed massive success in the UK during 2001, applying the midas touch to the big room track of the moment; &#x2018;Firewire&#x2019;.

Bringing deeper, dirtier trance to his sets, DJ Scot Project combines hard percussive elements with melodic trance. In his own words: &#x2018;The perfect combination of sugar and spice.&#x2019;

Tags: hard trance, trance, techno, electronic, dance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Scot+Project" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scot_Project" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/scotprojectofficial" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/DJ+Scot+Project" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Scot+Project" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312646400" id="organdonors" startTime="1312642800" title="Organ Donors">
      <itemDescription>Hard dance / hard trance producers&#x2026; best check their official website www.organdonors.dj

Tags: hard trance, trance, hard house, dance, hard dance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Organ+Donors" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/organdonorsdj" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Organ+Donors" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312650000" id="tomharding" startTime="1312646400" title="Tom Harding">
      <itemDescription>Tom Harding was born in Bristol, UK in the year 1974.
He&#x2019;s become famous as a HardDance/HardHouse DJ all over Europe.
He was also the Resident DJ of the monthly HQ parties @ Melkweg, Amsterdam.

Tags: hard house, hard trance, rock, stoner rock, trance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Tom+Harding" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/recordertom" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Tom+Harding" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Tom+Harding" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312653600" id="tidyboys" startTime="1312650000" title="Tidy Boys">
      <itemDescription>Legendary Hard House pairing from Rotherham, individually known as Andy Pickles and Amadeus Mozart, a duo who through their work as pioneers of the biggest label in Hard Dance music, Tidy Traxx, have arguably long since established themselves as the most important force in the Hard Dance scene. They are famed for their energetic performances on stage while DJing and their sense of humour which has without doubt rubbed off on the whole Tidy franchise.

Tags: favourite artists, trance, tech trance, seen live, hard house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Tidy+Boys" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Tidy+Boys" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Tidy+Boys" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312657200" id="yoji" startTime="1312653600" title="Yoji">
      <itemDescription>Japanese DJ Yoji Biomehanika, who has recently reduced his artist name to Yoji

Tags: techno, hard trance, japanese, japan, hard techno</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Yoji" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yoji_(DJ)" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/yojibiomehanikaofficial" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/kido_yoji" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Yoji+Biomehanika" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Yoji" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="andywhitby" startTime="1312657200" title="Andy Whitby">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djandywhitby" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/andywhitby" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Andy+Whitby" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Andy+Whitby" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="hqmc" title="HQ (MC)">
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="mcdasilva" startTime="1312624800" title="MC Da Silva">
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/MC+Da+Silva" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=MC+Da+Silva" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="showtekpresentsdutchmasterworks" title="Showtek presents Dutch Master Works">
    <item endTime="1312628400" id="thera" startTime="1312624800" title="Thera">
      <itemDescription>Thera is a 5-piece Alaskan rock band forging their own brand of epic, soaring music. Their goal is to create the kind of music that ranges from majestic highs to crushing lows in the span of one song, leaving the listener breathless and reeling in its wake. Thera began writing such music after solidifying their lineup in January of 2009, and releasing the remarkably mature ep, The Aftermath, in April of 2009. However, the true beginnings of the band go back much earlier: Thera was first conceived in 2005 by founding members Ronnie Plate and Stephanie Plate in the small-town of Soldotna, Alaska, where they cut their teeth playing their first local shows. They quickly progressed to playing around the rest of the state, which brought them into contact with their future drummer, Benny Maus. They found their lead guitarist, Mason Venhaus, after moving to Oklahoma in the summer of 2007 in order to pursue both music and higher education.

After returning to Alaska in the start of 2009, Thera added their fifth and final member in bassist Steven Cornfield. They quickly regained and increased their local fanbase with the release of The Aftermath and consistent gigging.

Work on their full-length indie debut, If This Is the End&#x2026;, began in the fall of 2009. Set to release in February of 2010, If This Is the End&#x2026;

Tags: female vocalists, post-hardcore, alternative rock, rock, alternative</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Thera" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Thera" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312632000" id="nitrouz" startTime="1312628400" title="Nitrouz">
      <itemDescription>NitrouZ, aka JP Pirrello, is considered to be one of the biggest Hardstyle Talents in Australia. At a young age he was surrounded by music; learning to play the piano and singing in the school choir and other youth choirs. His singing was quite successful, performing at the openings of some of Sydney&#x2019;s most prestigious events as well as singing on albums.

Dance music had always been a part of his life as his older siblings passed down the music that they so passionately listened to, the music that was heard throughout the clubs at the time. This was also the music that was played at the &#x201C;all age&#x201D; events that he attended. When he turned 18 he began to develop his skills as a DJ and became attracted to the pulsing beat of the harder styles of Dance music. Overwhelmed with his passion for dance music JP decided to follow his dream of becoming a DJ and Producer. He built his own recording studio and is now on the path to his dream.

After a number of years of travelling and learning his craft JP is now set to release on Dutch Master Works, one of the World&#x2019;s Number 1 Hardstyle Labels, home to Showtek, Dutch Master and many more great talents.

In 2008 it seemed JP&#x2019;s dream of becoming a world renowned DJ/Producer and vocalist was finally coming true. He was invited to play at X- Qlusive Showtek at the Heineken Music Hall in Amsterdam and also the prestigious Defqon 1 Festival in Almere Holland, both of which are great honours to bestow on any DJ.

Tags: hard trance, hardstyle</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Nitrouz" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/producerdjnitrouz" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/NitrouZ" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Nitrouz" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312635600" id="kodex" startTime="1312632000" title="Kodex">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/kreationkodex" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Kodex" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312640100" id="abyssjudge" startTime="1312635600" title="Abyss &amp; Judge">
      <itemDescription>Biography Abyss &amp; Judge

&#x201C;The Abyss &amp; Judge sound is very diverse,&#x201D; says DJ/producer Gevrey Heijnes, &#x201C;but catchy as well. We prefer hardstyle with great melodies, heavy basses and pounding kicks.&#x201D; He should know, since he forms the Abyss &amp; Judge duo together with fellow DJ/Producer Justin Putuhena.

Abyss:
Gevrey decided to get involved with the magic of vinyl at the age of 15. Records and mixing tracks were really something to focus on and so oldstyle, hardcore and houseclassics (Late 80&#x2019;s and early 90&#x2019;s) were the start in his repertoire. More people started to notice Gevrey&#x2019;s unique skills and passion to always look for exciting new musical paths. So it was no surprise when the hardstyle sound started to conquer the scene, Gevrey was on the forefront.

After sending a mix-cd to Q-dance Gevrey performed in the talent room of Qlubtempo #5. After this, things just got better and Gevrey played on several major events in Holland; Matrixx, QrimeTime, DefQon One Festival, Qlimax(VIP), X-Qlusive labels, Seqtion and several other local/national and international events (Lloret De Mar, Callela, Mallorca). Since 2003, Gevrey (co) produced a handful of well received productions on labels such as Straight On Recordings and DJS Records.


Judge:

Tags: hardstyle, shuffle, techno, hard techno, makes me wanna shuffle</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Abyss+%26+Judge" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/abyssjudge" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/club-matrixx/abyss-judge-dreamfields" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Abyss+%26+Judge" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Abyss+%26+Judge" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312643700" id="activator" startTime="1312640100" title="Activator">
      <itemDescription>There are multiple artists with the name Activator.
1) An Italian hardstyle DJ and producer
2) A heavy rock band from Austin, Texas.
3) An afropunk metalcore band from New York.

1) Activator is an Italian hardstyle DJ and producer.

2) Activator was formed at the end of 1990s in Austin, Texas. Their debut album &#x201C;Both Barrels&#x201D; (2004) mixes heavy fuzz rock riffs and Black Sabbath-like heavy and groovy bass. The band is currently on hiatus and now Jason Roberts (vocals), Jason &#x201C;JRo&#x201D; Roberts (guitars) and Scott Cerda (drums) are in a blues band called El B.

Band members:
Jason Roberts - vocals
Scott Cerda - drums
Jason McMaster - bass
Derek Halfmann - guitar
Jason &#x201C;Jro&#x201D; Roberts - guitar

3) Activator is an afropunk metalcore band from New York.

Band members:
Shannon - vocals
Jared - guitar
Cavassa - bass
Jimmy - drums

Tags: hardstyle, stoner rock, hardbass, italian hardstyle, psychedelic rock</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Activator" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/activatorwins" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Activator" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312648200" id="alexkiddkutskiexperience" startTime="1312643700" title="Alex Kidd &amp; Kutski Experience">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djalexkidddotcom/blog/540198737" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/rossco-addict/alex-kidd-and-kutski" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/Alex-Kidd-Kutski-Goodgreef-Present-The-Alex-Kidd-Kutski-Experience/release/2407427" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Alex+Kidd+%26+Kutski+Experience" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312650000" id="toneshifterz" startTime="1312648200" title="Toneshifterz">
      <itemDescription>Toneshifterz, aka Elie &amp; Olcay, is an upcoming hardstyle project from Sydney, Australia. They are signed to Fusion Records, home to famous hardstyle artists like Zany, Noisecontrollers and Donkey Rollers.

Elie produced UK Hardcore, House, trance and electro while Olcay was also producing UK Hardcore and Gabber. They occasionally produced together as Lumin8 &amp; Cheever. Then after the opportunity arose in Australia with the arrival of Q-Dance this opened up many oppurtunities for the Australian Born and bred Duo. They decided to begin producing hardstyle together, bringing Australian hardstyle to a totally new level, and have now placed the country down under, on the map.
Even though they are still fairly new in the hardstyle scene, in 2009 they had a massive response to their music, gathering support from massive artists from the top&#x2026; Within their first year, coming from Australia, they have already played at Defqon.1 Australia, and have begun their Europe Tour.

Toneshifterz now are, and have been signed to the renowned Fusion Records and have had some massive releases that started with &#x201C;Sahara&#x201D;. After that they we&#x2019;re honored enough to work with the talented and most awarded hardstyle artists in the scene at the moment, the &#x2018;Noisecontrollers&#x2019; on their second release collaborating the tracks &#x201C;Jaydee&#x201D; and &#x201C;Empire of the Sun&#x201D; which both were massive hits.

Tags: hardstyle, rave, shuffle, hard dance, australian hardstyle</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Toneshifterz" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/toneshifterz" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Toneshifterz" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Toneshifterz" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312654500" id="dblockstefan" startTime="1312650000" title="D-Block &amp; S-te-fan">
      <itemDescription>With a big love for melody and bass, D-Block &amp; S-te-Fan (real names Diederik &amp; Stefan) found eachother at the end of 2004. Exploring their musical strengths seperately, both guys knew that this meeting was the beginning of something they dreamed from the beginning they started getting their musical love to a higher level.

Diederik always had a big love for melody. Music was not only his passion, but also his strength. With his father producing electronic music in his own studio in Amsterdam, Diederik heard the word music before he even knew what it was. This fact resulted in a big musical interest in the years that passed.

Stefan started to create his musical point of view in the early nineties, when happy hardcore was introduced. Evolving his love for music in the years after, Stefan always remembered the hard pounding tracks, with huge melodic influences from that period.

After they started to work as a team, things went fast. All of their releases got huge feedback, and were played by all the major jocks, resulting in several bookings for the biggest parties hardstyle knows (for example: Qlimax, DefQon.1, Mysteryland, Decibel, Thrillogy, Reverze, Q-Base)

For a year Diederik and Stefan hosted the &#x201C;Next Chapter&#x201D;, a hardstyle label with some of the most popular releases, like: Keep it coming, Lockdown, Natte asbak and Guilty.

Nowadays they are the happy owners of the &#x201C;Scantraxx Evolutionz&#x201D;, a sublabel from the &#x201C;Scantraxx&#x201D; label which will bring you huge releases with one goal: to get every party started!

More info at: http://www.dblock-stefan.com/

Tags: hardstyle, hardbass, jumpstyle, nu-style, house</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/D-Block+%26+S-te-fan" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/D-Block_%26_S-te-Fan" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/dbstf" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/D-Block+%26+S-te-Fan" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=D-Block+%26+S-te-fan" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312658100" id="dutchmaster" startTime="1312654500" title="Dutch Master">
      <itemDescription>1.
Olaf Veldkamp - DJ and Producer brought in by Dutch Master Works in 2009 to replace Henry Snijders who decided to leave the Dutch Master project.

2.
Dutch Master, aka Henry Snijders, is considered one of the biggest hard-style talents. At the age of 16 he was already a resident in a huge club in his hometown. The place where he developed his DJ Skills. Dutch Master became more and more attracted to play dance-music in the harder styles. Stimulated by his passion for music Henry began to live his dream of becoming a DJ and producer. He owns his own recording studio and works together with the guys of Showtek.

After two years Dutch Master delivered his first hard-style tracks: Insomnia and Get up, these tracks became the absolute club-bangers! Even DJ Luna called it the track of the year 2006. The track slammin&#x2019; the bass is released on vinyl and on the album from Showtek. The track is also released on the Sensation black 2007 CD.

As a new upcoming man in hard-style it&#x2019;s difficult to get your own little space. But the hard work he puts into his dream is paying of. He went on tour with Showtek around Europe and also played at X-Qlusive Zany. Dutch Master was also booked for Defqon1 2007 and Q-base.
For this artist see www.slimshore.nl

Tags: hardstyle, techno, jumpstyle, hardbass, dutch</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Dutch+Master" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Dutch+Master" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312662600" id="showtek" startTime="1312658100" title="Showtek">
      <itemDescription>The Eindhoven based act existing of the brothers Wouter (1982) and Sjoerd Janssen (1984) form the Dutch hardstyle formation Showtek. After their first release &#x201C;Save the Day&#x201D;, which scored more than twenty compilations CDs, they immediately established their name in the Dutch dance scene. Their follow up &#x201C;Controller&#x201D; turned out to be one of everyone&#x2019;s favourite hardstyle track, and Showtek became more and more popular in The Netherlands and in other countries.

Later they released their records in co-operation with ID&amp;T. This was a step forwards in the career for the two guys. So in March 2003 their record &#x201C;Seid Ihr Bereid&#x201D; was released on the Q-Dance/ID&amp;T label. Again a pounding track which is on every DJ&#x2019;s playlist.

The two brothers are booked on big events and clubs all over the Netherlands (Sensation Black, Shockers, Qlubtempo, Hardbass Extreme, Loudness, Qlimax, Xxlerator), and they have a monthly residency in their hometown, which is a great success. But they are not only spinning records&#x2026; They also have a blasting live act. Their latest track is &#x201C;Puta Madre&#x201D; in 2006. They recently cooperated with Gizmo and released &#x201C;3 The Hard Way&#x201D;, and created &#x201C;Rockin Steady&#x201D; with Deepack.

Besides their great teamwork as Showtek, they also have their own solo projects. The youngest brother, DJ Duro produced his first record &#x201C;Again&#x201D;.

Tags: hardstyle, techno, jumpstyle, hardtrance, hardbass</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Showtek" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Showtek" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/showtekmusic" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Showtek" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Showtek" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="showtekpresentsdutchmasterworksmc" title="Showtek presents Dutch Master Works (MC)">
    <item endTime="1312662600" id="mcthawatcher" startTime="1312624800" title="MC Tha Watcher">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/mcthawatcher" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/MC+Tha+Watcher" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=MC+Tha+Watcher" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="enhancedmusicpresentshardtechnotitans" title="Enhanced Music presents Hard Techno Titans">
    <item endTime="1312630200" id="alexkvittalive" startTime="1312624800" title="Alex Kvitta Live">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/alexkvitta/photos/35325638" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/enhancedmusic/alex-kvitta-live-at-enhancedtv05012011" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Alex+Kvitta+Live" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312635600" id="djboldvspaullangley" startTime="1312630200" title="DJ Bold vs Paul Langley">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/paullangley/photos/41678258#!" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/search?type=all&amp;q=Paul+Langley+%26+DJ+Rush" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=DJ+Bold+vs+Paul+Langley" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312641000" id="frankkvitta" startTime="1312635600" title="Frank Kvitta">
      <itemDescription>Hard blasting techno at 150-158 BPM on 3 or even 4 decks: THAT&#xB4;S FRANK KVITTA. He knows how to rock his crowds and has already had bookings all over the world, including clubs like Sulivan Room in New York, Tunnel in Linz, u60311 in Frankfurt, K4 in Slovenia, Suburbia in Italy, Tor 3 in D&#xFC;sseldorf and many, many more. He is also very successful as a producer.

Having released and releases planned on labels such as lifeform, artillery, carnage, bitshift, schubfaktor, crowbar, combat skill, highball, free vision, audio aussault, kne&#xB4;deep rec., pattern rec., inflicted rec., friendly fire rec., insane rec., bullshit rec., kvitta rec., abstract rec. and many more&#x2026; Furthermore Kvitta and ViperXXL started their own label &#x201C;Insane Records&#x201D;. He also started a new label with Ben Santo called &#x201C;Bullshit Records&#x201D;. Frank started as a dj 1997 when he found a tape with electronic music. He liked this kind of music and decided to buy records and started with some friends to dj. 2000 frank started to play at small partys around germany. 2001 was the year when he decided to produce his own tracks. He doesn&#xB4;t wanted to be longer just a dj. When frank gave dj rush 2001 a demo cd of his own tracks, rush gave him the chance to release on his label kne&#xB4;deep rec. 2002 he released his first remix on a technolabel in germany.

Tags: schranz, hard techno, hardtechno, electronic, kvitta</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Frank+Kvitta" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/frankkvitta" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/frank-kvitta" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Frank+Kvitta" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Frank+Kvitta" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312646400" id="robertnatus" startTime="1312641000" title="Robert Natus">
      <itemDescription>Robert Natus is a man who not only certainly knows his own mind but also continuously and straight sets new standards. He is a member of the &#x201E;young savages&#x201C; who could set up a steady place in the music scene in a nutshell and besides stands out as the creator of the genre Hardtechno. His musical foundation was already laid to the turn of the millennium, besides, he succeeded in 2004 with the introduction of the progressiv music character Hardtechno in pulling an incalculable and also abstract demarcation to the item &#x201C;Schranz&#x201D; which was falsely associated with him and his sound.

His success constitutes on his strict principle of selfcreation, everything is penned by himself, he had to trouble marketing machinery and media hype at no time, straight-lined and with absolute energy he styled his own empire. This was the right decision as you back up with his triumphal processing cross the clubs. His thick-twisted network from homebase and atmosphere of departure offers him the perfect base.

His more than hundred own releases as well as remixes carry his clear regalia of the bohemian imagination, all carry equally a closed work in themselves, indifferently whether it concerns releases under his project name &#x201C;Pneumatik&#x201D; or &#x201C;Brainshaker&#x201D;. Outstanding his debut album with the adequate title &#x201C;Straight&#x201D; or the works for DJ Rushs Globalhit &#x201C;Get on up&#x201D; to entitle only some highlights.

The turn of his intensive life time dream into truth turned him to one of the most popular DJ of a loyal young following within shortest time which can be proved by overcrowded dance floors of the clubs and events.

Tags: schranz, hard techno, techno, german, hardtechno</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Robert+Natus" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/robertnatus" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/jack-ds/kai-tracid-vs-robert-natus" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Robert+Natus" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Robert+Natus" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312650900" id="arkusplive" startTime="1312646400" title="Arkus P Live">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/video/bahiajakrussel/live-arkus-p-at-lagoa-pounding-and-techno-music/103394435" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/turi/turi-live-arkus-p" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Arkus+P+Live" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312656300" id="petduo" startTime="1312650900" title="Pet Duo">
      <itemDescription>DJ David PET and DJ Ana PET are the PET DUO. Hard Techno DJs, they play almost every time together in 4 decks. From the brazilian underground clubs, like A Loca, in Sao Paulo to to Berlin and Amsterdam, and big festivals as &#x201C;I Love Techno&#x201D; and &#x201C;Monegros&#x201D;, the couple spread huge and fast beats around. Known for their four-deck sets, the couple spends their time between Europe and Brazil, playing in the best clubs, parties, and festivals around the world. http://www.petduo.com

s&#xF3; pet salva!

Tags: schranz, hard techno, techno, hardtechno, fucking amazing techno</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Pet+Duo" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/petduo" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/petduo" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/PET+Duo" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Pet+Duo" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="borisslive" startTime="1312656300" title="Boris S Live">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/hardfactory/blog/486926078" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/frank-kvitta/god-s-army-live-awakenings" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Boris+S+Live" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="nachtboetiek" title="Nachtboetiek">
    <item endTime="1312628400" id="enricodeluca" startTime="1312624800" title="Enrico de Luca">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/enricodelucamusic" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/iansolano/solano-making-waves-enrico-de-luca-remix" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Enrico+de+Luca" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312628400" id="emielroch" startTime="1312624800" title="Emiel Roch&#xE9;">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/pdjmusic" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/emielroche" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Emiel+Roch%C3%A9" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312631100" id="rubenvitalis" startTime="1312628400" title="Ruben Vitalis">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/rubenvitalis" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/ruben-vitalis" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Ruben+Vitalis" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Ruben+Vitalis" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312634700" id="mikes" startTime="1312631100" title="Mike S">
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Mike+S" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312637400" id="groovenatics" startTime="1312634700" title="Groovenatics">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/groovenatics" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/groovenatics" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Groovenatics" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Groovenatics" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312641000" id="jean" startTime="1312637400" title="Jean">
      <itemDescription>There are currently two artists named &#x201C;Jean&#x201D; as of the year 2009.

1) Jean, part of the progressive trance doujin circle Einherjar Records. More information regarding this circle can be found on http://www.einherjarrecords.net/.

2) Jean Carlos Rodr&#xED;guez L&#xF3;pez-Cepero (born December 10, 1980), better known by his stage name Jean, is a Puerto Rican singer and the younger brother of composer / singer / soap opera actor Luis Fonsi. Jean is signed to Sony BMG and released his debut album On in 2006. His second studio album, Out the Box, was released on December 9, 2008.

website: www.jeanmusiconline.com

Tags: breakbeat, touhou, pop, pop latino, doujin ongaku</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jean" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Jean" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312644600" id="gelazershagspeareladybeeftthedarkraver" startTime="1312641000" title="Gelazer! Shagspeare &amp; Lady Bee ft. The Darkraver">
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Gelazer%21+Shagspeare+%26+Lady+Bee+ft.+The+Darkraver" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312650000" id="spider" startTime="1312644600" title="Spider">
      <itemDescription>There is more than one artist called Spider

Spider is an alias for Brooklyn indie-folk musician Jane Herships. Most of the songs on her only release so far,The Way to Bitter Lake, are hushed, personal folk songs with elements of shoegazing reminescent of musicians such as Nick Drake and M. Ward.

Spider was a New Wave Of British Heavy Metal band from the late seventies/early eighties.

Spider was also a Hungarian punk rock band in the 90&#x2019;s.

Spider is Erin from The Spits and his girlfriend. Lo-fi. synth. post-punk. new wave.

Spider is a Malay rock band with ska influences from Malaysia.

Spiders (order Araneae) are air-breathing arthropods that have eight legs, and chelicerae with fangs that inject venom.

Tags: folk, acoustic, singer-songwriter, female vocalists, indie</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Spider" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Spider" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312653600" id="randykatana" startTime="1312650000" title="Randy Katana">
      <itemDescription>Randy Katana originally came from the Dutch Antillean Islands (Aruba, Curacao and St Maarten), where for many years he worked as resident DJ at many of the trendiest clubs on the Islands. He also spend many years playing drums in Brass Bands, which on the islands where specialized in Carnival music. This is where Randy acquired the Latin tribal soul that he projects in his music today.

Shortly after moving to Amsterdam in 1988, he started his own record company BPM Dance and opened one of the most successful online vinyl shops till this day: Only-Djs.com. After experiencing difficult times in the music industry, because of the free downloads, he decided to become a fulltime DJ. January 2003 he stopped the activities in the companies and by the end of the year he agreed to become resident DJ to, what was to become one of the hottest places in party history in Amsterdam, &#x201C;Xtra Large&#x201D; (Marcanti Plaza) and &#x201C;Crazyland&#x201D;. It took him only two years to make his first entry in the DJ Mag world top 100 list, in 2005, at number 150.

Currently Randy Katana is working on an album that will specifically project his unique style combining new material with special edits of floor fillers. The album was initially scheduled to be released in the end of 2006. But the dance scene changed so fast in this period that he decided to wait and see what direction it would go. 2007 is the year of the &#x201C;Electro&#x201D; sound.

Tags: trance, hard trance, dance, electronic, tech-trance</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Randy+Katana" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Randy_Katana" type="wikipedia"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/randykatana" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Randy+Katana" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Randy+Katana" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312657200" id="mem" startTime="1312653600" title="MEM">
      <itemDescription>The Mem sound is characterized by soaring melodies and lush musical textures. With a newly-released debut album, &#x201C;A Peek At Heaven Through Square Binoculars&#x201D;, and an exuberant live presence, the band is headed feet-first to the top.

Mem&#x2019;s musical style has changed significantly over the last three years. Having previously released two very electic EPs in &#x201C;Equilibrium&#x201D; (2004) and &#x201C;5 to 6&#x201D; (2005), mem have once again reinvented themselves with the refreshing take on lo-fi indie pop featured on their debut LP.

Mem&#x2019;s existence has been characterized by its closely-knit cast of musicians. At the core of the band is singer/pianist/songwriter Grayson Sanders. The latest Mem line-up also comprises Alex Kveton (guitars, strings, vocals), Sam Greenfield (bass), Mike Morrill (drums, vocals), and Jonathan Koh (guitars, vocals).

Tags: trance, progressive trance, mellow, jazz, progressive</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/MEM" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/memmusic" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=MEM" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="bingoplayers" startTime="1312657200" title="Bingo Players">
      <itemDescription>Bingo Players (Paul B&#xE4;umer &amp; Maarten Hoogstraten) have been left gasping for air after a seriously hectic year with bookings in the Netherlands and abroad. Outgrowing local bingo halls to play with the big ballers of the game has been the result of their hard work and devotion. The Bingo Players appear to have been made for each other, the proof of which came in November 2009, when the DJ/producer duo topped the Beatport overall chart for a second time with their remake of the dance floor classic, &#x201C;Devotion&#x201D;, which stayed on no. 1 for two weeks and over a month in the top 10!

Back in 2008 the Bingo Players were still experiencing the extensive aftermath of their UHM &amp; Tony Flexx &#x2013; &#x201C;Our House&#x201D; remix. The cooperation with Chocolate Puma on the legendary label Strictly Rhythm/Defected, &#x201C;Touch Me&#x201D; was released and gained support all over. If that wasn&#x2019;t enough, it also hit Beatport&#x2019;s chart number one position! &#x201C;Touch Me&#x201D; then appeared on various compilations, like Defected In The House and Sensation White.

After that, Dutch house mogul, ErickE&#x2019;s &#x201C;Wanna Go Again&#x201D;, was treated with the inner Bingo and this remix hit the Dance Tunes top position and was inserted in the CD machines of Noir, Sander van Doorn and Patric La Funk amongst others. In September 2008 &#x201C;Get Up&#x201D; hit the shelves following a huge buzz and support from Laidback Luke, A Trak, Crookers and made it onto the 2008 I LOVE TECHNO! compilation, mixed by Boys Noize.

Tags: house, electronic, dirty house, techno, electro</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Bingo+Players" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/bingoplayers" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/bingoplayers" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Bingo+Players" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Bingo+Players" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="nachtboetiekmc" title="Nachtboetiek (MC)">
    <item endTime="1312646400" id="mcboogshe" startTime="1312624800" title="MC Boogshe">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/boogshe" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/maged-mega/ralvero-feat-mc-boogshe-party" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=MC+Boogshe" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="mcladybee" startTime="1312646400" title="MC Lady Bee">
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/djchanson/promo" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=MC+Lady+Bee" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="evlo" title="EVLO">
    <item endTime="1312628400" id="miquelet" startTime="1312624800" title="Miquelet">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/miquelettheclown" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Miquelet" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312632000" id="kosmetiq" startTime="1312628400" title="KosmetiQ">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/kosmetiq" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/kosmetiq" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Kosmetiq" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=KosmetiQ" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312637400" id="onnik" startTime="1312632000" title="Onnik">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/deejayonnik" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/onnik" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Onnik" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312644600" id="loulouplayers" startTime="1312637400" title="Loulou Players">
      <itemDescription>In 2004, Gregg aka Kolombo produced many electro house EPs under the name &#x201C;LouLou Players&#x201D;, with co-producer Djerom and vocalist Lotus, which came out on Sharam Jey&#x2019;s label, King Kong. Thanks to high sales, LouLou Players have also remixed many tracks for labels like Darren Emerson, Fatphaze, Dahlback &amp; Ekenback, John Acquaviva, Remo feat Cheleonis R Jones, &#x2026;

He carried on building on his success, and in 2005, again with Fabrice, he founded an independent electro label supported by Audiopolis Distribution. Called LouLou Records, Gregg uses the label to put out his tracks, with the artist name Kolombo, his new solo project.

Kolombo allows himself to put out a wider variety of sounds, from dark electro to minimal, while keeping his electro house feel throughout. He&#x2019;s currently signing many tracks and remixes on labels like Strobe Music, Lektroklash, Color, Blu-Fin, Jackmoves, Dirty Dancing, Kitt Ball, Surprise, Artminimal and many more.

Since September 2006, Kolombo has joined Mugwump: a project where he produced music in collaboration with Geoffroy and Compuphonic. At the same time, he is managing to create a new record label with Marc Romboy from Systematic call &#x201C;Vice versa Recordings&#x201D;.

Tags: electro, house, minimal, to listen, seen live</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Loulou+Players" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/loulou_players" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/loulou_players" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Loulou+Players" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Loulou+Players" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312651800" id="prinz" startTime="1312644600" title="Prinz">
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Prinz" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="paullomaxdreguazzelli" startTime="1312651800" title="Paul Lomax &amp; Dre Guazzelli">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/paullomaxibiza/stream" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/audioregister/following" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Paul+Lomax+%26+Dre+Guazzelli" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="bombdiggytropicalbass" title="Bomb Diggy : Tropical Bass">
    <item endTime="1312630200" id="bombdiggycrew" startTime="1312624800" title="Bomb Diggy Crew">
      <itemDescription>Imagine bright coloured airhorns honking in a rainforest, sweaty dancefloors on hot beaches, a club in the middle of the jungle in Africa, beats from different continents but with the same purpose: making the boys smile and the girls scream on the dancefloor!

It&#x2019;s okay to feel horny

Tags: tropical bass</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Bomb+Diggy+Crew" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/bomb-diggy/bomb-diggy-crew-rambazamba" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Bomb+Diggy+Crew" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312633800" id="narainashad" startTime="1312630200" title="Narain Ashad">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djnarainashad" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/dj-narain-ashad" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Narain+Ashad" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312635600" id="bombdiggycrew2" startTime="1312633800" title="Bomb Diggy Crew">
      <itemDescription>Imagine bright coloured airhorns honking in a rainforest, sweaty dancefloors on hot beaches, a club in the middle of the jungle in Africa, beats from different continents but with the same purpose: making the boys smile and the girls scream on the dancefloor!

It&#x2019;s okay to feel horny

Tags: tropical bass</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Bomb+Diggy+Crew" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/bomb-diggy/bomb-diggy-crew-rambazamba" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Bomb+Diggy+Crew" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312641000" id="hatnhoodie" startTime="1312635600" title="Hat'n Hoodie">
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/hatnhoodie" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/hatnhoodie" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Hat'n'Hoodie" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Hat%27n+Hoodie" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312642800" id="bombdiggycrew3" startTime="1312641000" title="Bomb Diggy Crew">
      <itemDescription>Imagine bright coloured airhorns honking in a rainforest, sweaty dancefloors on hot beaches, a club in the middle of the jungle in Africa, beats from different continents but with the same purpose: making the boys smile and the girls scream on the dancefloor!

It&#x2019;s okay to feel horny

Tags: tropical bass</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Bomb+Diggy+Crew" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/bomb-diggy/bomb-diggy-crew-rambazamba" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Bomb+Diggy+Crew" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312648200" id="diamondbass" startTime="1312642800" title="Diamond Bass">
      <itemDescription>Diamond Bass is Joel IIdefonso, a 28 year old Portugese artist living in Lisboa. Regularly playing in clubs around Lisboa and Porto, his production fuses House, Kuduro, Baile Funk and Dubstep. He has collaborated with J-WOW Buraka Som Sistema.
</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Diamond+Bass" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/diamond.bass" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/diamond-bass" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Diamond+Bass" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312651800" id="munchi" startTime="1312648200" title="Munchi">
      <itemDescription>Just a kid that likes to make music.

Tags: moombahton, house, breakcore, roskilde 2011, munchi</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Munchi" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/originalmunchi" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/munchi_productions" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Munchi" type="google"/>
    </item>
    <item endTime="1312657200" id="baobinga" startTime="1312651800" title="Baobinga">
      <itemDescription>A UK-based Drum &amp; Bass / Grime / Techno artist.

www.myspace.com/baobinga

Tags: breakbeat, breaks, electronic, dubstep, electronica</itemDescription>
      <itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Baobinga" type="lastfm"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/baobinga" type="myspace"/>
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/baobinga" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Baobinga" type="discogs"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Baobinga" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="radioderozepanters" title="Radio de Roze Panters">
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="featuring" startTime="1312624800" title="featuring: De Sheik, Gewoon Super, Der Pudel, Duo Penaughty, Jay Baron &amp; Maze, Nelis, Misjah, MC Pompheimer,">
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/battles/ice-cream" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=featuring%3A" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="whatishappeninghere" title="What Is Happening Here">
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="featuring2" startTime="1312624800" title="featuring: Miaw, Kroons, Robert de Hiro, Saskia Rocks, Zupa, Frenky D, Jean D'Egbert,">
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/battles/ice-cream" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=featuring%3A" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="dutchacidfamily" title="Dutch Acid Family">
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="featuring3" startTime="1312624800" title="featuring: Lady Lago, Mickey Louder, dj polo, mcManus, Mantra Flow, Dj Zen,">
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/battles/ice-cream" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=featuring%3A" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
  <line id="smirnoffcube" title="Smirnoff Cube">
    <item endTime="1312660800" id="featuring4" startTime="1312624800" title="featuring: Nachtbrakers, Guerilla Speakerz, Memphis Maniacs, Ralvero, Hitmeister D + guest, Taras van der Voorde, 3&#x2019;s A Crowd, MC Spyder,">
      <itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/battles/ice-cream" type="soundcloud"/>
      <itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=featuring%3A" type="google"/>
    </item>
  </line>
</schedule>
