<schedule id="nl.lovelandfestival.2012" title="Loveland Festival 2012" xmlns="http://gaa.st/giggity#sched"><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/google.png" id="google" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/lastfm.png" id="lastfm" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/wikipedia.png" id="wikipedia" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/myspace.png" id="myspace" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/soundcloud.png" id="soundcloud" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/discogs.png" id="discogs" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/youtube.png" id="youtube" /><line id="fire" title="Fire!"><item endTime="1344681900" id="dmzs" startTime="1344675600" title="DMZS"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=DMZS" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344687300" id="sbastienlger" startTime="1344681900" title="S&#233;bastien L&#233;ger"><itemDescription>The son of two professional musicians, for 10 years S&#233;bastien attended the academy of music learning technique and musical theory on piano and drums. Soon he began visiting record stores, where he was introduced to a new world of sounds and styles. What he liked most was what he heard from the likes of Daft Punk and other dance electronic music pioneers, and before long he stepped behind the turntables. In 1998 he started creating his own productions - house that spanned into the realms of techno while always retaining a unique element of funk- and in that same year he also published his first EPs under the alias Deaf&#8217;n&#8217;Dumb Crew. In 1999 his first album &#8216;Atomic Pop&#8217; was released. In the years since S&#233;bastien has released more than 30 tracks on many international labels, building his reputation as a key player within the new blood of talented producers. Parallel to this, and to his DJ activity, he is becoming more and more in demand for his remixing skills; working for the likes of Justin Timberlake and
Armand Van Helden, and labels including Ministry Of Sound, Defected and Intec, to name a just a few. In 2007 S&#233;bastien will launch his own record label and release the album &#8220;Planets&#8221;.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/S%C3%A9bastien+L%C3%A9ger" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/S%C3%A9bastien_L%C3%A9ger" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/sebastienleger" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/sebastienleger/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/S%C3%A9bastien+L%C3%A9ger" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344692700" id="secretcinema" startTime="1344687300" title="Secret Cinema"><itemDescription>Introduction
Jeroen Verheij aka Secret Cinema started producing as Meng Syndicate in 1990. His first record &#8216;Sonar System &#8217; came out on the Hithouse label in Belgium (ARS) and was an instant rave classic. In 1993 Michel de Hey recognized Jeroen &#8216;s excellent producing skills and convinced him to release his music on Michel &#8216;s Immaculate Music record labels. A string of tracks that shattered dance floors and charts followed under many aliases like Grooveyard, Point Blank and his most powerful identity: Secret Cinema.

In search of an identity
The first hit came within a year of signing with Immaculate Music in 1994 on Brave New World Records: The melodic rave anthem Meng &#8216;s Theme. In later years it made its way on to the &#8216;Vintage R&amp;S &#8217; compilation alongside such legends as Model 500 (Juan Atkins), Aphex Twin, Kenny Larkin and Joey Beltram. At this point Secret Cinema was born to vent Jeroen &#8216;s more refined side as a producer. The first track he released under this alias was his second international hit for &#8216;94, Timeless Altitude. It sold over 20.000 copies within six months and proved to be more timeless than anyone had expected at the time. It can be a challenge to follow up a success of this magnitude so Verheij came up with yet another identity: Grooveyard- Watch me now was the result. This energetic break beat driven track also made its way into musical history, sold ten thousands of copies and was licensed to dozens of compilations in &#8216;95. By now Verheij had become one of Holland &#8216;s most respected producers and started playing mainstage gigs
for festivals like Mysteryland and Dance Valley.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Secret+Cinema" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/secretcinemasound" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/secretcinema/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Secret+Cinema" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344697200" id="extraweltlive" startTime="1344692700" title="Extrawelt LIVE"><itemDescription>Extrawelt is the latest project from Hamburg&#8217;s Arne Schaffhausen and Wayan Raabe, otherwise known as tech-trance duo Midi Miliz.

The Extrawelt story began in 2004 with a release on the UK&#8217;s Border Community label - the doubleheader &#8216;Soopertrack&#8217; and &#8216;Zu Fuss&#8217;. Since then they have gone on to have releases on Germany&#8217;s Cocoon, Traum and Kompass labels, as well as remixes for the likes of Alexander Kowalski, H-Man and Fuzzion.

Already veterans in the field of live performance thanks to their many Midmiliz live appearances around the world, the duo also have a seriously impressive Extrawelt live show which they are currently taking on the road.

The new Extrawelt album &#8217; Sch&#246;ne Neue Extrawelt &#8217; exists of 12 new tracks and has been released on Cocoon in october 2008.


Hamburg, Germany
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Extrawelt" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/extrawelt" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/ak-tanzpaedagogik/alex-ak-tanzpaedagogik-xtrwlt" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Extrawelt" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344708000" id="svenvth" startTime="1344697200" title="Sven V&#228;th"><itemDescription>Sven V&#228;th (born 26 October 1964, Obertshausen, Germany) is a Frankfurt based DJ who has produced an extensive range of work since his career began in 1982. From 1985, he was part of the band OFF (acronym for Organization for Fun) which released the hit &#8220;Electrica Salsa&#8221; in 1986. He was also one of the founders of trance music labels Harthouse and the now-defunct Eye Q,[1] as well as being among the first DJs to play trance records. In 1995 Mixmag rated his album Accident in Paradise one of the top-50 dance albums of all time; although the title track is a fast techno piece, the rest is far more sedate, such as the track &#8220;Coda,&#8221; which features merely a flute and a harpsichord.
V&#228;th is also known as &#8220;RU Ready&#8221; and &#8220;Sam Vision&#8221;. He has been a member of the groups 16 Bit, Astral Pilot, Barbarella, the Essence of Nature, Metal Master, Metal Masters, Mosaic, and Off. Today he is the owner of the Cocoon Music Event GmbH, which contains his Label, Cocoon Recordings. He is also a shareholder of the Cocoon Club in Frankfurt.
Sven V&#228;th is mentioned in the song Hyper Hyper by German hard dance band Scooter.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Sven+V%C3%A4th" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sven_V%C3%A4th" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/svaeth" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Sven+V%C3%A4th" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344711600" id="egbertlive" startTime="1344708000" title="Egbert LIVE"><itemDescription>Egbert Van Der Gugten is currently one of the most promising talents within the field of electronic dance music. Jeroen Verheij alias Secret Cinema, whose attention was drawn to Egbert via myspace.com, invited him on the spur of the moment to his parties and his studio last year, and thus smoothed the way for Egbert to the Dutch Techno scene. After his debut on Lo-Fi Stereo, it was mainly his &#8220;Vlammen-EP&#8221; on Michel de Hey&#8217;s EC Records in February 2009, which went down a bomb on the dancefloors and belonged to the basic vinyl inventory of Sven V&#228;th&#8217;s record case in this season.

With &#8220;Vreugdevuur&#8221;, Egbert still tops this and provides Cocoon Recordings with a musical exclamation mark that sets standards in harmonic but consequently demanding TechHouse somewhere in between Dub, Progressive House and Detroit. With many high profile releases coming up in 2010, Egbert will be a name to remember!
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Egbert" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/egbertmusic" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/egbert/egbert-live-extrema-outdoor-17-07-10" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Egbert" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344718800" id="dubfire" startTime="1344711600" title="Dubfire"><itemDescription>Dubfire (aka Ali Shirazinia)&#8212;one half of the Grammy Award winning and four-time nominated electronic music duo Deep Dish&#8212;has joined forces with Global Underground for the April 10 release of his first solo mix album Dubfire GU31 &#8211; Taipei. The 2-CD mix set is a sweeping change from anything you would have previously expected to hear from the Deep Dish member and it features the finest in house, electro, techno, and even industrial music.

Growing up in the Washington, DC area, Dubfire spent much of his youth playing the guitar in school bands and listening to heavy doses of classic Hip-Hop, jazz/rare groove, dub reggae, new wave and industrial. Dubfire was also influenced by the local punk scene and the music of hometown bands like Fugazi and Minor Threat. Members of these bands also worked at a local record store called Yesterday And Today Records, and this is where Dubfire first picked up on the sounds of acts such as Kraftwerk, Ministry, Jesus &amp; Mary Chain, Depeche Mode, Nitzer Ebb, Adrian Sherwood/On-U Sound and Einsturzende Neubauten. Through this heavy industrial influence, namely the sound of Chicago&#8217;s famed Wax Trax! label, Dubfire discovered the Chicago house scene and what labels like Trax and D.J. International Records were releasing.

Dubfire&#8217;s eclectic new mix is the product of his diverse past and addictive music personality, and this mix is more about Dubfire personally and as a DJ. Dubfire&#8217;s mix was compiled with tracks that he&#8217;s both really into at the moment and that have also had a profound influence on shaping his love for music.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Dubfire" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dubfire" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djdubfire" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/edmtunestv/dubfire-essential-mix-26-05-2012" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Dubfire" type="discogs" /></item></line><line id="rise" title="Rise"><item endTime="1344682800" id="juansanchez" startTime="1344675600" title="Juan Sanchez"><itemDescription>Juan Sanchez is one of the most promising artists within the international electronic music scene. His track selection of sophisticated house and tasty techno is an excellent blend of emotion, energy and rhythm coated in nasty jacking grooves. It is this refined musical vision, an endless string of (inter)national bookings and red hot productions and remixes that made him one of 2009&#8217;s most sought after artists of the past few years, and a definite DJ of choice for many promotors in years to come. Juan has shared prestigious peak time spots with the likes of Derrick May, Josh Wink, Gregor Tresher, Funk D&#8217;Void, Guido Schneider and &#194;me on a variety of national and international stages. And that&#8217;s just the tip of the iceberg: Other highlights include sought-after residencies at Holland&#8217;s popular Rekorder and Rockit events as well as countless gigs in Spain (including Barcelona&#8217;s The Loft venue and the highly anticipated Sonar festival), Ibiza (Blue Marlin), Germany and France. This May even sees Juan crossing
the pond for a 10-day Brazil tour (!) including several gigs in Sao Paulo!

Juan, who hails from a Spanish-Dutch family, began his musical career at the early age of eight, when he fell in love with the guitar. He honed his musical skills by playing in various bands, thereby continuously expanding his musical vision and transcending the boundaries of rock.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Juan+Sanchez" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/juansanchezzz" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/juan-sanchez" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Juan+Sanchez" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344690000" id="dimitrikneppers" startTime="1344682800" title="Dimitri Kneppers"><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/dimitrifromamsterdam/photos/6210321" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/dimitri-2/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Dimitri+Kneppers" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344693600" id="arilbrikhalive" startTime="1344690000" title="Aril Brikha LIVE"><itemDescription>Aril Brikha (born in 1976 in Tehran, Iran) is a producer currently residing in Stockholm, Sweden, who initially discovered electronic music by listening to the likes of Depeche Mode, Front 242 and Jean Michel Jarre before discovering the more futuristic sounds of artists like Detroit&#8217;s Robert Hood and Underground Resistance.

After not receiving any response in his native country he sent a demo to some of his favourite record labels stateside. Before he knew it, Derrick May released The Art Of Vengeance EP, featuring the track &#8220;Groove La&#8217; Chord&#8221;, on his Fragile record label in 1998, and was playing it all around the world. This was followed by the release of the Deeparture In Time album also on Transmat.

His live sets have been highly appreciated all the way from DEMF in Detroit to Fabric in London, with his take on Detroit Techno adding special soul and funk to it.

In 1998 Aril Brikha reacquainted the world with deep techno soul, as his record Groove La Chord crossed generic boundaries. Is it techno? Is it house? Is it deep house? It&#8217;s everything and nothing. Groove La Chord is simply timeless. No one was more surprised about the success of Groove La Chord than Brikha himself - after all, he&#8217;d originally presented it on his demo as a potential B-side. Two years after he recorded Groove La Chord, Brikha heard it in a club for the first time - Derrick May pulled it out in Chicago. Aril then realised it was a good track. The renegade always walks alone. As a cultural exile in Sweden, Aril Brikha has never been one to conform.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Aril+Brikha" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/arilbrikha" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/roberlage/aril-brikha-live-at-fuse-in-festival" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Aril+Brikha" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344700800" id="sasha" startTime="1344693600" title="Sasha"><itemDescription>There are currently several artists using the name Sasha:

1) Sasha, born Alexander Coe (born September 4, 1969), is a Welsh DJ and record producer. He is best known for partnering with English DJ, John Digweed, as Sasha + Digweed. The pair released several mix albums together, including the Northern Exposure series (released between 1996 and 2001). They also released one of the all time best selling mix albums, The Renaissance Mix Collection part 1, in 1994. The album was recently re-issued. Sasha also released two Global Underground solo mix CDs, San Francisco (GU009) and Ibiza (GU013), which are considered classics of the progressive house genre.

In 2002 he released his first solo LP, Airdrawndagger, a result of collaboration with Charlie May and Junkie XL, the album also featured a guest appearance from James Holden. The album enjoyed excellent reviews upon its release, and recently a wave of quality remixes by various producers has re-kindled interest in Sasha&#8217;s production work. 2004 saw the release of Involver, his third in the Global Underground series. This mix album differed from previous albums in that each track was completely reproduced in the studio, as opposed to simply being blended together.

More recently, in 2005, Sasha began moving away from mixing with records and CDs in favor of a new approach with computer software and a dedicated controller for his live sets.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Sasha" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sasha_(DJ)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djsasha" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Sasha" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344706200" id="mayajanecoles" startTime="1344700800" title="Maya Jane Coles"><itemDescription>Maya Jane Coles (aka Nocturnal Sunshine), is a London, UK tech house / deep house / techno producer / DJ / musician / songwriter. She d&#233;buted with the single &#8220;Sick Panda&#8221; (2008, Dogmatik Records) and her latest is the EP &#8220;Focus Now&#8221; (May 2011, 20:20 Vision).

2010 has certainly been the year that 23 year old Maya Jane Coles announced herself as one of the most talented up and coming artists in electronic music.

In the years preceding a steady output of techy cuts on labels such as Dogmatik and 1trax simmered away catching the attention of cluded up heads and savy A&amp;R people alike. It was her debut EP on Franck Roger&#8217;s Real Tone though that ignited the fire of hype and boosted her profile on the global stage receiving heavy support from the house &amp; techno elite. Aside from being hammered repeatedly on the worlds most happening dance floors &#8216;What They Say&#8217; reached the number 1 spot on across the board; Beatport Deep House Chart No. 1, Tarxsource top download &amp; Resident Advisors most charted tracks for October. It&#8217;s safe to say the release won the hearts and heads of fans and critics a like and a landmark year was topped off with a nomination for Best Breakthrough Producer nomination in the DJ Mag Best of British awards.

Not one to fall victim to the pitfalls of being one of the scenes &#8216;buzz names&#8217;, Maya has built on her flourishing reputation with a slew of gigs across Europe holding her own alongside world renounced DJs.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Maya+Jane+Coles" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maya_Jane_Coles" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/mayajanecoles" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/mayajanecoles" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Maya+Jane+Coles" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344711600" id="guiborattolive" startTime="1344706200" title="Gui Boratto LIVE"><itemDescription>Born in 1974 in S&#227;o Paulo Brazil,Gui Boratto - architect, musician, composer and producer - began his career in the advertising sector in 1993. From 1994 until 2004 his work appeared on both national and international record labels, including EMI, Virgin, Irma, BMG, Edel, Vidisco, and ZYX. Over these 10 years he worked with artists such as Pato Banton, Garth Brooks, Steel Pulse, Desiree, Manu Chao, Gal Costa, Chico Buarque, Fernanda Porto, Kaleidosc&#243;pio, Leila Pinheiro, and many others.

Boratto handles A&amp;R for the Brazilian independent label, Megamusic (distributed by Trama); he is also one of the label&#8217;s owners, along with his brother Tchorta.

In 2005 he began to dedicate himself to his own productions and compositions, displaying a more personal side to the public. With releases on a number of respected European labels, such as Plastic City, Circle, Kompakt, and Audiomatique, Boratto has managed to appear in the charts and on the playlists of Michael Mayer, Tiefschwarz, Steve Bug, Phonique, Martin Landsky, Hernan Cattaneo, among others.

With respect for his talent growing in the world scene, Gui Boratto is a name to look out for on the Brazilian house, techno and minimal scene.

DISCOGRAPHY
1994 - Sect - &#8220;F&amp;D&#8221; (Don&#8217;t Stop)
1995 - Sect - &#8220;Eleven&#8221; (Spotlight Records)
1997 - Sect - &#8220;The Remixes&#8221; (Spotlight Records)
2001 - Crossover - &#8220;Music Will Never Stop&#8221; (Tanga Records)
2002 - Crossover - &#8220;Lay It Down on Me&#8221; (Tanga Records)
2003 - Gui Boratto - &#8220;Royal House&#8221; (Megamusic/Trama)
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Gui+Boratto" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/guiboratto" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/nightclubber-ro/gui-boratto-live-tsugi-podcast" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Gui+Boratto" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344718800" id="cassyb2bdannyhowells" startTime="1344711600" title="Cassy B2B Danny Howells"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Cassy+B2B+Danny+Howells" type="google" /></item></line><line id="underground" title="Underground"><item endTime="1344682800" id="olivierweiter" startTime="1344675600" title="Olivier Weiter"><itemDescription>At the age of 19, Roel Varkevisser, also known as Olivier Weiter, bought his first DJ-equipment. Inspired by the Dutch DJ-duo: Ille Bitch &amp; De Man Zonder Schaduw and Sven V&#228;th, Olivier developed himself as a DJ, who stands for warm mood-uplifting electronic music. Emotion and melody are the keywords in his DJ-sets, often filled with huge climaxes and lots of craziness. Not only DJ-ing, but also producing became his passion. With his new set-up, his first release only will be a matter of time. He is also one of the founders of Bar27, a new collective who are upcoming in Amsterdam. 21 year &#8220;old&#8221; Olivier is still at the beginning of his career, yet has already played at some well-respected parties and clubs, national but also international (Bar25 Berlin, Miro Club Bolzano) With his eccentric taste of music and his ability to entertain the crowd , Olivier is definitely ready for the big adventure! For bookings please contact: booking@wearee.nl For more info: info@wearee.nl
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Olivier+Weiter" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/olivier-weiter" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Olivier+Weiter" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344686400" id="lenimaldjcontestwinner" startTime="1344682800" title="LENIMAL - DJ Contest Winner"><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/natte-verf/lenimal-pioneer-loveland-dj" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=LENIMAL+-+DJ+Contest+Winner" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344690000" id="arjunaschikslive" startTime="1344686400" title="Arjuna Schiks LIVE"><itemDescription>Arjuna (1985) was born and raised in Amsterdam and has been composing and producing ever since he turned fifteen. Throughout the years he made hundreds of tracks. His style varies between ambient, tech- house, electro and electronically produced modern classical music. His sound is characterized by a very melodic and mainly warm electronic vibe.
From 2006 Arjuna started performing live. Since 2006 he has been performing live at dj caf&#233; Twstd and later The Getaway in Amsterdam. He has already been performing in all important Dutch clubs like: Studio80, Sugar Factory, Odeon, Westerliefde, Winkel van Sinkel and many more.

Arjuna composed and produced music for the Diesel fall/winter fashion show during the Amsterdam Fashion week 2007 and the Midzomer Zaan festival where his music was played by deejay Isis alongside pieces performed by and with violist player Janine Jansen and the Wouter Hamel band. His music has been well received by deejays and crowd amongst them is: deejay Dimitri. Arjuna performed live at Mysteryland festival twice, FFWD Parade Rotterdam, Amsterdam Dance Event and many other major dance events.
He ran up for the finals of &#8220;Grote Prijs Van Nederland&#8221; (one of the biggest producers contests in the Netherlands). Also Arjuna is working in the studio at several co productions with Isis a.k.a. dj 100 % Isis, dj Dimitri and many others.

His first record release &#8220;Konijntje&#8221;, was a collaboration with Willie Wartaal from &#8220;De Jeugd van Tegenwoordig&#8221; under the alias AKA The Junkies. It and went straight into the charts, reaching high into the Top 10 in Holland and Belgium.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Arjuna+Schiks" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/arjunaschiks/arjuna-schiks-live-queensday" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Arjuna+Schiks" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344695400" id="martinbuttrichlive" startTime="1344690000" title="Martin Buttrich LIVE"><itemDescription>You&#8217;ll know Martin Buttrich from his production work for Timo Maas and Loco Dice however he is now becoming known as an artist in his own right with &#8216;Full Clip&#8217; on Carl Craig&#8217;s Planet E label.

Returning home to Four:Twenty Recordings &#8216;Well Done&#8217; is deep and beautiful as the majority of Martins work is and to compliment Serafin (cadenza/mountainpeople) has remixed with awesome effect. The original is hypnotic, full of minimal sexy tones, deep pulsating bass and quirky grooves whilst the original is an epic journey of two halves, techno fuelled dry drum minimal fusing into an uplifting beautiful chord progression.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Martin+Buttrich" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/martinbuttrich" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/medellinstyle/martinbuttrichlive" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Martin+Buttrich" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344700800" id="butch" startTime="1344695400" title="Butch"><itemDescription>There are more artists using this name:

1) Butch is a DJ, producer and remixer. As soon as he steps behind the decks or into his studio his only ambition is to find the perfect sound which transforms the dancefloor into an ecstatic crowd. His unique productions and remixes transcends between Neo-Trance, Techno and Minimal and are defined through their high quality sound productions and the trademark sounds, which have enabled him to release productions on renowned labels such as Great Stuff, Craft Music, BluFin and Stil vor Talent (Oliver Koletzki&#8217;s label).

His first production for Craft Music, an impulsive remix for Whebba&#8217;s production &#8220;Mary&#8217;s Army&#8221; found world-wide recognition with Key-DJs and fans of electronic music. Shortly afterwards his first own single followed for Tomcraft&#8217;s label entitled &#8220;Life is Deadly&#8221;. This production found support with DJ greats such as Deep Dish, John Acquaviva, Benny Benassi and Oliver Koletzki.

Already mastered is his follow-up for Great Stuff called &#8220;On the Line&#8221; which boasts remixes by Oxia, Pig &amp; Dan and Swen Weber, which presumably will be released in September 2007. His newest project is a remix for probably one of the most wanted producers of minimal-techno at the moment. Stay tuned&#8230;

Source: http://www.myspace.com/cometobutch

2) Butch, romanian hip hop / hardcore artist, member of Dagga. http://www.myspace.com/fiulrisipitor

3) Butch is also the name of an Asheville singer/songwriter

4) Butch is a Japanese disco/punk band on Imomushi Records.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Butch" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/cometobutch" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Butch" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Butch" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344708000" id="solomun" startTime="1344700800" title="Solomun"><itemDescription>Mladen Solomun is hosting the club &#8220;DIY&#8221; at the RO.DIY Cultural Club since 2004 and a monthly club in the Uebel &amp; Gef&#228;hrlich.

Mladen&#8217;s musical passion concentrates in his own label Diynamic Music. The first five EP Releases presented a very successfull start and cought the attention of many artists and DJs like Laurent Garnier, Tiger Stripes, Gabriel Ananda, DJ T., Tobi Neumann, Martin Landsky, Jennifer Cardini, Anja Schneider, Prins Thomas and Fabrice Lig who layed and charted the tracks in their playlists.

Solomun is going to release tracks on the labels Liebe*Detail, MOTT, Sonar Kollektiv, Four:Twenty Recordings, Dessous, etc. 2012 saw him mix Watergate11 in the prestigious comp CD series so it&#8217;ll be curious what else Solomun will do this year&#8230;
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Solomun" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/solomun/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Solomun" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Solomun" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344715200" id="maceoplex" startTime="1344708000" title="Maceo Plex"><itemDescription>Located deep within the circuitry of a mechanical alien host known as Maetrik you will find a complex web of synaptic dispersements resembling what could be called a soul. And this soul which drives it&#8217;s host and manipulates it&#8217;s every move is finally beginning to emerge. Its name is Maceo Plex. The emergence of such an entity has been the result of a need for feeling, a need for interplanetary funk. We as humans consider this need a feeling, a feeling rooted in emotion, and emotion being the very basis of humanity.

Maceo Plex is on a quest to fullfil his need to inject feeling and funk into the world, and he&#8217;s already proving to be quite productive. With deep and funky works of audible engineering for the label Crosstown Rebels in the form of a full length album titled &#8220;Life Index&#8221;, a night with Maceo Plex will be one of galactic proportions.

To explain the evolutionary process behind Maceo&#8217;s existance we must travel back to 1993, to the beginning of his creativity. At the start&#8230;Maceo was intrigued by a pair of circular shaped objects designed for holding discs created from vinyl that produced vibrations resulting in sound and music. Soon he began conjuring up mixxes of techno, electro, and house music that quickly gained him popularity within the early 90s rave culture. But in 1997, while Heavily influenced by the sounds of other modern funk theorists such as Model 500, Kenny Larkin, Idjut Boyz, Convextion, etc&#8230;
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Maceo+Plex" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/maetrikmusic" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/maceoplex/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Maceo+Plex" type="discogs" /></item></line><line id="tdansant" title="T-Dansant"><item endTime="1344682800" id="tomnovy" startTime="1344675600" title="Tom Novy"><itemDescription>Tom Novy aka Thomas Reichold, born in 1970, is a German house DJ and producer. Tom Novy was the first German DJ who mixed the british compilation &#8220;Ministry of Sound Annual&#8221;. He also did remixes for Sonique, Lou Bega, Tom Jones &amp; Mousse T., Backstreet Boys and Snap!.

Beyond doubt, Tom Novy belongs to an elect circlet of exceptional artists in the music scene whose name doesn&#8217;t need any explanation. Worldwide chart successes and appearances in the world&#8217;s best clubs seam his career.

His international breakthrough came along in 1996 with his single &#8220;Superstar&#8221;, which rose up to position 15 in Germany and made it into the top positions in 18 other countries.

In 1998, his single &#8220;I Rock&#8221; not only became a chart-breaker, but a downright House anthem.

As said, Tom Novy also was the first ever German DJ to be granted the honour to mix the &#8220;Ministry of Sound Annual Compilation&#8221;. The compilation took the German as well as the British charts by assault. His single &#8220;Pumpin&#8221; also made it onto position #19 in the UK Charts in 2000. Later he produced remixes for Sonique &#8220;&#9679;I Put A Spell On You&#8221;, Lou Bega &#8220;mambo #5&#8221;, Tom Jones and Mousse T. &#8220;Sexbomb&#8221;, Backstreet Boys &#8220;&#9679;The Call&#8221;, Snap! &#8220;Eternity&#8221;, just to name a few.

His singles &#8220;Your Body&#8221; &amp; &#8220;Lovin U&#8221; in 2004 caused a worldwide sensation, similar to South Africa, where Tom conquered the Top 10. Tom Novy had two shows in German television: &#8220;MTV Dance Floor Charts&#8221;, the one and only dance music show on German television, and &#8220;MTV Streetlife&#8221;.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Tom+Novy" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tom_Novy" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/tomnovy" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/tomnovy" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Tom+Novy" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344690000" id="roog" startTime="1344682800" title="Roog"><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/rooghardsoul" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/roogvanbueren" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/DJ+Roog" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344697200" id="funkerman" startTime="1344690000" title="Funkerman"><itemDescription>http://www.facebook.com/funkerman
http://www.youtube.com/funkermantube/

Funkerman, known to his postman as Ardie van Beek, (born 1975, Breda, The Netherlands), is a well known DJ/producer and founder of Flamingo Recordings.

From his first love of pioneering US hip hop, through obsessive crate digging for classic soul, Disco and Funk, to riding on the first waves of US house; he has always been on a quest to find, make and play new and exciting music.

Whilst spinning at the Spock club in Breda in the mid nineties he was also starting to produce and promote music, while working in local record store, Magik. Being surrounded by the records he loved gave him an insight to the dance music industry as well as keen sense of how music moved people, and he quickly became a A&amp;R manager; working at the heart of the burgeoning Dutch scene.

Through years of hard work DJ-ing and producing, Funkerman established himself internationally, and by 2004 he decided it was time to capitalise on his success, so he founded Flamingo Recordings, with fellow producer Raf and DJ/producer Fedde le Grand.

In the six years since, the label has gone from strength to strength, releasing some of the biggest house tracks of recent times, like Funkerman&#8217;s &#8216;Speed Up&#8217; , Ida Corr&#8217;s &#8216;Let me think about it&#8217;, Fedde le Grand&#8217;s &#8216;Put Your Hands Up For Detroit&#8217; and their collaboration on &#8216;3 Minutes To Explain&#8217;.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Funkerman" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Funkerman" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djfunkerman" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/funkerman" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Funkerman" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344704400" id="theshapeshifters" startTime="1344697200" title="The Shapeshifters"><itemDescription>There is more than one artist with the name Shapeshifters:

1) A British house music group consisting of producers Simon Marlin and Max Reich, featuring female vocalist Cookie. They first became popular in 2004 with their debut single &#8220;&#9679;Lola&#8217;s theme&#8221;. After several months on various high profile DJ playlists, the song was picked up by Positiva Records and topped the UK Charts and became a Top 10 hit across Europe. The following year they released &#8220;&#9679;Back To Basics&#8221;, a Top 10 hit in the United Kingdom. In March 2006 they released their debut LP &#8220;Sound Advice&#8221;, along with a third successful single titled &#8220;&#9679;Incredible&#8221;. Marlin and Reich use the name Shape:UK for releases in the United States due to a name conflict with LA hip hop group The Shape Shifters.

2) The Los Angeles based underground collective of hip hop artists, found under the name The Shape Shifters.

3) The Shapeshifter is also an electronica act from New Zealand.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/The+Shapeshifters" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shapeshifters_(music_act)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/theshapeshifters" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/theshapeshifters" type="soundcloud" /></item><item endTime="1344711600" id="sanderkleinenberg" startTime="1344704400" title="Sander Kleinenberg"><itemDescription>Sander Kleinenberg is a Dutch DJ and producer. Born in Delft in 1971, he started DJing in his early teens playing at local bars. After getting his start in production in 1996, some of the biggest DJs in the world, including Sasha, Deep Dish, and Max Graham have used his tracks on their mix compilations. &#8220;&#9679;My Lexicon&#8221; and &#8220;Sacred&#8221; are examples of his trancier production work, while &#8220;&#9679;The Fruit&#8221; and &#8220;Work To Do&#8221; are examples of a more funk-tinged house. His most recent compilations fall under the &#8220;Everybody&#8221; moniker, and reflect the style of DJing that he is playing out at the time. &#8220;&#9679;My Lexicon&#8221; was a favorite of famed DJ Sasha in the late 1990&#8217;s.

Sander&#8217;s star is currently on the rise, with him currently holding down monthly or seasonal residencies at the world&#8217;s top venues, including Space in Miami, the former Crobar in New York City and many others. His remixing career has also recently caught the attention of pop-star Justin Timberlake, who has commissioned Sander to do club remix and production work on some of his more popular tracks and the song &#9679;Rock Your Body.

Kleinenberg also has a record label, known as Little Mountain Recordings.

Sander Kleinenberg remixed Janet Jackson&#8217;s &#9679;All Nite (Don&#8217;t Stop) in 2004.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Sander+Kleinenberg" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sander_Kleinenberg" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/sanderkleinenberg" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/kleinenberg" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Sander+Kleinenberg" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344718800" id="feddelegrand" startTime="1344711600" title="Fedde le Grand"><itemDescription>Fedde le Grand stands on the edge of global superstardom. Behind him lies a glittering career that includes worldwide number ones, packed arenas, throbbing dance floors, A-list collaborations and a raft of international awards. Just ahead &#8211; his first studio album called &#8216;Output&#8217;, setting the pace for what is already shaping up to be a fast track 2009.

It could be said that Fedde came out of nowhere, riding off the success of a hit record. Well, let&#8217;s set that record straight &#8211; you couldn&#8217;t get further away from the truth. The truth is that his parties had been rocking the Netherlands since 2001 when he started to spin at the Danssalon in Eindhoven, one of Holland&#8217;s finest clubs at those days, on Sundays for more than two years; Sneakerz is his own club night; his label Flamingo Recordings has been pushing its unique sound since 2004; and then in 2006 Put your hands up for Detroit happened.

In fact &#8216;happened&#8217; doesn&#8217;t do what occurred justice &#8211; quite simply, it exploded. The track hit No 1 in the UK, Spain, Russia, Finland and Bulgaria; won Best Underground House Track and Best Breaks/Electro Track at the IMDA 2007, Club Banger Of The Year at the 6th Annual Club Awards in Miami 2008 and secured Fedde the fiercely fought over Best Breakthrough Solo Artist gong at the IMDA 2007.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Fedde+le+Grand" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fedde_le_Grand" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djfeddelegrand" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/feddelegrand" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Fedde+Le+Grand" type="discogs" /></item></line><line id="house" title="House"><item endTime="1344686400" id="gregorsalto" startTime="1344675600" title="Gregor Salto"><itemDescription>Gregor started playing classical piano as a small kid.
He got fascinated by the new House sound after hearing the record &#8216;Royal House &#8211; Can you party&#8221; and around the age of fourteen he started making electronic music on his dad&#8217;s Commodore Amiga. Together with his childhood friend dj Ernst he won a talent prize at their high school (In Aeternum award. Stedelijk Gymnasium, Haarlem ) and with the money from the award + some loans they bought their first gear. From that moment they spent every free minute in their small home studio, while fantasizing about hearing their on music in a club.

Gregor&#8217;s first record was released in 1994 on Outland Records in Amsterdam and many more followed. From that very start Gregor mixed his favorite musical styles Soul, Latin, Afro and Jazz with his own music.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Gregor+Salto" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/djgregorsalto" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/gregorsalto" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Gregor+Salto" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344691800" id="shermanology" startTime="1344686400" title="Shermanology"><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/shermanologymusic" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/shermanology" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Shermanology" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344697200" id="bennyrodrigues" startTime="1344691800" title="Benny Rodrigues"><itemDescription>Benny Rodrigues has infiltrated himself in the list of famous Dutch top DJs in a very short time. This Rotterdam born and raised talent with Portuguese blood understands the art of using the funk, of getting the dancing floor full and the room to its feet. Although confessed because of its groovy/funky (deep) tech-house sound with lots of detroit, minimal and acid influences , he also knows that he has to do some work now and then and he knows how he must use that hatchet, what results in a particularly strong and delightful portion of techno which remains above everything well digestible.

Meanwhile he has turn tabled at all the major and important clubs and festivals in the Netherlands.
On the international base he has showcased his skills around the rest of the world (Opium Garden Miami, Hao Man 17 Jerusalem, Resident-dj for Chris Liebing&#8217;s Spinclub night @ Space Ibiza &amp; Privelege, Ibiza, Antwerp where he held a 3 year saturday night-residency at the famous Belgium superclub: Cafe d&#8217; Anvers + the annual Detroit&#8217;s Electronic Music Festival (Movement/Fuse-in) where he is a gladly seen guest being invited twice (2005/2006) by the legends of techno: Derrick May &amp; Kevin Saunderson).

Besides his huge (mainly dutch) amount of dj-gigs, Benny&#8217;s main focus nowadays is to produce music wich reflects his tipycal edge sound, so the rest of the world will get to know and experience where Benny Rodrigues musically stands for. With releases scheduled on Darren Emerson&#8217;s (ex-Underworld) Underwater Records and other very interesting upcoming projects he&#8217;s setting himself quite a good step in the right direction!
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Benny+Rodrigues" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/bennyrodrigues" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/bennyrodrigues" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Benny+Rodrigues" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344704400" id="umek" startTime="1344697200" title="Umek"><itemDescription>For a long time, Slovenia has been known for its great electronic parties, but as the local scene is of boutique dimensions, everyone who wishes to take the art of mixing and producing to a professional level, has to go out there and enter the worldwide scene. UMEK has done this step as early as in the middle of the 90s and so he became one of the most important techno players of the global techno scene, even before the end of the last millennium.

In the beginning of the year 2007, UMEK started a new 1605 Music Therapy - Sixteenofive, with which he marked the beginning of the second era of his music creation and what an era it is! After 5 years the label is tagged as a great success and is one of the world&#8217;s fastest growing techno labels, which spawns releases and new talents almost every week.
UMEK pocketed quite a few achievements over the last two years. In the beginning of 2011 an interesting documentary &#8220;Techno heavy-weights UMEK &amp; Carl Cox in back to back interview&#8221; was released and was aplauded by UMEK&#8217;s audience and shared tremendously over the internet and social networks. In February, UMEK was again nominated on the Beatport Music Awards, this time as a best artist overall, along with the likes of David Guetta, Deadmau5, Mark Knight. He won by staff pick and is 2011&#8217;s Beatport&#8217;s Best artist. At that time he also started his own weekly radio show, wittily titled &#8220;Behind The Iron Curtain with UMEK&#8221;, which was instantly favourited among the millions of listeners across the globe.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Umek" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DJ_Umek" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/umek" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Umek" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344709800" id="bingoplayers" startTime="1344704400" title="Bingo Players"><itemDescription>Bingo Players (Paul B&#228;umer &amp; Maarten Hoogstraten) have been left gasping for air after a seriously hectic year with bookings in the Netherlands and abroad. Outgrowing local bingo halls to play with the big ballers of the game has been the result of their hard work and devotion. The Bingo Players appear to have been made for each other, the proof of which came in November 2009, when the DJ/producer duo topped the Beatport overall chart for a second time with their remake of the dance floor classic, &#8220;Devotion&#8221;, which stayed on no. 1 for two weeks and over a month in the top 10!

Back in 2008 the Bingo Players were still experiencing the extensive aftermath of their UHM &amp; Tony Flexx &#8211; &#8220;Our House&#8221; remix. The cooperation with Chocolate Puma on the legendary label Strictly Rhythm/Defected, &#8220;Touch Me&#8221; was released and gained support all over. If that wasn&#8217;t enough, it also hit Beatport&#8217;s chart number one position! &#8220;Touch Me&#8221; then appeared on various compilations, like Defected In The House and Sensation White.

After that, Dutch house mogul, ErickE&#8217;s &#8220;Wanna Go Again&#8221;, was treated with the inner Bingo and this remix hit the Dance Tunes top position and was inserted in the CD machines of Noir, Sander van Doorn and Patric La Funk amongst others. In September 2008 &#8220;Get Up&#8221; hit the shelves following a huge buzz and support from Laidback Luke, A Trak, Crookers and made it onto the 2008 I LOVE TECHNO! compilation, mixed by Boys Noize.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Bingo+Players" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bingo_Players" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/bingoplayers/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Bingo+Players" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344717000" id="roncarroll" startTime="1344709800" title="Ron Carroll"><itemDescription>Ron Carroll is an American singer, songwriter and producer. He is primarily known in the house music circuit. Carroll has worked with many of house&#8217;s most famous producers, including E-Smoove, Maurice Joshua and Bob Sinclar. He has also produced, usually with partner Spero Pagos, for other vocalists or his own songs.
A few of his tracks have gained mainstream attention and radio airplay, including &#8220;My Love&#8221; (produced by Kluster), &#8220;Lucky Star&#8221; (produced by Superfunk), &#8220;The Sermon&#8221; (produced by Carroll himself) and Back Together (produced by Hardsoul).

Ron Carroll&#8217;s nickname is The Minister of Sound.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Ron+Carroll" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/roncarroll" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Ron+Carroll" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Ron+Carroll" type="google" /></item></line><line id="nest" title="Nest"><item endTime="1344686400" id="sanproper" startTime="1344675600" title="San Proper"><itemDescription>San Proper is a well respected DJ from the Amsterdam underground club scene. Over the last ten years, he has been spinning in all the major clubs, bars and lounges, in and around Holland. You&#8217;ll hear him play at most of the major Summer and Dance festivals (San has a residency at Europe&#8217;s top Summer festival, Lowlands) as well as the more dodgy and underground locations. He&#8217;s very known and praised for his House &amp; Disco sets, but also for blending a lot of different styles into an eclectic mix, which results in him playing at various spots. In Amsterdam, San proudly presents &#8220;The Black Disco Bust&#8221; - a club night that, throughout the years, has won a cult status with some international DJs being featured (p.e. Daniel Wang, Alton Miller, Kalabrese, Trus&#8217;me). The Disco Bust is all about preserving the true sound of old school underground Disco music. In 1998, together with Alan Luna who, like San, is a resident at the Supper Club, he founded &#8220;Choque&#8221; -a club night about the deeper and warmer sound of quality
House music. He&#8217;s been organising these programs at top Amsterdam clubs like Mazzo, Bitterzoet, Club 11, Sugar Factory and more.
San Proper started out as a guitar player. He played with several bands in the live circuit where he gained a lot of experience in music. In &#8217;95 he founded &#8220;The Mindmenders&#8221;, a Funk/Hip hop band, which eventually won &#8216;De Grote prijs van Nederland&#8217; in &#8217;99, the country&#8217;s leading annual talent show for upcoming artists.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/San+Proper" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/sanproper" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/san-proper" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/San+Proper" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344693600" id="tomtrago" startTime="1344686400" title="Tom Trago"><itemDescription>Tom Trago (born 1983, Amsterdam) has been operating at the forefront of electronic music for the past ten years. Started playing records as a local Amsterdam DJ - and soon abroad - holding down residencies and making underground radio to promote new music, he quickly moved to producing his own sound. Now one of Rushhours prominent producers, Trago debuted in 2006 with his first single Live with the BBQ, which rapidly gained cult status.

Since then he has been remixing various artists such as Franz Ferdinand, Laidback Luke and Philippe Zdar. Other remixes have been released on record labels like Kindred Spirits, Magnetron, Philpot and Rushhour. In addition, his music has been remixed by Aardvarck, Actress and Motor City Drum Ensemble amongst many others.

In 2009 Trago released Voyage Direct, an 8-track EP which envisions his philosophy on Disco and House music. In that same year he was invited to conduct with the Kindred Spirits Ensemble during Amsterdam Dance Event. The Voyage Direct series is now a sublabel of Rushhour, releasing records by Awanto 3, Dexter and Legowelt.
In order to create and share music with like-minded producers, Trago initiated 08Bar, a music platform founded in 2005 to stimulate talent and promote new productions. Collaborations such as Alfabet and Yuro Trago grew from there and now Trago produces several artists locally as well as internationally. Together with Parra he released two edit compilations: Edith Niaf and The Von Small Hausen edits.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Tom+Trago" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/tomtrago" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/tomtrago/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Tom+Trago" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344699000" id="melon" startTime="1344693600" title="Melon"><itemDescription>There are 4 or more artists use this name.


*Jeroen Hofer, a DJ from Amsterdam who owns the ratio?music label.
&#8212;&#8212;-
*Melon was founded by David Doyen and Shawn Pratzner in 2003 in Wilmington, Delaware originally operating as the homemade recording project &#8220;Throat Wobbler Mangrove and the Post Nasal Drips&#8221; an eclectic mix of esoteric lo-fi goofy weirdness that eventually evolved into the more rock oriented project &#8220;Melon&#8221;.

In 2005, they recruited drummer Ernest Goldner and bassist Chris Haug (Giant Bags of Weed, Take Down Your Art)and eventually started writing songs as a collective unit. Since that time they have recorded two Eps in 2007 &#8220;Drink of the Gods&#8221; and &#8220;Mirage&#8221;.
Melon has been described as a refreshing, exciting blend of stoner rock, psychedelic frequencies, noise and grunge that is all topped off with a weird set of quirks that makes it impossible to truly pigeonhole these guys into any exact corner.
&#8212;&#8212;-
*Japanese pop unit founded by Toshi and Chica(former members of Plastics).
Their unfixed sessions of begging bore Water Melon Group(their side unit) and Mute Beat.
&#8212;&#8212;-
*Melon, a Mexican singer who recorded tropical and salsa music from the late 1960&#8217;s through the 1980&#8217;s both as a solo artist and together with in duo with his musical partner Lobo.
&#8212;&#8212;-
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Melon" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/melonproductions" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Melon" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344704400" id="miguelcampbell" startTime="1344699000" title="Miguel Campbell"><itemDescription>Miguel has been galvanised by the house music scene since the early 90&#8217;s and has also been a DJ since that time. Miguel began producing his own music as one &#8216;half&#8217; of the underground duo HCB.

In 2006 he founded Outcross Records and also began to release music under his own name.

Miguels goals are to work hard to develop Outcross, help in the development of new and experienced artists and to continue with his own productions.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Miguel+Campbell" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/miguelcampbell" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/gouranga/miguel-campbell-ibiza-voice" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Miguel+Campbell" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1344709800" id="lovebirds" startTime="1344704400" title="Lovebirds"><itemDescription>Lovebirds is the solo project of Hamburg resident Sebastian &#8216;Basti&#8217; Doering. Following 3 excellent singles on the much-respected Winding Road Records label, Lovebirds is big news right now. Labels such as Freerange and Buzzin Fly are hot on his heels, eager to sign his tracks.

The first Lovebirds release appeared on Trax of Interest in . In 2006, having built up a repertoire of unsigned material, he sent a CD to John Buckby, label owner of Winding Road Records and a mutual friend of Vincenzo.

The Lovebirds sound is like a blast from the past with house steroids packing serious production muscle. Listening to Lovebirds is like taking trip back to the 70s and 80s - but riding in a gleaming futuristic spaceship.

The first Lovebirds single on Winding Road was the &#8216;Modern Stalking&#8217; EP, which came out in 2007. The EP contained tracks of mid-tempo house, each coming from a different musical angle and giving the world a taste of what he was capable of. It was received by the deep house and neo-disco community with open arms. Top-flight DJ&#8217;s such as Prins Thomas, Ashley Beedle and Jimpster went wild for it. Bill Brewster made the EP the Single Of The Month in iDJ magazine. Lovebirds had landed.

His second single for Winding Road was slamming vocal track &#8216;Love On My Hands&#8217;, which featured the voice of Holly Backler. As with the first EP, this release drew much praise from the deep house cognoscenti and put Basti ever more firmly on the map. Most recently, July 2008 sees the release of third single for Winding Road, &#8216;In The Shadows&#8217;. Once again, an extremely classy offering received by the tastemakers to great acclaim.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Lovebirds" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/lovebirdmusic" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/lovebirds/" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Lovebirds" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1344715200" id="jimpster" startTime="1344709800" title="Jimpster"><itemDescription>Jimpster is a solo project of - Essex, UK producer, remixer &amp; DJ - Jamie O&#8217;Dell (aka Audiomontage &amp; Tea Dancers). He has been active for 15 years &amp; co-running Freerange (aka Freerange Records), for the last ten. His musical upbringing &amp; open minded attitude, to all types of music, has resulted in his productions finding fans internationally, in the electronica, downtempo &amp; house scenes.

His seminal Jimpster LP Messages From The Hub (1997) as well as his more dancefloor orientated Audiomontage 12&#8221;s really helped establish Jamie as an artist of some merit and he quickly became in regular demand as a remixer (over 50 at the last count!) and co producer on a wide range of underground projects. His third Jimpster LP Amour has just been released on Freerange to great critical acclaim and is already appearing in various published Top 20 LP&#8217;s of the year (eg. No.17 in IDJ). He has also recently released his first original track for another label, choosing Ben Watt&#8217;s Buzzin&#8217; Fly for Square Up. This has been a big track which has sat in the top 5 of DJ Mag&#8217;s Hype Chart for a month.

Jamie has also built up his reputation as a highly regarded dj in the UK but even more so abroad. With an emphasis on top quality house music, but never afraid to stray from the path, he retains a freestyle approach that has seen him booked for gigs as diverse as Fabric and Plastic People in London, Cocoon in Frankfurt and 11 in Amsterdam.
</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jimpster" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jimpster" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jimpster" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/jimpster" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Jimpster" type="discogs" /></item></line></schedule>