<?xml version="1.0"?><schedule id="nl.luminosity.2012" title="Luminosity Beach Festival 2012" xmlns="http://gaa.st/giggity#sched"><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/google.png" id="google" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/lastfm.png" id="lastfm" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/wikipedia.png" id="wikipedia" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/myspace.png" id="myspace" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/soundcloud.png" id="soundcloud" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/discogs.png" id="discogs" /><linkType icon="http://wilmer.gaa.st/deoxide/youtube.png" id="youtube" /><line id="waikikibeach" title="Waikiki Beach"><item endTime="1340454000" id="aerofoil" startTime="1340449200" title="Aerofoil"><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/aerofoil-music" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Aerofoil" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340458800" id="bartclaessen" startTime="1340454000" title="Bart Claessen"><itemDescription>Bart Claessen (also known under the pseudonym Barthezz) was born in the Netherlands on January 22nd, 1980, always loved music and got his first piano lessons at the age of seven. Impressed by electronic music at the end of the nineties, he worked hard during high school to buy his first studio equipment: a synth, a sampler, an Atari computer and a small mixer. With this equipment, he changed the attic of his parental house into a small studio and there it all began&#8230;

After graduating from high school, he started studying Music Technology at the Utrecht School Of Arts and impressed the dance scene one year later, in 2001, with his fist release ever: Barthezz &#8211; On The Move.
With top dj support, it started as a massive dancehit in his home country and ended up as a worldwide charthit with releases on labels like Positiva (UK), Superstar (Germany), avex (Japan) and Ultra (US). Top 10 positions in single charts of over ten countries were achieved, nominations for two dutch TMF Awards and almost 150.000 copies were sold in Germany only. The follow-up, Infected, had almost the same success.
This, together with many worldwide dj gigs (Trance Energy and Impulz in the Netherlands, Innercity New Zealand, Tokyo, Barcelona, Moscow, Beiruth, Warschau, Vancouver and more), placed him in the top regions of dance music instantly.

After a long break it was time to try something new and Bart decided to release his new tunes under his own name: Bart Claessen.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, electronic, house, techno</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Bart+Claessen" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bart_Claessen" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/bartclaessen" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/bartclaessen" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Bart+Claessen" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340463600" id="ummetozcan" startTime="1340458800" title="Ummet Ozcan"><itemDescription>Ummet Ozcan iUmmet Ozcan, originally from Turkish descent but rooted in The Netherlands, is best known for the production of grand Trance records. His releases can mostly be found in the highest regions of the Beatport trance charts and are supported by A-list DJs like Sander van Doorn, Armin van Buuren, Ti&#235;sto and Markus Schulz. Hits include &#8216;TimeWave Zero&#185; (Doorn Records), Arcadia (Doorn Records), Shamballa (Reset) and many more. Ummet is also known for his softsynth and soundbank design for well established music software houses like Rob Papen (Albino, Predator) and Acces Music (Virus).

www.ummetozcan.com

Tags: trance, tech trance, tech-trance, progressive trance, electronic</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Ummet+Ozcan" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Ummet+Ozcan" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Ummet+Ozcan" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340468400" id="marcelwoods" startTime="1340463600" title="Marcel Woods"><itemDescription>Even though his star is rising exponentially, Dutch &#8216;bon vivant&#8217; Marcel Woods really knows what it&#8217;s like to stay down to earth. With a respectable list of banging floor fillers to his credit Woods refuses repetition and is on a constant quest for new innovations. It is because of this attitude that he is in the same league as the greatest trance oriented DJs in the Netherlands. However, hating the confinement of being tagged, Woods therefore always thinks outside the box, leaving the techno and trance label far behind him. Only when something is &#8216;Raw &amp; Energetic&#8217; &#8211; and only then - it deserves the Marcel Woods mark.

Musical Madness has become the creed under which Marcel flies the world, with &#8211; so far - 2005 and 2006 as absolute first class years. For there aren&#8217;t that many DJs around that can say that they have had the honour to have headlined both Mysteryland and DanceValley festivals in one season. And it is not just DJing, it&#8217;s also producing massive tracks, because one mustn&#8217;t forget that Marcel is the producer of the &#8216;most downloaded track of all times&#8217; on the DJ Download Portal. This wasn&#8217;t Woods&#8217; first contact with chart success. Ever since 2004 all of the singles he&#8217;s released made it to #1 in many national and even international charts with 2006 Trance Energy Anthem &#8216;Advanced&#8217; as absolute bestseller. Early 2006 Marcel kicks in hard yet again when Pete Tong proclaimed &#8216;Monotone&#8217; BBC 1&#8217;s Essential Tune.

It is because of this success that DJ Marcel Woods is in such massive demand.

Tags: trance, hard trance, tech trance, electronic, techno</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Marcel+Woods" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marcel_Woods" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/marcelwoods" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Marcel+Woods" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340473200" id="simonpatterson" startTime="1340468400" title="Simon Patterson"><itemDescription>From being the driving force in the engine rooms of two of the biggest shows on Radio 1, he utilised his finely tuned ear working as the tastemaker behind Seb Fontaine and Judge Jules, peak-time Saturday nighters. Drawing on all the knowledge gained, and an unparallel passion for music, he has now thrust himself firmly at the forefront, and is firmly forging his own career as an in-demand DJ, producer and remixer.

His style can only be described as Cutting edge, dark, driving, pulsating. In the past five years Simon has really clocked up the air miles, rocking some of the biggest parties on offer. Recently he has plied his trade in Rotterdam for crowds of up to 500,000; he has performed at the sun-drenched dance Mecca that is Ibiza year in, year out; and he has completed a huge tour of the far-east and an indoor festival in Russia where he gave 20,000 Muscovites a musical masterclass.

Last summer Patterson graced the world stage at Dance Valley, Sunrise, HI-FI, Planet Love, Mexico Stadium, plus various dates in Ibiza, Dubai, Malta, Netherlands, Canada, Germany and Cyprus and countless UK performances.

His production debut track in 2006, entitled &#8216;F-16&#8217;, was massive; &#8216;Strip Search&#8217;/&#8217;Panic Attack&#8217; is the scheduled follow up.

Simon&#8217;s alter ego is one half of the massive Dogzilla with Richard Kayvan, most famous for recording the ever-popular &#8216;Without You&#8217;, which spawned the new rock trance movement.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, uplifting trance, tech-trance, electronic</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Simon+Patterson" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Simon_Patterson_(musician)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/simonpatterson" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/simonpatterson" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Simon+Patterson" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340478000" id="john00fleming" startTime="1340473200" title="John '00'Fleming"><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/john00fleming" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/john00fleming/john-00-fleming-global-8" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/John+'00'+Fleming" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340482800" id="seantyas" startTime="1340478000" title="Sean Tyas"><itemDescription>According to NY-born, Switzerland-based trance man Sean Tyas, the electronic storm over the US Billboard Charts won&#8217;t influence the music he makes one iota; he does, however, find it extremely encouraging.
As main players of the scene jump ship to collaborate with artists Simon Cowell probably still has wet dreams about having discovered, Tyas&#8217; game-plan is to continue doing his own thing and wait for the kids to follow, as minds across the super-nation yield to electronic styles travelling from across the Atlantic.

&#8220;In America, if you look at the average of people at dance music festivals, it&#8217;s clear kids are really getting into it,&#8221; asserts Sean. &#8220;Minds and tastes are being moulded at those events, so it&#8217;s a really good time to have a crack at it and gain a bunch of fans right off the bat.&#8221;
As a result, there is no time like the present for Sean to try new things, he points out. While pushing forward on the same uptempo tip, the discovery of his year was that dubstep shares the same BPM. Thus, jilted time signatures, bone-crunching breakdowns and chainsaw electro-tinged melodies are now finding their way into both his DJ sets and productions, to euphoric effect.
&#8220;With trance, sounds are constantly being recycled,&#8221; he admits. &#8220;But if you integrate that dubstep texture into trance, it really adds something.&#8221;

You only need hear his remix of Argentinean duo Phun Park (&#8216;Midnight&#8217;) - on Tytanium Recordings, started by Sean earlier in the year - to see what he means.

Tags: trance, uplifting trance, progressive trance, electronic, hard trance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Sean+Tyas" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sean_Tyas" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/seantyas" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/seantyas" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Sean+Tyas" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340487600" id="johnocallaghan" startTime="1340482800" title="John O'Callaghan"><itemDescription>1) John O&#8217;Callaghan is an Irish DJ, mainly producing electronic music. He also produces music under the alias of Joint Operations Centre, Mannix and Stenna. He has also collaborated with fellow Discover artists such as Bryan Kearney, Neal Scarborough (as Inertia), Thomas Bronzwaer (as Lost World) and Greg Downey. His best known track is Big Sky, done with vocalist Audrey Gallagher, formerly of the 90&#8217;s alt-rock band Scheer.

O&#8217;Callaghan has had the majority of his work released on Discover, the British record label set up by John Askew. Recently, his work has been released by sub-labels of the Armada Music label; primarily on Armind and Soundpiercing. The remix of his vocal trance production &#8220;Big Sky&#8221; by Agnelli &amp; Nelson was voted &#8220;Tune of The Year&#8221; by listeners of Armin van Buuren&#8217;s A State of Trance radio show in 2007.

In addition to numerous single releases, he has released a live album (Discover &#8220;Live As&#8221; Volume 2) and an artist album, Something To Live For. He entered the DJ Mag 100 in 2008 at number 60.

In 2009 he released his second artist album &#8220;Never Fade Away&#8221;, which includes famous track &#8220;Big Sky&#8221;.

2) John O&#8217;Callaghan is the singer of the Arizona American based pop group, &#8216;The Maine&#8217;.

Tags: trance, vocal trance, uplifting trance, progressive trance, melodic trance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/John+O%27Callaghan" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_O'Callaghan_(DJ)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/johnocallaghan" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/edmtunestv/john-ocallaghan-live-beyond-wonderland-asot-550-san-bernadino-usa-03-17-2012" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/John+O'Callaghan" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340492400" id="artentodivini" startTime="1340487600" title="Artento Divini"><itemDescription>Artento Divini started spinning the wheels of steel at the age of 19.

Within a short while he was spinning at his own parties. It didn&#8217;t take long before he got in contact with the owner of the Scala Dance Theatre (Netherlands) where he became resident DJ. Artento performed besides great names like: Marco V, Bas &amp; Ram and Hennes &amp; Cold. The Friday nights became so successful and Divini&#8217;s name was set.

In the year of 2002 things picked up fast. He spinned at Xxlerator, (Club Matrixx) and Index in Germany. To top it all off, he picked up his suitcase and went 3 months to Manaus, Brazil, performing at several clubs and parties like Eco System 2.0, Amazon&#8217;s largest jungle party.

Back from Brazil and fully inspired, Artento was invited to perform at a club in Amsterdam. In this club he met his budy Melvin Warning, they started a collaboration and the duo Divini &amp; Warning was born.

They spinning together in trendy clubs like XL, Lexion and The Hemkade. In the year 2006 they performed a back to back session at the main stage of Pleasure Island.
In 2006 Divini &amp; Warning delivered a smashing techtrance monsterhit with the track &#8220;4LB&#8221;. The tune got picked up by Paul van Dyk, Armin van Buuren, DJ Tiesto, Marco V and many others. Armin even used this track as an opening theme at the main stage of Dance Valley Festival 2006.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, tech-trance, electronic, electronica</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Artento+Divini" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/artentodivini" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/artentodivini" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Artento+Divini" type="discogs" /></item></line><line id="hawaii" title="Hawaii"><item endTime="1340454600" id="basiloglue" startTime="1340449200" title="Basil O'Glue"><itemDescription>Basil O&#8217;Glue (Haris Vasiloglou) born and raised in Athens,
now lives in a small city near Thessaloniki &#8211; Northern Greece.
He has studied 3d animation and graphic design, and now works as a photographer.
As a teenager he loved electronic music, especially bands as The Prodigy,
The Chemical Brothers etc. A few years later he started to produce his own music
with some amateur software. His first attempts were really not cool,

but after getting his first midi keyboard and some equipment while learning new programs,
there was an obvious improvement.His producing tools are, Propellerheads Reason,
some mastering vst plug-in and a couple of good monitors!

Tags: progressive trance, trance, electronic, progressive house, electronica</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Basil+O%27Glue" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/basiloglue" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/saintjulesmusic/mike-saint-jules-vs-basil-o-glue-nova-flare" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Basil+O'Glue" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340460000" id="oliversmith" startTime="1340454600" title="Oliver Smith"><itemDescription>There are two Oliver Smith&#8217;s. A DJ from the UK and a Folk musician who was signed to Elektra Records.

1. Oliver Smith has been described as &#8220;an excellent DJ&#8221; by Armin van Buuren, &#8220;the best thing to happen in trance&#8221; by Mixmag and &#8220;sensational&#8221; by DJ magazine. In recent years the highly successful UK trance DJ and producer has released over 50 records and remixes and has performed as a DJ in many of the biggest clubs around the world so it&#8217;s no wonder he&#8217;s in great demand.

Oliver&#8217;s music is regularly played by leading DJs such as Tiesto, Ferry Corsten, Armin van Buuren, Paul van Dyk and Above &amp; Beyond. In addition to this, Oliver&#8217;s work as one half of the highly acclaimed production duo Smith &amp; Pledger has assured him a place as one of the leading figures in the trance scene. His tracks are a regular feature on compilations such as Anjunabeats Volume 6, which features a record breaking five Oliver Smith productions. Meanwhile, on the remix front, Oliver has been making waves with his remixes for Signalrunners, Jaytech, Maor Levi and Above &amp; Beyond - all featuring on leading radio and club play lists and flying high in the Beatport charts.

As a DJ, Oliver has played at legendary UK super clubs such as Ministry of Sound, Godskitchen, The Gallery, and Matter; and at far flung locations worldwide such as America, Switzerland and Singapore. He also regularly features on international radio shows and is a resident presenter of Anjunabeats Worldwide.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, uplifting trance, anjunabeats, electronic</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Oliver+Smith" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/oliversmithmusic" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Oliver+Smith" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Oliver+Smith" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340465400" id="airbase" startTime="1340460000" title="Airbase"><itemDescription>The Airbase story begins in 1994 when he got his hands on the software Scream Tracker pitched to him by a Finnish cousin. A few years later, Airbase switched to better software that came highly recommended from others called Fast Tracker. The following years were kept busy with hard work which rendered numerous tracks, but also a lot of knowledge and understanding in how to produce, arrange and write melodies. With the first full time employment pay check received in early 2000, the first piece of hardware was bought, the Yamaha CS2x Control Synthesizer. For almost 2 years, a large number of tracks were created using the CS2x tool. However, with building frustrations, Airbase felt he could no longer bring anything new to his productions using only this piece of hardware. In 2001, a friend showed him the new exciting Swedish software, Propellerheads Reason. Soon after, Airbase flew right into producing with Reason, ditching Cubase in only days, using the CS2x as a midi keyboard only.

In a short time with Reason, the track Airbase - Emotion had been created, which caught the attention of the German label Alphabet City. Airbase was offered his first record deal, and in early 2002, Emotion was released. During the wait for Emotion to get released, the track Genie was produced and was instantly chosen to be the follow up of Emotion. With support from the top jocks, requests for remixes and original records for other labels came pouring in. This has kept him constantly busy ever since.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, uplifting trance, electronic, vocal trance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Airbase" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/airbase" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Airbase" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340470800" id="kyaualbert" startTime="1340465400" title="Kyau &amp; Albert"><itemDescription>Kyau &amp; Albert, formerly known as Kyau vs. Albert, is a German duo consisting of Ralph Kyau and Steven Moebius Albert, which has been active since 1995 on the trance scene as both remixers and producers. In 1997 they founded the German recorded label Euphonic.

In August 2006, prior to the release of the single &#8220;Are You Fine?,&#8221; it was announced that the duo had dropped the &#8220;vs.&#8221; from their name and were renamed Kyau &amp; Albert. Other aliases they use are Black Emanuelle, Dope the Globe, Moebius AG, and Quad.

http://www.kyauandalbert.com

Tags: trance, progressive trance, vocal trance, electronic, dance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Kyau+%26+Albert" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kyau_%26_Albert" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/kyauandalbert" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/kyauandalbert" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Kyau+%26+Albert" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340476200" id="andymoor" startTime="1340470800" title="Andy Moor"><itemDescription>Andy Moor (real name Andrew Beardmore), was born in 1980. DJ/producer/remixer from Stoke On Trent, UK. This is a discography of all releases by his (Sworn, Dub Disorder, Dwight van Mann) and related projects (Indigo, Leama &amp; Moor, Tilt, Whiteroom, Zoo DJ&#8217;s) known by me.

This DJ/Producer and musician&#8217;s talents were picked up on at 5 years old when he had his first keyboard and instantly started playing songs which he subconsciously knew. At 7 he had composed complex music which exceeded GCSE examinations which teenagers take at 16 years old, teachers were amazed and made him take up other instruments and sent him to a musical high school.

Following the progression of house music through the 90&#8217;s Andy knew what he wanted to do, but didn&#8217;t know how to do it so classical music was the only style which schools would fund which was to give him real musical knowledge. Many of nights were spent hanging around outside Shelly&#8217;s in Stoke trying to get a listen to the &#8220;new&#8221; music which everyone was talking about. Still in his early teens he got hold of tapes from these nights and started making music in this style on his cheapy Yamaha keyboard.

Frustrated by this lack of technology at his disposal he had to keep working with the orchestra&#8217;s playing his bassoon and piano whilst he waited for the school to get some technology. This never happened so at 16 he was balancing further education with unpaid work at a studio which produced many a top 10 hit to gain priceless experience.

Saving his money from DJing at mobile disco&#8217;s he gradually built up his equipment to enable him to finally make real electronic music. He was producing pop bands and trance music with successful outcomes under various disguises until the `stoke on Trent old timers&#8217; showed him the way.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, melodic trance, electronic, progressive house</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Andy+Moor" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Andy_Moor_(DJ)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/andymoor" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/djandymoor" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Andy+Moor" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340481600" id="super8tab" startTime="1340476200" title="Super8 &amp; Tab"><itemDescription>Only a select number of modern trance artists can convincingly say they are taking the sound to the next level. Although the humble, softly spoken duo would never shout it out themselves, Super8 &amp; Tab are undoubtedly among them.

Renowned for their innovative approach and intricate production values, the Finnish producers have stealthily pushed themselves to the front of the trance pack since coming together in 2005.
DJs like Armin van Buuren, PVD, Above &amp; Beyond &amp; Ferry Corsten regularly smash their tracks both club-side and on the radio, while global dance bibles such as Mixmag and DJmagazine laud them with 5 star reviews.

Through their own energising DJ sets, Super8 &amp; Tab themselves have conquered some of the biggest club brands in the game. They headlined the Future stage at this year&#8217;s Trance Energy, recently played Australia&#8217;s Future Music Festival and have also rocked trance totem poles like The Gallery, Mayday, Godskitchen, Trance Energy and A State Of Trance. On home turf, they command a legendary residency at Helsinki&#8217;s legendary Hallmark club and also find time to hold down a regular spot on the monthly Anjunabeats Worldwide radio show.
Now an integral part of the Anjunabeats family, Super8 &amp; Tab first caused a fervour with the breakthrough success of tracks like &#8216;First Aid&#8217; and the definitive &#8216;Helsiniki Scorchin&#8217;. Since establishing themselves as the label&#8217;s best selling artist behind Above &amp; Beyond, the Finnish trailblazers have delivered trance of the highest quality ever since - their ethereal epic &#8216;Suru&#8217; was picked out by DJmagazine as &#8220;the tent-pole release of Anjuna&#8217;s summer&#8221;, while &#8216;Elektra&#8217; conquered the download charts and festival stages with equal aplomb in 2008.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, uplifting trance, anjunabeats, electronic</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Super8+%26+Tab" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super8_%26_Tab" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/super8anddjtab" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/super8tab" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Super8+%26+Tab" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340487000" id="solarstone" startTime="1340481600" title="Solarstone"><itemDescription>Solarstone is a British musician/production/DJ team formed by Rich Mowatt, Andy Bury (1994-2006) and Sam Tierney (1994-1997), renowned for producing and releasing melodic trance, progressive house and chillout since 1994.

In the past Solarstone has also been known under various aliases including Young Parisians, Z2, Liquid State, Skyscraper, 2nd Element and Sebatu as well as having produced three collaborations with Scott Bond. Most recently in 2011 Rich started the Federation project alongside Ben Lost releasing tracks on the Perfecto Fluoro label.

The most popular Solarstone releases to date include &#8216;Seven Cities&#8217;, &#9679;Solarcoaster, &#8216;Late Summer Fields&#8217;, &#8216;The Calling&#8217;, &#8216;Rain Stars Eternal&#8217;, and &#9679;4Ever.

Solarstone&#8217;s label interests currently include co-owning the well known Solaris Recordings, pioneering the experimental Molecule Recordings, the uplifing Crashing Waves label and the newly launched Touchstone Recordings in 2012. Past interests include co-owning Deep Blue Records (1999-2008) and running Insatiable Records, which in 2009 morphed into solarSwarm Recordings - the world&#8217;s very first social network record label.

Rich hosts the Solaris International radio show every week on AH.fm and accross 50 other FM radio stations. The show was previously co-hosted with Robbie Nelson of Agnelli &amp; Nelson fame under the name Deepblue Radio Show. It has been broadcast for over 6 years and in 2012 reached it&#8217;s 300th show.

Official website: www.solarstone.co.uk
Un-official Last.fm group: Solar Stone.

Tags: trance, melodic trance, progressive trance, uplifting trance, electronic</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Solarstone" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/solarstone" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/solarstone" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Solarstone" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340492400" id="mennodejong" startTime="1340487000" title="Menno de Jong"><itemDescription>Menno de Jong is a 24 year old DJ from the Netherlands. He is the owner and founder of Intuition Recordings. He also has his very own podcast at http://www.mennodejong.com, released and aired on ETN.fm&#8217;s trance stream the first Wednesday of the month.

Menno has played at some of the biggest and most noteworthy events including Gatecrasher and Godskitchen. He has also seen huge success at events such as The Love Parade in Berlin and many others as well as travelled extensively the world over.

Menno&#8217;s &#8220;Tundra&#8221; (2005) (on his own label Intuition), &#8220;Guanxi&#8221; , &#8220;Majestic&#8221; &amp; &#8220;Second Thoughts&#8221; and other famous remixes, help placed him at #62 in the Top Dj List of 2008.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, uplifting trance, melodic trance, electronic</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Menno+de+Jong" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Menno_de_Jong" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/mennodejong" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/mennodejong/menno-de-jong-never-lose-the" type="soundcloud" /></item><item endTime="1340542800" id="orkidea" startTime="1340535600" title="Orkidea"><itemDescription>Despite his age (born &#8216;77), DJ Orkidea (or Orkidea) has been one of Finland&#8217;s and Scandinavia&#8217;s leading trance and progressive trance DJs for over ten years.

His background lies in illegal squat parties and big finnish raves of the 90&#8217;s. He has played around Finland in all major clubs and events. Recently also Cream, Renaissance, Gatecrasher, Global Underground and Prodigy have used Orkidea on their tours to Finland. Today he holds residencies and runs his own Unity, Jack and Sun club nights and the Renaissance events in Helsinki.

Foreign Gigs
During the last few years Orkidea&#8217;s foreign gigs have been rapidly growing and he has played at such legendary venues as Tresor and WMF (Berlin, Germany), Pacha (Ibiza, Spain), Panama (Amsterdam, Netherlands), Club CODE (Tokyo, Japan), Nature One Festival (Frankfurt, Germany), Viva (Toronto, Canada), Roskilde Festival (Denmark), Fokused (Stockholm, Sweden) and Tunnel (St.Petersburg, Russia) as well as some more exotic venues in Cairo, Macedonia and Murmansk.

At these parties in Finland and abroad Orkidea has played alongside such world class DJs and bands as Tiesto, sven vath, Paul van Dyk, Dave Seaman,Mark Spoon, Armin Van Buuren, BT, Jose Padilla, Prodigy and The Orb.

Records
Orkidea&#8217;s recording career started with Unity released in 1999 by London based Steelfish Records. Unity was immediately in Top 10 of such legendary DJs as Paul Oakenfold, Sasha, John Digweed, Dave Seaman &amp; DJ Tiesto and was also included on Renaissance and Gatecrasher compilations. Both Sasha and Paul Oakenfold used Unity as the opening track for their BBC1 Essential Mixes on NYE 1999 and at Homelands 2000.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, electronic, finnish, uplifting trance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Orkidea" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/orkidea" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Orkidea" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Orkidea" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340548200" id="airwavelive" startTime="1340542800" title="Airwave Live"><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/angelsandairwaves" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Airwave+Live" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340553600" id="giuseppeottavianilive" startTime="1340548200" title="Giuseppe Ottaviani Live"><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Giuseppe_Ottaviani" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/edmtunestv/giuseppe-ottaviani-live-a-state-of-trance-550-den-bosch-31-03-2012" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Giuseppe+Ottaviani+Live" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340560800" id="alyfila" startTime="1340553600" title="Aly &amp; Fila"><itemDescription>Aly Amr Fathalah (Aly) and Fadi Wassef Naguib (Fila), the Egyptian duo, were both born in 1981 and have known each other since kindergarten. After falling in love with the music of Paul van Dyk, Steve Helstrip and Chicane they built their first small studio and started doing electronic music and DJ&#8217;ing from 1999. After establishing themselves in Egypt, they decided to go international. In 2002, they signed with the prominent German record label, Euphonic Records. Their first release, &#8220;Eye of Horus&#8221; received huge airplay from the likes of Paul van Dyk, Armin van Buuren, DJ Ti&#235;sto, and many others. Due to the tracks huge success it was licensed to Fundamental Recordings in Holland and reached number 4 position in the Dutch Dance charts. &#8220;Solid Globe has got hold of it. Eye Of Horus was always quite light in terms of style. That didn&#8217;t stop it from having an army of admirers.&#8221; (DJ Magazine, July issue 2004). Not only that, but it was also featured on many successful compilations such as Gatecrasher Resident
Transmission 02, Viva Club Rotation, Mexico Love Parade, Energy 03, to name but a few.

After finishing their contract with Euphonic Records, Fila met with Andy Prinz and they decided to launch their first sublabel of Offshore. Upcoming Egyptian releases would follow. Their first release through Offshore Music Switzerland / AP Pro Audio &#8216;Spirit Of KA&#8217; already made it on numerous playlists. The track has already been played several times by Paul van Dyk and Markus Schulz who did a remix for it.

Tags: trance, uplifting trance, progressive trance, melodic trance, electronic</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Aly+%26+Fila" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aly_%26_Fila" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/alyfila" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/edmtunestv/aly-and-fila-live-at-a-state-of-trance-550-los-angeles-17-03-2012" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Aly+%26+Fila" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340566200" id="leonbolier" startTime="1340560800" title="Leon Bolier"><itemDescription>Leon Bolier was born in 1980 somewhere in the middle of Holland, and always was in love with moody music.
When he heard Energy 52&#8217;s Cafe Del Mar he fell in love with melodic trance, and quit producing hardcore house.
In 2002 and 2003 he got his first record deals, together with his brother Bart. They released some tracks on Bonzai/Banshee and FTM sublabels. Back then the first contacts with Armada frontman Maykel Piron were established via Armin van Buuren, and this resulted in Leon remixing the first ever Armada release.

Nowadays Leon releases stuff on labels like Armada Music, Blackhole Recordings, Spinnin Records and Sweden-based Captured Music (Bart quit musicproducing due to the fact that he started his own company that provides in garden-architecture). He uses different guises for different styles, this resulting in progressive, trance, techy and even electro influenced releases on those various labels. His releases have been caned by the worlds big djs, like: Tiesto, Armin van Buuren, Paul van Dyk, Ferry Corsten, Sasha, John Digweed, Paul Oakenfold, Marco V and many many more. Besides. his tracks have been compiled on CDs by e.g. Tiesto (In Search of Sunrise) and Armin van Buuren (A State of Trance), and on other big compilations.
Due to these successes he&#8217;s been a popular remixer now, and becomes a more and more well known DJ, getting more and more gigs, in the Netherlands and abroad.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, tech trance, tech-trance, electronic</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Leon+Bolier" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leon_Bolier" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/leonbolier" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/edmtunestv/leon-bolier-live-at-trancefusion-prague-14-04-2012" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Leon+Bolier" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340571600" id="danielkandi" startTime="1340566200" title="Daniel Kandi"><itemDescription>Daniel Kandi (Danish) was originally a producer known for his remixes. His remix team, Hit &#8216;N&#8217; Run, worked with such danish artists as Tue West, Thomas Helmig, TV2, Christine Milton, Sisse Marie, and Infernal, as well as artist from other countries, such as Pain &amp; Rosini, Terri Walker, and David Morales.

He then turned his musical experience and focus onto the trance scene, recording on the Anjunabeats label.

Tags: trance, uplifting trance, progressive trance, anjunabeats, epic trance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Daniel+Kandi" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daniel_Kandi" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/danielkandi" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Daniel+Kandi" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340578800" id="ferrytayleb2bmanuellesaux" startTime="1340571600" title="Ferry Tayle B2B Manuel le Saux"><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Ferry+Tayle+B2B+Manuel+le+Saux" type="google" /></item></line><line id="fijibeach" title="Fiji Beach"><item endTime="1340457000" id="estiva" startTime="1340452800" title="Estiva"><itemDescription>Steven Baan, in the music scene better known as Estiva, was born in 1987 in a small town called Reeuwijk located in the Netherlands.
At a very young age Steven fell in love with melodic trancemusic inspired by the summer. Hearing music from compilations as &#8220;In Search Of Sunrise&#8221; by Tiesto, made him want to create this kind of music also. His producing skills were improving and early 2006 the wish to get his own music out in the world became reality.

His dream debute came with the release of his Stella EP. This record, released by Enhanced Recordings, was picked up by the biggest DJ&#8217;s in the world such as Armin van Buuren. This encouraged Steven to keep on doing his thing in music. From that day on he was determined to show the world his creativeness in music.

It was early 2008 when Tiesto got his hands on Estiva&#8217;s collaboration with his friend Marninx &#8216;Casa Grande&#8217;. A dream came true when Tiesto decided to put this track on &#8220;In Search of Sunrise 7&#8243;.
With his latest Strawberry Fields EP getting the likes of number one dj Armin van Buuren, Tiesto and Ferry Corsten the succes story continues&#8230;

Tags: trance, uplifting trance, progressive trance, electronic, enhanced recordings</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Estiva" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/estivamusic" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Estiva" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Estiva" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340461200" id="juventa" startTime="1340457000" title="Juventa"><itemDescription>Born in the Netherlands on the 4th of October 1994, Jordin Post (better known as Juventa) is quite early to enter the electronic music scene. He has been producing since he was seven, but just recently started to make some real progress in his career as a producer. Inspired by the electronic music he had been hearing for several years, he began producing music in 2000. Since then his techniques grew rapidly, learning most by himself. Though he hasn&#8217;t stopped developing yet, he has already managed to create his own recognizable style and sound, which can be defined as a blend of Uplifting and Progressive Trance. Having huge support already and working together with some big names, this is probably just the start of something great. With several releases coming soon, there will be many more for sure&#8230;

Tags: trance, uplifting trance, progressive trance, electronic, melodic trance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Juventa" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/juventa" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Juventa" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Juventa" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340465400" id="gregdowney" startTime="1340461200" title="Greg Downey"><itemDescription>Greg Downey began DJing over 6 years ago and in this time has established himself firmly among the best young DJs in the UK. Born in Belfast - Ireland, Greg developed a taste for tougher electronic dance music from a young age. He has reflected this in his unique style which combines underground and uplifting trance with elements of techno&#8230; The result&#8230; An Explosive sound!

2007 has been an amazing year so far for Greg&#8230; He has a full summer ahead with dates across the UK including top notch clubs Lush, Inside Out, Goodgreef, Gatecrasher, The Gallery and a host of others as well as dates planned for Canada, Godskitchen in Shanghai, Indonesiaand Finland to name but a few&#8230; On top of that, the coming months only sees Greg set to perform alongside some of the industries most credible artists at this years massive Planet Love Festival in Northern Ireland. Here will see Greg recording his first Live As album in front of his home crowd, for the mighty Discover label due for release later this year, so keep your ears peeled!

Greg&#8217;s DJ performance is one not to be missed. Using 3 CDJs, Serato Scratch Live, Pioneer DJM 800 and EFX 1000 to devastating effect, one thing that you can be sure of is that Greg will rock your club!

Tags: trance, uplifting trance, tech-trance, melodic trance, electronic</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Greg+Downey" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/gregdowney" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/greg-downey" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Greg+Downey" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340469600" id="ronnyk" startTime="1340465400" title="Ronny K"><itemDescription>Ronny K. was born on 1st August 1974 at Trinec, Czech Republic. In 1991 he started his career as a DJ. He was learning to mix on vinyl decks (later on CD players) under the direction of professional DJs. After 4 years of practice he DJs solo and starting to produce his own music. His first projects were called Exhibit, Sonic Empire and FM FACTORY, which rised in 1997 and was devoted to commercial genre of music. The first album of this project, called The Album, arose in 2001. It included debut tracks like 17 story, Get up, Give you more, Mrazik 2001, Malo je malo. Year 2003 brought fresh wind to Ronnys production. He started to produce club/house together with his friend and they formed project called Weekend Project, which was oriented on this genre.

In years 2004 and 2005 he adds new genres to his production: eurotrance, trance and uplifting trance. Meanwhile he cooperates with interactive TV channel and radio Fun1, for which he creates music graphics, jingels and signatures.

The main change has come in 2006, when he changed not only the place of his work, but even the place where he lives. He moved from Prague to London, UK.

Now he prepares one hour-long set called Trance Insurgence. New episodes are brodcasted every month on FM stations like radio GO DJ on Slovakia and his brand new show called trance4nations on famouse trance radio station Afterhours.FM. Besides mixing sets he still works on his new tracks and remixes for foreign producers.

Tags: trance, uplifting trance, balearic trance, electronic, electronica</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Ronny+K" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/moeronnyk" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/ronny-k" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Ronny+K." type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340473800" id="arcticmoon" startTime="1340469600" title="Arctic Moon"><itemDescription>Arctic Moon is one of the most exciting producers in today&#8217;s current trance scene. Recently voted in at #177 in the 2011 DJ Mag Poll he is not only a highly talented, respected and loved producer but an entertaining and exciting DJ set to take the next decade by storm.

Hailing from Poland his musical journey began during his childhood when he became fascinated by electronic dance music at an early age. He spent 3 years learning step by step how to produce music and also spent this time experimenting with different sounds until he found the one he was passionate about. In 2007 he decided that Trance was indeed his one true music love and it was then he focused on creating euphoric and uplifting Trance music encompassing elements of classical music, new age, chill out and even rock music.

As the years progressed so has the quality of his music and indeed his international profile. His name is now synonymous with labels such as the massive &#8220;Armada Music&#8221; and indeed Aly &amp; Fila&#8217;s world famous &#8220;Future Sound of Egypt Recordings&#8221;. It was on FSOE that recent singles &#8220;True Romance&#8221; and &#8220;Adelaide&#8221; were released with both tracks topping download charts, gaining a massive amount of radio plays and huge gig support from a high number of top DJs.

Tags: uplifting trance, trance, epic trance, progressive trance, electronic</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Arctic+Moon" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/arcticmoonmusic" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/arctic-moon" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Arctic+Moon" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340478000" id="bjornakesson" startTime="1340473800" title="Bjorn Akesson"><itemDescription>Bj&#246;rn &#197;kesson was born in 1986, in a town called Lund (southern Sweden). He first noticed electronic music in the middle of the 90&#8217;s when he heard music from a videogame called Wipeout 2097. With artists such as Future Sound of London, The Prodigy and Orbital the interest grew. A few years later a friend from school introduced Bj&#246;rn to trance/club music. This sounded a lot better and much more interesting than the techno he had heard before. In early 2003 Bj&#246;rn teamed up with a fellow swedish producer for a collab. The track was called Havannah &#8211; Havannah&#8217;. Havannah was played by top DJ&#8217;s like Ti&#235;sto, Armin van Buuren, Ferry Corsten, Johan Gielen, The Thrillseekers and many others.
After this collaboration Bj&#246;rn continued making his own tunes and few years later he luanched the &#8220;Akesson&#8221; project which made a big impact on Above &amp; Beyonds radioshow &#8216;Trance Around The World&#8217;.In early 2008 the track &#8216;Perfect Blue&#8217; was introduced to the world as &#8216;Tune Of The Week&#8217; by Armin van Buuren on his huge radioshow &#8216;A State Of Trance&#8217;. Both Sunchaser and Perfect Blue was very well recieved by the trance community and appeared on several big compilations mixed by world class DJ&#8217;s and released by huge recordcompanies such as Sony BGM, EMI and Ministry Of Sound.This is surely the beginning of a very successful music career for the talented young man.Today you can find Bj&#246;rn on his way out to the clubs all over Europe making his epic DJ appearances. So keep an eye out!

Tags: trance, uplifting trance, progressive trance, uplifting, electronic</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Bjorn+Akesson" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/bjornakesson" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/bjorn-akesson" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Bj%C3%B6rn+%C3%85kesson" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340482200" id="activa" startTime="1340478000" title="Activa"><itemDescription>In a relatively short time since his first release on Somatic Sense, Rob Stevenson, better known as Activa, has been one of the most hard working producers in the Trance genre. He has created many new alias&#8217; such as Solar Movement, Mekk, Substate, Force One, Aira Force, CMR and Eluna to showcase the range of his production skills, while continuously developing the sound of his main Activa alias.

Rob has appeared on the likes of Spinnin (Liquid), Discover, High Contrast, Black Hole, Enhanced, Somatic Sense and finally Paul van Dyk&#8217;s mighty Vandit Records which has enabled him to push his way into the record boxes of the biggest names in the industry and receive their continuous support.

As an engineer Rob has worked closely with Jon O&#8217;Bir to create Jon&#8217;s first artist album, From Within and has engineered and produced, singles and remixes for Jon, Aled Mann (Discover), Owen Clark (Club Elite), Freesoup (Five AM), Chris &amp; Matt Kidd (Joyride) and David Newsum (Discover), clearly showing the range and diversity of Rob&#8217;s production skills.

Although he is primarily known as a producer, Rob has been DJing since his first experience with a pair of turntables while at school. He has gone on to play at the biggest nights in the UK including Gatecrasher and Passion and regularly travels the UK and often abroad to perform. He is a bi-monthly resident at easily the best and fastest growing night in the UK, Digital Society, where his late sets have become a popular part of the night showcasing the harder side of his style.

Tags: trance, uplifting trance, progressive trance, melodic trance, uplifting</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Activa" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/activa" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Activa" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340486400" id="indecentnoise" startTime="1340482200" title="Indecent Noise"><itemDescription>Indecent Noise is Aleksander Stawierej from Warsaw (Poland).He was influenced by Paul van Dyk, John O&#8217;Callaghan, John Askew, Nu NRG and Bryan Kearney.Had his releases on this labels:Excessive Pressure, Vandit, Infrasonic, Yakuza

Tags: trance, progressive trance, uplifting trance, polish, tech-trance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Indecent+Noise" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/indecentnoise" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Indecent+Noise" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Indecent+Noise" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340490600" id="bryankearney" startTime="1340486400" title="Bryan Kearney"><itemDescription>Bryan Kearney began DJing when he was 19 years old and in this time has established himself firmly on the dance scene in Ireland. His sets contain the very best in upfront trance and techno with the emphasis always on energy and the unexpected.

He was a permanent fixture on the airwaves of Dublin throughout 2002 and 2003 with prime time shows on Energy Fm and Kiss Fm providing the capital with the very best in brand new material each week. In 2003, Bryan began his own night Tranceformation in the Crypt at the legendary Temple Theatre. Each of the three nights was a full house which in turn led to him warming up for the likes of MIKE and Lisa Lashes on the main stage.

At the same time, he had began to get into producing and obtained a Higher National Diploma in Sound Operations and Music Technology. His collaboration with John O&#8217;Callaghan entitled Restricted Motion was signed to Discover Records by label boss John Askew. Askew was so impressed with the track that he decided to designate himself for remix duties. The track has become a cult classic and one of Bryan and John&#8217;s proudest moments.

In 2005, he completed a remix of one of his all time favourite tracks, the massive Lost Emotions by Fire &amp; Ice. The track has become bigger than first thought possible with the remix been signed for full release by the legendary Bonzai Records. Bryan is the first Irish producer to have a production signed to Bonzai. The remix was featured on Matt Hardwick&#8217;s Essential Mix and was the midnight track at UK superclub Passion on NYE.

Tags: tech-trance, trance, uplifting trance, techno, electronica</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Bryan+Kearney" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bryan_Kearney" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/bryankearney" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/bryankearney" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Bryan+Kearney" type="discogs" /></item></line><line id="tranceclassics" title="Trance Classics"><item endTime="1340541000" id="tontb" startTime="1340537400" title="Ton TB"><itemDescription>Ton T.B. is one of these guys thats been around in the music industry forever. He&#8217;s probably best known for his production work with Three Drives, being responsible for the massive clubhits Greece 2000, Sunset On Ibiza,Carrera 2 and Air Traffic.

His tracks have been licensed to upfront international labels as Hooj Choons, Xtravaganza, VC Recordings and Vandit Records.

Together with his partner in music, Erik de Koning, Ton T.B. has released his stuff under many different pseudonyms, such as Tangled Universe, Legal Traders, Three Drives and Fate Federation.

At the beginning of his dj-career, Ton T.B. held various residencies in the Netherlands. Now he has played on major outdoor events DanceValley, Impulz Outdoor and Mysteryland. And has rocked established clubs as Club Space Miami , Turnmills London, Heaven London, Haoman 17 Jerusalem,Hotel Arena Amsterdam, Trance Club Heaven in Los Angeles and Privilege Ibiza. Ton T.B. Is signed to Black Hole Recordings for various projects.

His track, Electronic Malfunction, was been hammered by Ti&#235;sto on his Ti&#235;sto In Concert event,and was released on both Black Hole labels.

His single Dream Machine was played by Ti&#235;sto for months and features the vocals of Alexander Perls and was released including a remix of Marco V and Estuera. This track was even mentioned as Tune Of The Month in DJ Magazine.

Tags: trance, electronic, progressive trance, electronica, vocal trance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Ton+TB" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/tontb" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/DJ+Ton+T.B." type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Ton+TB" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340544600" id="marknorman" startTime="1340541000" title="Mark Norman"><itemDescription>Mark Norman are the award winning Dutch production duo, responsible for a series of high profile original productions and remixes. Dubbed by Tiesto as his hot prediction for the future, dance floor anthems such as Touchdown, Phantom Manor, Overkill, RUSH, and Mark Norman pres. Celine have assisted in their meteoric rise from hopefuls to fully fledged international artists in just a few years.

Signed to Black Hole Recordings on Tiesto&#8217;s own Magik Muzik label, original tracks such as Stream, which was featured on Tiesto&#8217;s DVD &#8216;Another Day at the Office&#8217;, and almost every release have also proved massively popular with the worlds leading DJs whilst Paul Oakenfold, BT, Tiesto, Turkish Pop star TARKAN and many more remain among the privileged artists to receive the Mark Norman remix touch.

Whilst remaining the only artists to have polled at number one in the Dutch DJ Charts with almost every single release, Mark Norman also remain one of only a select number of artists commissioned to mix the globally renowned &#8216;In Trance We Trust&#8217; series.

Ever growing in popularity, Mark Norman collect The Frysian Pop Award in Holland for services to Dance Music, They teamed up with an classical orchestra and did an unique project and currently they are producing some tracks for the debut album of Jes known from Motorcycle (As the rush comes).

Tags: trance, progressive trance, hard trance, uplifting trance, electronica</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Mark+Norman" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mark_Norman_(DJ)" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/deejaymarknorman" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Mark+Norman" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340549100" id="thethrillseekers" startTime="1340544600" title="The Thrillseekers"><itemDescription>The Thrillseekers

Steve Helstrip has been at the very forefront of the global dance scene for over 7 years now. From his breakout hit &#8216;Synaesthesia&#8217;, through to the anthems &#8216;Dreaming of You&#8217; and most recently &#8216;By Your Side&#8217;, he has continued to produce a powerhouse of the most emotive, evocative music going. He has remixed for luminaries such as Tiesto, Timo Maas, Sonique and Chicane, lending them all his trademark melodic, euphoric sound.

Steve has enthralled crowds the world over with both his Thrillseekers Live and DJ sets. The Ministry, Gallery, Gatecrasher and Godskitchen have all born witness to his fluid mixing, unique style and highly energetic performances. It&#8217;s these sets that saw him crack the DJ Magazine&#8217;s &#8216;Top 100 DJs&#8217; chart for the first time in 2004, and more recently break the top 50, coming in at no. 45, in Oct 2006.

Steve started out making electronic music while working for the computer games developer, Manic Media. Whilst living in Chipping Norton, on the Oxfordshire border, with a relatively basic home studio he constructed the trance milestone &#8220;Synaesthesia&#8221;. Signed and released by Neo Records in 1999, at the height of the trance boom, it went on to sell over 12,000 copies on its initial UK release.

With its vibe on the subtler side of the genre it took more than a year to fully realise its own potential however. Its road to full-blown chart success was assisted in no small part by Paul van Dyk. He took the record and gave it a six month long, gig in, gig out battering.

Tags: trance, vocal trance, electronic, chillout, ambient</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/The+Thrillseekers" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Thrillseekers" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/thethrillseekers" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/the-thrillseekers" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Thrillseekers,+The" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340553600" id="jonassteur" startTime="1340549100" title="Jonas Steur"><itemDescription>Jonas Steur, born in 1982 in Belgium, (also known under his alias Estuera) has been into music since he was very young. Influenced by his father&#8217;s favorite 70&#8217;s progressive rock with its wealth of synth sounds and his mother&#8217;s classical music, Jonas got his taste for both beautiful melodic and rougher electronic music.


After a lot of messing around with cheap Casio keyboards, Jonas got his hands on a set of turntables when he was 15, and started discovering the world of vinyl. The urge to make his own tracks grew, resulting in his first record deal when he was 17. (Silvertear - so deep)

Over the next few years, he continued improving his production skills and released a number of tracks in different styles, ranging from hard house to a trance track for the successful Ian van Dahl album &#8216;ace&#8217; in 2002.


At the end of 2003, the alias &#8216;estuera&#8217; emerged when the first estuera e.p. &#8216;travels / 7 clouds &#8217; got signed to Tiesto&#8217;s black hole recordings. Other releases followed in 2004 on different black hole sub labels, such as &#8217; in trance we trust&#8217; and the big trance hit &#8216;estuera - tales from the south&#8217; on Tiesto&#8217;s personal &#8216;magik muzik&#8217; imprint.


Jonas also got in contact with Paul Moelands and Menno de Jong who were in the process of setting up their &#8216;intuition&#8217; sub label under fundamental recordings. In 2005 the first intuition release saw the light, &#8216;Jonas Steur - Castamara / Silent waves&#8217; and got massive support by every top dj in the trance scene. Another big accomplishment was the collaboration between Paul Moelands and Jonas, &#8217; Estuera vs. Re:locate - Palma Solane &#8216;, which got featured on the huge in search of sunrise 4 Tiesto mix cd and vinyl sampler.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, uplifting trance, melodic trance, vocal trance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Jonas+Steur" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jonas_Steur" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/jonassteur" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Jonas+Steur" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340558100" id="galenbehr" startTime="1340553600" title="Galen Behr"><itemDescription>Finally the moment is here. We sure do remember Galen&#8217;s track &#8220;Wet Dream&#8221; together with partner-in-crime Leon Bolier.

Well, the new Behr was set loose and you all had the chance to have a little bite&#8230; and now he is BACK!

A new marker in the rising career of ever-developing producer Galen Behr proves he is still capable
of bringing you the freshest beats in the scene.

A new sound combined with a new era!

&#8220;SECONDS BEFORE WE LANDED WITH OUR EYES CLOSED&#8221;

OUT NOW on his own new label Parker Alley Recordings - home of many forthcoming dancefloor killers.

Already heavily supported by Markus Schulz on his Global DJ Broadcast and at events such as Mayday.

This is one NOT to be missed.

Here&#8217;s a teaser:

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dPXBen3lF6c

Grab your copy now!

BEATPORT: https://www.beatport.com/en-US/html/content/release/detail/244773/Seconds%20Before%20We%20Landed%20With%20Our%20Eyes%20Closed%20%28TM%29%20-%20Single

iTunes: http://itunes.apple.com/nl/album/seconds-before-we-landed-with/id368171837?i=368171838

TrackItDown: http://www.trackitdown.net/genre/house/track/2192975.html

Audiojelly: http://www.audiojelly.com/singles/416432

http://www.galenbehr.com
http://www.twitter.com/galenbehr
http://www.facebook.com/galenbehr
http://www.myspace.com/galenbehr
http://www.youtube.com/galenbehr

Tags: trance, progressive trance, melodic trance, uplifting trance, epic trance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Galen+Behr" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/galenbehr" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Galen+Behr" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Galen+Behr" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340562600" id="binaryfinary" startTime="1340558100" title="Binary Finary"><itemDescription>Matt Laws and Stuart Matheson are the writers in this unique project.

Growing up with Tron, Hackers and the explosion in computing &#8211; both were destined to use the technology that surrounded them to create the stunning musical soundscapes.

Through the creative use of software applications fused with various pieces of hardware they have been able to streamline the musical process into a sublime and emotional play for the listener to enjoy.

The greatest challenges have been in the preparation stages. Two years alone were spent on sampling and creating original sounds to use for the forthcoming albums and live sets.

The initial release &#8216;1998&#8217; was an epic trance monster that took Binary Finary worldwide within a year and became an all time classic overnight. The track charted in many countries as the Djs kept pumping the music out worldwide &#8211; Judge Jules amoung others used the tune to keep the crowds happy. Paul Van Dyk wanted the European clubbers to experience &#8216;1998&#8217; and remixed a successful version that took Binary Finary to the top of the German Dance charts. Kay-Cee also made an excellent chilled house mix that was eventually to become the soundtrack to the Binary Finary Video and enter into history as the first piece of English instrumental electronic music that had charted in the primarily vocal based music scene.

The track was picked up by Kevin Robinson while he was A&amp;R at Positiva (EMI) who unleashed this sonic assault on the senses to the masses of clubbers who had known the tune not knowing the people responsible for this monster. They took a great record and brought it out from the underground into the light for everyone to enjoy.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, electronic, dance, techno</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Binary+Finary" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Binary_Finary" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/binaryfinary" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://soundcloud.com/binaryfinary" type="soundcloud" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Binary+Finary" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340567100" id="signum" startTime="1340562600" title="Signum"><itemDescription>There is more than one artist under the name of Signum

1. Signum from Netherlands
2. Signum from Serbia
3. SignuM from Lithuania (rock band)

Signum is the combination of two talented producers in the European music industry. They are Pascal Minnaard, (age 29) and Ronald Hagen (also age 29). Both live in Zoetermeer, a little city nearby Hague, their home base in Netherlands.

Pascal &amp; Ron first met each other in high school. This was the place where they found out that they had the same interest in making music, and started to do some work together. Although they lost contact later, they both continued making music.

During that time, Pascal got a record contract at the Dutch label/agency BPM Dance. He made his first track there, under his own name on the label 4-Play (Inside a Rainbow). For his second release (&#8220;Flow of Knowledge&#8221;, &#8220;The Other Side&#8221;, &#8220;Adapter&#8221;), he started working under the name Signum, under the label &#8220;Jinx&#8221; from former company BPM Dance.

At this time Pascal met up with Ron again. Ron also signed up with BPM Dance and they started producing together again, not knowing that this will turn out to be a huge success. When they released their first track together, in 1997, under the JINX label, called &#8220;What you got for me&#8221;, the record became a huge club anthem. And with it&#8217;s re-release in 2001 (on TidyTrax) it even got the nr. 36 position in the UK Top40!!!! &#8220;What you got 4 me&#8221; turned out to be, what you now call, a true &#8220;Trance Classic&#8221;.

In the mean time, they did a remix for &#8220;Travel&#8221; called &#8220;Bulgarian&#8221;, which also did well in the club charts and was well received by a lot of Dj&#8217;s.

Under their own names, Ron Hagen &amp; Pascal M, they did other releases, such as &#8220;Forever&#8221;, &#8220;Take U There&#8221; and &#8220;On Stream&#8221;.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, uplifting trance, electronic, dance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Signum" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Signum" type="google" /></item><item endTime="1340571600" id="johangielen" startTime="1340567100" title="Johan Gielen"><itemDescription>Johan Gielen, born February 23rd, 1968 in the Belgium town of Mol, is a world renowned trance artist, DJ and remixer.

Johan Gielen started DJ&#8217;ing at the age of 17 in his homecountry Belgium, and has during the latest 15 years build up an international fame spinning as a DJ in Japan, Australia, Germany, Spain, Holland, Belgium, England, Northern Ireland, Israel and now also as resident DJ at Club Gorgeous in Copenhagen, Denmark and annual Trance Energy event.

Besides DJ&#8217;ing Johan is a very successful trance producer working with his &#8220;partner in music&#8221; Sven Maes. Johan and Sven are behind European smash hit&#8217;s from Airscape, Balearic Bill, Des Mitchell, Abnea, Svenson &amp; Gielen. Furthermore they are well known for their remixing skills which can be heard on productions on releases by Chicane, Delerium, Vengaboys, Ti&#235;sto, Scooter, Boy George a.o. They have proved that they are also capable of creating commercial dance hits, after finishing a single for Alice DeeJay.

After nearly two years of warming up the Saturday night party people by broadcasting his weekly radio show &#8220;Lift Off&#8221; on ID&amp;T, he decided the leave the station in favour of Fresh FM where he hosts a weekly show called &#8220;In Session&#8221; every Saturday from 21:00 to 23:00 CET.

Tags: trance, progressive trance, electronic, melodic trance, vocal trance</itemDescription><itemLink href="http://www.last.fm/music/Johan+Gielen" type="lastfm" /><itemLink href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Johan_Gielen" type="wikipedia" /><itemLink href="http://www.myspace.com/johangielen" type="myspace" /><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/artist/Johan+Gielen" type="discogs" /></item><item endTime="1340578800" id="talla2xlcb2btaucher" startTime="1340571600" title="Talla 2XLC b2b Taucher"><itemLink href="http://www.discogs.com/lists/Talla-2XLCs-Techno-Club-series/19626" type="discogs" /><itemLink href="http://www.google.com/search?q=Talla+2XLC+b2b+Taucher" type="google" /></item></line></schedule>